out. Okay, I think it's working on my head too. Guys, heads
up. Welcome to call final live how to get to if I was starting
over today, how I would get from zero to $20,000 as quickly as
possible. Appreciate you guys being on. It's 104am for me in
West Africa. But your boy, he took a shower. He's looking
fresh. He's ready to go. I told you I'd come prepared for this.
I've been working on this for a long time. Super stoked to have
you guys on. I really appreciate you being on. But I am in
Africa. So there's a chance my internet goes out. If that
happens, please stay on the live. Porter's going to be able
to be the co host. I'll hop right back on. If the power goes
out, the generator will kick on. But there's going to be a
little little gap. Please stay on and I'm going to give you
some reasons why we're going to be giving away it just for
staying on this live till the end. Number one thing we're
going to be doing is giving you guys a replay. This is not
going to stay up obviously in the free group because that's
changing. But if you stay on this live till the end, you're
going to get a replay of this live today, which I hope you
guys take and watch again and again. You dissect it. You take
notes, everything else. So please stay on that. We're also
going to be doing our giveaways. We've got a bunch of stuff
we're going to be giving away. So stay till the end. I'm going
to pack the training, going to make this really a value field
and we're going to try to end this in 55 minutes. I also want
to let you guys know, you know, what the what the transition is
because the free group is no more. OK, so Porter, you could
still hear me. We're good where everything's good. Yep, we're
good. OK, I want you to monitor the comments. I've also got
Ashley watching live because when we do the giveaways, I want
her to take notes, even though she isn't on this live that you
can see. She's there. She's watching about a whole team
watching. So, guys, let's get into it. This group, the Art of
Digital Real Estate. And by the way, it was called the Art of
Pre-selling before. As you guys know it right now, it will never
be the same as of today. OK, but today I'm going to show you
guys where it's going and how you can be a part of it, too, if
you choose. But we're also going to be doing the training. That's
the main thing is the training, the giveaways. But I do want to
let you guys know where this is going, because this is not going
to be the same as it was this morning. OK, so in addition to
the training, guys, here's what we're going to be doing. We're
going to be giving away two to two different people. We're
going to be giving away three free months of three free a
three free month membership to Rankin and Ningen. We're going to
be giving away five copies of a 12 part exclusive training
series that I did a few months back. We had some amazing
topics. One of the one of the trainings, we had some
incredible feedback. People, to my knowledge, people actually
made money from this specific training. So there's 12. It's
like 12 hours long. You're going to get we've got five
different people are going to get copies of that. We're going
to give away 10 pieces of merchandise, coffee mugs, t
shirts, mouse pads. And then guys, we're also going to give
away one, not a full but a partial scholarship to digital
landlords. OK. Also, just as a reminder, anybody that stays
till the end of this training is going to get a copy of this
training. I'm going to let you know how to do that. We got to
stay till the end to get those instructions. Again, guys, 53
minutes. We're going to buzz through this as quickly as
possible. Guys, it's been an amazing ride. It's been over 150
plus weeks of me pouring my heart and soul into this group.
And I literally mean that. OK, let me give you guys really,
really quick. Just a quick background on this group. OK, I
started it back in September of 2021. This was after I had my
very, you know, I had my first year of making seven figures
renting simple websites in 2020. Then I had another year. We did
like 1.4, 1.45 in 2021. And guys, what ended up happening is
I was sharing my journey, which I encourage you guys to do the
same. I was in other groups. I was sharing my journey in this
specific group. And I started getting people that would send
me messages. They would say, you know, Nick, how did you close
this deal up front? How did you, you know, Nick, how did you
scale to 100, 100K? That's insane. I didn't know anyone
could do that. Nick, my business owner keeps complaining about
the price. What is it? All these different questions. And at the
time, I didn't, you know, I had never had this happen. So it was
kind of fun. It was exciting. I felt I felt like my ego was
stroked a bit. And so two to three times a week, I would
spend after my day was done. It was I remember it was at
nighttime. My kids were asleep. I would spend 30 to 60 minutes
in the evening, opening the messages, turning on the camera,
responding to them directly. OK. But guys, eventually, I started
getting the same questions again and again and again. And I
realized, you know, I'm doing this is being I'm being stupid.
Let me put everybody in a free group. And then when the
question is asked, I'll just answer it once. And then
everybody can come and they can they can look at the answer,
right? Three years from now, you guys can go and look at answers
and questions that were asked three years ago. And that was
the entire goal. And so that's exactly what I did, guys. Three
over three years, three years and five months ago. And I
remember, guys, like I was doing everything at the beginning, I
was answering all the questions. I was also running my agency. I
was going live. I was doing all this kind of stuff. And I was
literally responding to every single question. I wouldn't let
a single notification pass by. So if you guys have ever heard of
Fix It Felix, our our admin, which does a phenomenal job. I
was Fix It Felix. OK, then we had somebody that came in and
helped. And then I hired somebody to help. But I was
Fix It Felix in the beginning. And that's just that's just how
it was. And it was it was super exciting. But it just wasn't
scalable. OK, guys, I've gone live over 150 times in this
group, sharing everything that I know and holding nothing back.
But what I've realized is as time has gone on, guys, I've
seen that people they've stopped appreciating what I'm doing.
And I'm not saying I need to be appreciated. But the sizzle is
gone. You know, when you send a business owner, Porter, you
know what I'm talking about? You send a business owner, those
first couple leads are super stoked. And then if you let it
go on too long, they kind of get entitled. Can't send them too
many. You can't send them too many. Right. People stop showing
up to the lives, guys. And I tried all kinds of stuff. I tried
to do them on Zoom. I tried to do a cap to number all kinds of
different stuff. And what I've just seen is a lot of people
have just become parasites, not producers. And I'm not speaking
to all of you, but a lot of people that has happened to. And
so, guys, I want I want to ask you guys, some of you guys are
going to be a little bit. I think I even had an Instagram
message from somebody that I had been talking to. In fact,
somebody that had been on one of the lives with us asked a
question. He's like, well, blah, blah, blah. You're changing the
group. And I didn't just rub me wrong. And I said, dude, same
thing. Guys, if you're sending a business owner free leads, OK,
you guys talk about, hey, we're going to have a conversation.
I'm going to send you free leads, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah. You send them three to five leads. You hop on a sales
call. You do the whole process and they tell you, you know
what? I think I can do this better on my own or I don't think
I need to pay you. I can just do it on my own. OK, we've all had
that happen. Porter, have you had that happen? Yeah. And it's
going to happen again. But the question is, are you going to
keep giving that person free leads? Obviously not. Right.
You're not going to do that. You're going to stop sending them
leads. So that's that's what this is, guys. That's all that
this is. But this isn't the what I'm doing, the value that I'm
giving me going live, all this content. It's going to a new
home. But it trust me, this is not going away. It's just
changing. OK, so guys, of course, you wouldn't give it to
them. You want you you would say, OK, good luck, go try it
out. And then once they go and try it out on their own, they're
going to come back and say, hey, yeah, those leads, what do
we got to do to work together? Right. They're going to
appreciate it because now it's gone. OK, so, guys, basically
what I'm saying is the days of free ninety nine, it's done.
OK, the the gravy train is over. You don't value what you don't
pay for. I have a thirty thousand dollar program that
somebody gave me the password to just to go and look at not even
the material, but how they structured it. It is sitting.
I have the password. I have it bookmarked. It is sitting there.
I have spent less than 30 minutes in it because I didn't pay
for it. And that's just what happens. OK, guys, I don't care
what the number of this group is. I know we have six point two
thousand members. Who cares? I don't care if after this live, we
go from six thousand two hundred people to 30 people, because
those 30 people that I'm still seeing are the people that I
want to work with, the people that are serious to the people
that are actually going to take action. OK, so here's the deal.
As of one hour ago, every single training.
Well, I don't think I think we're still working on it as we speak.
But as of one hour ago, I would say 90 percent.
And by the time this is over, by the time the day is done,
every single live training that I have ever done
personally has been deleted from the group.
OK, I've gone live over 150 times.
I've interviewed over 100 people.
Everything that I've ever done in this group personally
has been wiped. OK, it's gone.
It's done. And it is no more.
It's it's it's just gone. OK.
And there are over the next, you know, there might be a few interviews
still that we're trying to pull down, whatever.
But over the next few days, you're going to see everything disappear.
The gravy train is over.
And I want to work with the serious people only.
OK, so with that said, guys, what I'm going to do,
I'm going to spend three minutes, five minutes tops.
And I'm going to show you what right what the art of digital
real estate 2.0 looks like really quick.
I'm going to share my screen and how you can be a part of it.
And then we're going to get into the training, going to get into the giveaways
and leave you guys with a ton of value, give you guys the copies,
the replays for those of you that stay till the end.
And we're going to go from there.
So let me just do this really quick, Porter.
I'm still good on the the volume.
Yep, I can hear you perfect.
All right, guys, I want to present to you.
This is something I'm super stoked about this, guys.
I want to present to you version 2.0.
Let me just make sure I got this right. Hold on.
I don't want to be sharing anything just yet.
Let's make sure everything's good. OK.
Yes. OK, let me go ahead and get rid of this.
Guys, so with that said, I want to introduce you guys
to the rank and rent academy.
OK, that is where we are transitioning.
I'm going to show that to you right now as I share my screen.
OK, Porter, can you see my screen?
Yeah, I can see it perfectly.
Guys, welcome to the rank and rent academy.
This is a this is where our Facebook group has now gone.
And it is where it is going to be.
I'm going to give you guys a link here in just a moment
if you guys want to check it out.
But I want to just walk you through it really briefly.
Again, three minutes tops.
What we have some introductory videos
and stuff that explain how all this stuff is laid out.
But I want to walk you through the content really quick.
We have over I think it's 15 to 17 mini courses.
They call these mini courses.
You can also view them as modules.
But within each mini course, you're going to see lessons.
By the way, really quick, if you're in digital landlords
and you're freaking out going, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh,
this is not for you, you guys will have access to this.
Do not worry.
We're going to get you guys access to this
because you're part of digital landlords.
So don't be freaking out. You don't need to go whatever.
You're going to have access to this. OK.
But I do want to just show you this.
This is the classroom section.
This we're going to be adding to this every single month,
if not every single week.
I want to show you two of my favorite sections.
But obviously, guys, we talk about mapping your goals,
the mindset, tools, niches, due diligence, SEO, sales, all that kind of stuff.
This is these are two of my favorite mini courses.
Really quick. Number one is the vault.
OK, the vault, guys, is where I am going to be putting all of the library,
all hundred and fifty plus lives that we've done over the past
three and a half years are going to be found in the vault.
Right now, we have six different lives.
And every single week with that, to not overwhelm you guys,
every week, we're going to be adding one to two new lives that we did
back in twenty, twenty one, twenty, twenty two, twenty, twenty three.
We're just going to be stacking this vault with every bit of content.
OK, that module is going to be packed.
That, I guess, mini course is going to be packed with all kinds of training,
all kinds of stuff from ads to, you know, how much should this.
I mean, every nuanced topic you could possibly think about.
OK, that's that one.
The other one I want to show you guys is this, the interview series.
This is where I have interviewed over a hundred.
I think it's maybe even over 200 people, people just like you,
people from all walks of life, moms, dads, single moms, single dads,
people with speech impediments, people with accents, people with
no sales experience, people with no technical experience,
people that are retired, people that are young,
all kinds of different walks of life where I've interviewed them
and I've gleaned and I've tried to pull out what has helped them to be successful.
And we're going to have all those interviews inside of here.
Again, we're going to be adding, I think we have six in there right now.
And we're just slowly adding every single week.
We're going to be adding new interviews.
I don't want to just I didn't just want to throw everything in there
and just the vomit on you guys.
I want you guys to catch up on all the content.
And then every week you have like a little goody to watch a little
45 minute to an hour
vault video as well as the interview series.
OK, because also we have the replays, a bunch of different stuff.
Another thing I want to show you guys that's really, really cool
is we have this community world map where you're going to be able to see
where every single person that's in this community is, where
let's say you guys go on a little vacation to Vegas for your buddy's
bachelor party, you're like, hey, while I'm in Vegas, I want to spend,
you know, an hour on Tuesday and try to link up with somebody else
that's in the space, go grab lunch, go grab coffee.
You can jump on the community world map, go in, find them as a member,
send them a message and link up.
Guys, the community, this is this is what I've realized.
I've bought twenty three thousand dollars plus in courses
just related to rank and rent.
I always watch the the the course, you know, once maybe a year.
But I'm in the community every single day.
I've literally made I have two partners right now
that I've made from my community.
I have I've made I've had deals come out of it.
I've had friendships come out of it.
I've had all kinds of stuff that have come out of it.
So the community, guys, is is where I think the value of these.
And ironically, school calls these communities, but it's a group.
That is where I think the value is.
OK, so obviously, you can have the community aspect.
You're going to have the classroom.
You're going to have the community world map.
And then every single week, you can notice on the calendar.
I am going to be going live every single week.
Porter, can you see this on my screen?
Yep, I guess every single Monday to start the week, seven a.m.
I put it as a Q&A, but sometimes it's going to be training,
sometimes going to be Q&A every single Monday.
Me, I'm going to be live.
I'm going to be talking to you guys.
Any questions that you have, we're going to be going on to a live.
And the other thing, too, is all those lives are going to be put into
the replay section in case you can't catch it.
OK, so guys, there's a ton of other stuff.
I don't want to bore you with all the details,
but this is the Rankin Red Academy.
I've been working on this for months.
We're like, where do we transition?
What do we do? What do we do?
And this is it, by the way, all of the material in here.
Let me give you a little sample.
Let's go to let's go to the map your goal section, for example.
All of these videos that are in here, OK,
every single one of these videos, this is not training
that I pulled from somewhere else.
These are all new videos.
OK, this is all new content that I have produced for this community.
So all of this is new stuff.
OK, so that said, guys, that is where this is going.
The art of digital real estate, RIP, it was real.
Now we are moving into the
Rankin Red Academy.
And if you guys want to check that out, I'm going to go ahead
and just drop a little linky poo, by the way, just so you guys know
our plan with this.
I didn't even mention this, by the way, this is paid, by the way.
Our goal is we're going to be charging 100 bucks a month.
This is a this is it's a community.
So you pay every month.
But the introductory rate, what we're doing for this launch
is we're doing at half price.
We're doing at $50 per month. OK.
Now, one of the thing you need to know, that's why you digital
landlord students, don't worry, you're going to get access
any money that you spend. OK.
Any money you spend on the Rankin Red Academy,
we're going to take 20 percent of that money
and we're going to credit that toward you,
towards your digital landlords membership
when you decide to jump into digital landlords. OK.
So if you're in for a year, we'll take 20 percent of that.
That will be a discounted rate off of your digital landlord membership.
So you're you being in this is you're in a way kind of paying towards that,
which you'll eventually join, we hope, at some point. OK.
So that's it, Isaac Cheatham.
What's the main difference between this?
Isaac Cheatham, you have access to this, so don't worry about it.
This is this is the this is the beginner.
This is the free group.
This is basically the free group.
We're going to have the community.
We're going to have the training.
But we're not touching on anything that's in digital landlords.
So the difference is everything.
So in case anyone's like, well, I'll just get into this.
No, this is very different than digital landlords.
But this is basically the free group on steroids.
We're going to give it attention.
We're going to be having, you know, Porter and Jason are going to be in there
giving the the free coaching calls.
If you guys want to jump on those,
we're going to be doing giveaways, new trainings all the time.
But Isaac, this is nothing, nothing the same as digital landlords.
OK, this is like this is where you start.
This is the free group. Move to this. OK.
But you get access anyway, so it doesn't matter.
So here we go.
Rankinretire.com.
Easy peasy. Porter, you want to try that link?
And then, guys, we're going to get into the actual training.
We're done.
Hold on one second.
Make sure that work that post.
Yep, got it. Beautiful.
Let's make sure it goes to the old community.
And there it goes.
OK, let me just see if I can pin this.
Chris Aren't said people appreciate what they pay for.
Yes, 100 percent.
By the way, Chris, Isaac, those of you that are in digital landlords,
do not be afraid, my friends.
You guys have access to this.
I'm going to be working with the team to figure out how we give you access
so you don't have to pay.
So none of you digital landlords go and try to pay, please.
For everybody else, if you want to be inside the community,
it is $50 per month right now.
Again, 20 percent of that is going to be credited
towards your digital landlords membership when you make the jump. OK.
All right. And by the way, funny enough, Isaac asked what the difference is.
I literally have a note right here.
This is not digital landlords, guys.
We're not teaching the same stuff at digital landlords.
Don't expect to go in and learn, you know, exactly what digital
landlords students are learning.
This is an intro to the rank and run.
This is a community, this access to myself, my team, et cetera.
But I will tell you guys, there is going to be a ton of value in that vault.
OK, a ton of value in that vault.
You guys are going to be able to pull from that.
Just that one mini course.
So just so you guys know, that's that.
Welcome to the rank and run academy.
And guys, one more thing I want to mention, anybody that jumps in today,
I went into my vault, which is like all my old videos
of all my, you know, my old sales calls that I flopped, my new sales,
you know, all that kind of stuff from way back in the day.
And I found this closed sales call back in 2018
that anybody that joins today, I'm going to I'm going to share this with you guys.
I'm going to let you guys have this.
It's like a 33 minute video of a closed sales call I did back in 2018.
That's going to be included for anybody that joins today as well.
OK, so anybody that stays at all is going to get the replay of this.
We're also going to be doing the giveaways.
We're going to be doing the training now.
And then anybody that joins, we're going to be giving away the
you're going to also get the sales, the sales recording that did back in 2018.
OK, rank and retired dot com.
Check it out. That is the rank and run academy.
And guys, with that said, let's get into the training.
Porter, what are you at right now per month?
I'm almost 11K, actually, right now.
Ten, one, ten, ten, one, ten, ten, ten, seven right now.
Amazing. OK, by the way,
we got to get you to 20 quick, just so you know.
Welcome, Dylan, first join.
So, Dylan, welcome to the community.
Welcome to Rankin Academy for being the first join.
I think, Ashley, we need to hook him up with something special.
So, Ashley, why don't you send him some swag?
Let's send him some swag out of the deal store
since he was the first one to make the leap.
Welcome, Dylan.
So let's get into the training, guys.
I want to I want to give you guys some real value as I go out here.
Last live, it's one twenty five in the morning.
It's been a long three days.
I've been working my tail off.
I'm in the middle of West Africa.
I should be going and enjoying nature and checking all this kind of stuff out.
I've just been working because I wanted to get this thing launched
as soon as possible.
So let's get into this this training and then we'll do the giveaways. OK.
So, guys, here's what I did this training.
We're going to be talking about how to go from zero to 20K per month
in 2025 with digital real estate.
And that's if I had to start over today.
So if you told me, hey, Nick, you know, you're at zero.
Like you're literally at no money.
I'm going to take everything away.
I'm going to take away all your clients.
You can't call your old clients.
What would you do?
And I sat there when I was preparing this, which I've spent a lot of time
just preparing this this part right here.
And I thought, what would I really do if I was sitting,
let's say, with Porter and he asked me this question?
What would actually what I do?
Not what what sounds good. What would I do?
So before I get into it, I've got like a few things.
I just want to I'm going to buzz through them.
And then any questions you guys have, we're going to we're going to go into that, too.
Porter, if you were to do that today, let's say you were going from zero to 10K.
Everything taken away.
You know, obviously, your skill set, your knowledge is there,
but all your clients are taken away.
What's the very first thing you would do? Just curious.
I would set my goals.
I would map out how many.
Well, I pick one niche, first of all, or two niches,
because I think simplicity is best.
I would I would set my goal and figure out
how many campaigns I needed to run every single month
and how many closing calls I would need to do every single month
to make sure it happens with a little bit of a buffer.
And then I would just simplify it.
I would just completely simplify the whole process.
Just pick one or two niches just to scale it and not try to overcomplicate it.
I love it, dude. I love it. Keep it simple.
Real quick, I got my comments over here on the phone.
Not to jump, but actually keep track of this.
Isaac Cheatham, he needs a coffee cup.
He needs a coffee cup.
He's one of the swag winners. Done.
Give him a coffee mug, man.
Give Isaac Cheatham a coffee mug.
Thanks for asking, brother.
And now everyone's going to ask for a coffee mug.
But Isaac, first winner of the swag.
OK, I like that, dude.
I like that. Sounds sounds simple.
And guys, I don't ever think you want to overcomplicate this.
So I'm going to go through what I would do,
and then I'm going to kind of set it back on Porter as well.
By the way, if you guys don't know, Porter isn't just on here because he's my brother.
He's on here because he's at 10.
You said 10, what, 10, 7?
Yeah, 10, 700 now.
Ten thousand seven hundred dollars a month.
He's also working on the farm.
When I talked to him today, we're doing WhatsApp.
He was actually doing farm stuff in the middle of making calls.
Like, even though he does that part time, he does it full time in the summer.
And then I feel like part time.
I feel like this year you've worked more than you did.
Even last year.
Oh, yeah, by far.
And I've done way better. It's crazy.
Yeah, I feel like you just do better when you're it's honest.
It's the truth.
So here's what I would do, guys.
Step number one, if I was starting from zero, zero to 20K.
Step number one is and this may sound like I'm going from the very beginning
or I'm going a bit back, but this is literally I would do this before anything.
Number one is I would figure out why I wanted the 20K. OK.
Why? Why? Like, why do I actually want to make 20K?
And I know it sounds silly, whatever.
But for me, when everything everything changed for me in 2020.
Because in 2019, I sat down with a pen and a paper and I asked myself,
what do you want? Number one, which I said, 100K a month.
And then I asked the most important question, which was why?
And I answered, why do I want that?
And then that answer, I asked why again, and I went like seven layers deep.
And guys, I can tell you when I figured out exactly why I wanted that money,
I realized that it wasn't even the reason that I originally thought.
But every time that, you know, things got tough or I got tired or whatever
it was, it was Wednesday.
I just it was easy to remember my wife.
And I was very clear about it.
So if I was starting today, before I did anything, before I chose my niche,
before I chose my city, before I map my goals, first thing I'm doing
is I'm sitting down going, why do I want 20K?
What what what do I need? 20K?
Why is it not 25? Why is it not 30?
Why is it not 15? What's the 20K for?
Why is it important to me?
And that's the first thing I do.
OK, step number two, guys.
Again, and this is coming from somebody who went from
barely making like barely scraping by eight to 10K a month back in 2019.
To in July of 2020, doing a hundred thousand dollars per month.
And some of these are the same steps.
And some of this I didn't do, which I wish I would have.
OK, step number two for me would be eliminate everything from my life
that doesn't get me closer to that goal.
And the goal being 20K.
I heard her Mosey her Mosey say this, I watched it.
I don't I haven't watched a ton of his stuff in the last year,
but I did watch something recently and he said he said this and it stuck with me.
And I've shared it in digital landlords as well.
It says, ask yourself the following question every single time this year.
Does this and guys, write this down.
This isn't from me.
This is from somebody that's way smarter, way richer, way more business savvy.
And I love this question.
Does this thing, person or belief
make it less or more likely that I hit my goal?
Anything you do, anything you do,
getting ready to go out with the boys and hit some drinks.
Does this thing, person, belief make it more or less likely that I hit my goals?
OK. Getting ready to go on a vacation midweek.
Same question. Getting ready, you know, whatever it is.
Ask yourself that lunch that you got invited to.
Is it getting your close?
Is it getting you closer to your goal?
Is the belief getting you closer to your goal?
Is the is the person that you're around getting you closer to your goal?
If not, cut it.
OK, if you assuming that you want to hit the goal,
that would be the plan here, right, is I want to hit the 20K.
OK, step number three for me, guys, is then I would sit down
and I would set the date and create an exact roadmap for how to get there.
Now, I will say this inside of the RankinRant Academy
in the map your goals section.
That's exactly what I walk through of how to set that exact date, target
and how to how to create that map of how to get there.
And I'm not just talking about like a loose map.
I'm talking, OK, I want to break it down by quarter, month, week, day, everything.
How many deals am I going to need to close?
How many people am I going to need to pitch to get that many pitches? Right.
Sorry, how many people am I going to need to pitch to close that many deals?
How many business owners am I going to need to put on trial to get that many pitches
all the way down to how many due diligence am I going to need to actually do? OK.
That would be steps.
I think that was step three, right? Step three.
Step four, by the way, for those of you that are trying to scribble,
just stay to the end. I'll extend you to replay.
OK, step number four is I would pick.
I know I've told you guys in the past, pick one.
I would pick three boring, tried and true niches
that I was going to focus on exclusively.
I would just out the gate, pick three.
You know, and if I was going to start today without saying anything else,
Porter, if you're going to start today, what are the three niches you'd pick?
I know one of them is fencing.
Fencing, concrete and masonry.
There you go.
So from somebody who is really trying to get it this year,
who's really trying to get to your goals, 25K by the end of the year.
Yeah, and I've gotten two niches and most of them are concrete.
Most are concrete.
He's getting you're in concrete and fencing.
Yeah, homies at ten thousand seven hundred dollars a month.
He's in two niches.
One of them, you guys think, is oversaturated.
It is it is harder than it was.
Fencing is a great one.
Masonry is a great one.
OK, there's a lot of good niches go into three.
So I would go and pick three boring, tried and true niches
that I was going to focus on exclusively. OK.
Step five is I would go and I would set.
Well, you know, this is a step that you don't have to do.
But the next step is the due diligence process, where what I would do
is I would go in and crank out as many due diligence as I could possibly find
as I could possibly do.
I will tell you guys this just to give a little plug
for the rank and rent engine tool is knowing what I know now.
I would immediately go and fricking set up an account with rank
and rent engine just for the due diligence,
because you're going to be able to do due diligence in seven minutes
instead of 30. And you can do due diligence.
You can do four in a time.
You could do one and you can crank out way more due diligence.
So for me, knowing what I know now, I'd go set up an account.
I'd get the discount code.
It's like 69. What is it?
69 bucks for the starter pack for the first two, three months.
If you get the discount code and you can crank out due diligence like that.
And what I would do, guys, is I would go
and I would find my first five niche and city combinations.
OK, I'd find my first five.
Now, I know I'm deviating a little bit from what I've maybe said in the past.
And by the way, those of you that are that are in digital landlords.
I am in the middle of finishing the training 3.0.
This is the third time I'm going to be creating the new version of digital landlords.
But I'm in the middle of that.
So there's going to be some minor changes.
But I would go and I would find my first five niche and city combinations.
One of the reasons you can do that is because you have tools
like rank and rent engine where you can just bust out due diligence.
OK, now this is one thing I want to I did not do this.
And I really strongly encourage you guys to do this.
Is if I was starting again today, from this point on, I would record everything.
OK, loom Vimeo recording tool.
And I think it's on Google Chrome Store.
Porter, what do you use to record stuff?
A snapshot snapshot.
So it doesn't matter whatever you want to use, record everything.
Why? Because I'm going to hand this off to my VA as soon as possible.
And I can tell you guys in advance, due diligence is one of those things
you are going to want to hand off as soon as possible.
Once you master it, once you get good at it, you're going to want to get somebody else
to be putting in those hours.
OK, so, guys, yes, go find those five niches.
You can do it by hand. By the way, you don't have to use a tool.
Use frickin paper. I don't care.
But record exactly how you're doing the due diligence so that you have a PDF.
I'd have a PDF and I have videos on each one of those steps.
Because then I can hand it off to a VA.
OK, guys, I'm trying to get to 20K.
I'm not trying to get a deal.
I'm not trying to get one deal. I'm trying to get to 20K.
And I think you guys should.
And the reason I chose 20K for this presentation is because at 20K,
most everyone's out of the rat race, right?
I see people on here. I recognize they have all kinds of jobs
for everything from, you know, whatever.
Some people are business owners.
Some people work. They're teachers.
Some people are doctors, whatever it is, guys.
But. At the end of the day,
just just trust me on this one, guys, just record everything.
OK, just record everything.
And at 20K, you can almost anyone can get out of the rat race.
OK, that's that's really what I'm trying to say.
OK, so once I did that, guys, I found my first five
niche city combinations and I recorded everything.
Then what I would do is I would go and set up not one, not two.
I'd go set up three Google ad campaigns.
For three of those five cities, I've chosen five
niche and city combinations.
I'd pick three of them and I'd go set up three campaigns.
And then I would out of those three, I would choose the best two
and I would turn to one.
OK, I turn to one.
And then what I would do is as soon as one started to hit,
I would pause the other.
So now I got one going.
I got two ready to rip ones, pause ones hasn't been started yet.
And I got my first three pop, pop, pop.
OK, done. Just like that.
OK, now, again, guys, which this is one of those things
where I'm telling you what I would do now.
The reason I do it like this is because I know that once I get that first deal,
what everyone does is, Porter, this happened to you.
You got your first deal and then you're like, oh, back to the drawing board.
Now I got to go do due diligence.
And it kind of like slowed you down.
Yeah, I didn't have a plan.
I landed a deal and then I had to go back.
And it took me weeks and weeks and weeks.
And this was I should have been more prepared. Amazing.
So guys, again, record this record how you're setting up ads.
OK, you might not want to hand off ads right at the back.
Like, I don't want to trust a VA.
Just record it because you're going to at some point not going to say
because I don't I haven't set up ads personally in years.
And I'm the one that pays for them.
OK, I have somebody I trust.
Francesca sets them up.
And guess what? I don't even think she sets them up anymore.
I think she oversees somebody else to set them up.
So you're going to have to let the stuff out of control, guys.
I didn't record this stuff for years.
I was doing I was the only one then finally like, oh,
there's this book called The E Myth.
It says I should should create a system.
And then I started I'm just a knucklehead.
I'm trying to give you guys the shortcut here.
OK, so, guys, once I did that, I got the campaign running campaigns running.
I I would then go and build out my list for that city.
OK, now, if you've never done this before,
I would probably recommend that you build the list first
before you even decide to set up the ad.
So, you know, there's business owners.
But for me, because I've done this so many times,
I know what I'm looking for.
I can I can eyeball it and know, you know, hey, this
this has got enough business owners.
And for me, to be honest with you, if I see that there's three business
owners that are paying for ads for me, that's enough.
OK, because I'm really, really confident I'm going to close the deal.
And I know how to show them all the other work I've done, et cetera.
Now, in this scenario, I wouldn't be able to show them that.
But again, guys, I would then go build my list.
If you've never done this before, I'd probably do the list before. OK.
So, guys, now this is where I'm going to change a little bit
from what I've said in the past.
After I built the list, we got the campaign running.
We got to pause campaigns.
We got one one running.
And then the next that we're building, we build the list. Right.
So then, guys, this is where I deviate just a little bit.
What I would do while we're waiting for the ads for the ads to work,
the leads to come in, is I would go and of those two remaining campaigns. OK.
Whatever one is the lowest hanging fruit
with the lowest hanging fruit, like with the city niche combination,
I would actually recommend if I was getting to going to going to go to 20K,
I would actually recommend going and just building your first website.
So while you're waiting, you got, again, just to recap,
you got one that's running ads.
You're waiting for leads to come in.
Of course, leads come in. Focus on that.
You got that. You got to pause ready to rip as soon as you're good.
Then these remaining two, I'd choose one of the two.
I'd actually go build a website.
I've never said that in the past, but I'm starting to realize
that I think a good agency, you've got your you've got your ads.
Those are your quick deals that you're going to go snipe.
And then whenever you come across those city and niche combinations
that are very low hanging fruit, go and build the website.
Because guess what?
Once you close that first deal, you can always run ads to that website.
Now, you got to be careful.
You want to make sure that you're you know what the due diligence looks like.
I would make sure that the one that you build is the one
that's the lowest hanging fruit, because once you build it,
you're kind of stuck with it.
But if you're confident in it, go and build this. Why?
Because now I've got ads running.
I've got to pause.
And I've also got one that's now starting to rank.
And I can be doing work on this while I'm waiting for the leads coming.
I know a lot of people.
They get in.
They set up a campaign and they're like, what do I do now?
What do I do now?
And it's like, well, you go do more due diligence.
Well, I already told you to do five.
Right. So this is a good use of time.
And now, guys, you're going to go build out the website.
And guess what? While you're building out the site,
you know what you're going to do?
You're going to go and you're going to freaking record it.
Right. So you can hand it off to a VA.
Follow me so far.
I got four more things and I'm done. OK, guys, after that,
what I would do is once, of course, I'm sitting here.
The main target is to wait for the leads to come in.
Once the leads start to come in for that first city,
I'd go and I'd close a deal using my process.
If you guys don't know my process by now,
it's because you're brand new to the group.
Go into the Rankin Red Academy.
We outline the entire process in the Money, Love, Speed module.
I would use the my process to close my first deal,
even if it took me three tries.
OK, meaning even if I got leads coming in, I hooked a business owner.
I sent three to five leads.
I got them on the phone. I flubbed the deal. I lost it.
I had to do it again and again, even if it took me three,
even if it took me four or five tries.
We have a guy today inside of our community,
inside of Digital Landlords.
And that kind of a similar thing happened to him.
I think he went through a couple of business owners,
but he had spent a couple of hundred bucks on ads.
But he kept going. He kept going. He got the deal.
Guys, you don't lose money
until you quit running the ads, until you just decide to give up.
OK, so I would again.
That's the main thing.
What's different about what I'm giving you with this approach, guys,
is I already know what's going to happen is if you get that first deal,
you're focusing on one campaign.
Then as soon as you get that deal, you're going to go back to the due diligence.
And it's just like it's it's just this thing.
We're trying to get to 20K as soon as possible.
OK, so I would go, I would close that deal.
I would record every step of the process.
Guys, I'm building out a library for my company handbook.
OK, and then, guys, as soon as I land that first deal,
I just recoup my costs and I would immediately go to onlinejobs.ph.
Shout out plug for John Jonas and his his amazing product.
I would go to onlinejobs.ph
and I'm spending the first money that comes in to get a VA.
No questions asked.
All that stuff, due diligence,
fricking building websites, all that crap that I don't want to do.
I'm I've now got a library of stuff that I've trained them.
That I've I've got these videos on.
I'm just handing this stuff off, man.
I'm not dealing with it. I don't want to deal with it.
I'm trying to get to 20K.
I'm not. Again, the difference between what I'm talking about now,
some of you guys have heard me talk about getting that first deal going,
having a goal of getting to 20K is you're going to structure it differently
than if you have a goal of one K of one deal. Right.
And a lot of people don't think about this,
but this is how I'd get to 20K as soon as possible. OK.
So I'm going to get that VA that first one.
No questions asked.
Don't take the money and start, you know, go go buy clothes.
Put it into a VA recoup your costs on the ads, put it into a VA
and let them go buy back your time.
OK, now what I do is I turn my VA loose on my library
and then I train that person and have them start cranking due diligence
and to also to go build that first website that I that I sold. Right.
So they're going to just be churning out due diligence.
Everything, not everything.
This is when everything changed. But guys,
do before ranking an engine,
how long did it take you to do a due diligence?
It took me like 30 to 45 minutes because I had to go back and forth
and back and forth. It took forever.
I can open up like 15, like 10 to 15 minutes.
Like and I've done it like a couple of times.
Like I could do a lot faster if I did it more. Yeah.
For me, 30 minutes is about what it was.
So imagine I've done over personally over a thousand.
Well, I don't know how much how much time have I spent. Right.
Imagine you can go and get a VA using your rank and rent
engine account and they can bust one out.
Let's say they're not as fast as you.
Let's say there are 12 minutes of rip. Right.
They're they could do almost three.
Let's see. 12. So what they're doing five.
They could do five an hour.
You say four hours a day.
So five times four, you can do 20 a day.
You could do. I mean, dude, you can crank out some due diligence.
You can have them attack some cities. Right.
And so now all of a sudden they're doing due diligence.
They've got a list of these cities.
You're going in, you're making sure that they're good.
And guys, as you close the deal, guess what?
You're turning on the other campaign. Right.
And then that other website, you're setting up the ads.
And now you've got a whole list to do.
And it's just this rinse and repeat cycle.
And the issue is, is everyone's thinking about that.
And guys, the first deal is super important.
That's the best deal ever.
It's it feels it's the most amazing deal ever. Right.
But if we're trying to get to 20K, we've got to we've got to be
going to plan it on 20K.
And that's why I started off by saying set the target,
create the road map and then attack. OK.
And guys, that is exactly the process
that I'm going to be doing until I hit 10K.
I'm going to rinse and repeat, rinse and repeat, rinse and repeat.
And then when I hit 10K, then I think around 10K
I'm as when I would probably go get my second VA.
You could probably justify it earlier,
but you could get to 10K with a VA and yourself
and a simple tool like Rank and Rent Engine.
That's all you need. OK.
You get to 10K.
And then, guys, what my last step would be, as soon as I hit 10K,
I'd get a second VA.
I would have every single thing that's not making me more money.
I would have my VA's doing.
I'd be managing two VA's.
I'd be spending my time hooking business owners,
sending over leads and closing deals. That's it.
I've had them building websites, writing content, doing due diligence,
setting up ads, every single thing except for doing the sales.
And I would rinse and repeat until I hit 20K.
OK. Now, for those of you like, oh, man,
I wish I would take more notes again.
Guys, if you're in 13 minutes, I'm going to be giving away.
Everyone's going to get the replay of this.
You guys go listen to this again.
This is how I would freaking attack it.
By the way, for those of you that did that just hopped on
and have no idea what we're talking about,
just a spoiler alert.
The free group's gone.
All the content's gone.
Rankandretire.com. Go check it out.
You can rewatch this if you want.
But for those, I know we've got a bunch more people that jumped on.
Rankandretire.com. It's pinned at the top.
Go check it out.
That is our community.
That is the Rank and Rent Academy. OK.
So a couple of notes real quick, notes to some giveaways.
Guys, you plus one to two VA's,
you can muscle your way to 20K.
That's insane, right?
Porter, how much you pay your VA?
Well, a hundred dollars a week.
So four hundred bucks a month.
I think I have one VA that pay five hundred bucks a month.
I think I have my guy here in Africa.
It's been with me for like five years.
I pay him three hundred bucks a month.
I mean, imagine, right?
You plus two people, that's less than a thousand dollars in payroll.
You could scale to 20K a month.
That's freaking insane.
What other business, right?
OK, when I scale, let me tell you guys this, guys,
when I scaled to 100K per month, this is what my team looked like.
It was me.
Francesca was overseeing the sites and the clients.
There was one guy helping me hook business owners.
There was one guy answering and transferring leads.
And then I had one and a half because one of them was part time,
one and a half paid by the thousand words content writer.
And I had two VA's. OK, so what is that?
Like five people.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Six full time, three of which were VA's or overseas.
One was part time and we it was a million dollar company.
That's insane. Like my payroll was nothing
and it was a million dollar company.
OK, seven figure agency.
Now, last thing I want to cover,
what what kind of time frame would I be looking at for this 20K?
I if I were actually doing this for real,
I would set a die goal of six months, like I'll hit six months no matter what.
But I would set a stretch goal of three months.
I think you could set a goal if you really, really eliminated all the
distractions, you put your head down and went to work.
And this is all you focused on.
I think you could do it in three months.
OK, I think you could.
You'd really have to push.
But I think if you wanted to, you could do it in three months.
Now, somebody is going to quote me and say,
oh, you said I could get to 20K in three months.
No, I said that if you put your head down and you freaking nailed it,
you could. But no, most people aren't going to do that.
OK, that is, guys, the my.
That's what I would do.
You guys ever heard you,
Porto, have you heard that show called Undercover Boss, Grant Cardone?
Yeah. He got dropped in frickin what?
Somewhere in Colorado. You should know.
Frickin was a boulder.
I think it was Boulder with like a hundred bucks.
And he's supposed to create like whatever business.
That would be my if you said today you got no money.
You got to get a twenty thousand dollar business in three months.
That's it right there.
That's what I'm doing every second of every day.
I'm waking up and I'm cranking it out, baby.
I'm putting in my headphones, listen to a little
focus music on Spotify and just, you know,
maybe throwing in a couple of press ups every couple of hours.
That's it, dude. Just cranking away on the computer.
You can build guys.
I wish I could hold up my laptop with a laptop,
internet connection and some knowledge you guys can build.
You guys can escape the frickin rat race. Right.
Those of you that are on this call right now that had to go to work today
that hated every second of it.
And you're like, I can't wait for that live to see if there's a way
I can do it. You can.
You can. You just got to put in the work. Right.
And we have literally the model and the and I just gave you guys
literally a an exact game plan for how to do it.
Now you just got to execute. OK.
So, guys, once again, for those of you that didn't catch it,
rank and retire dot com, if you guys love the free group
and you want to continue it, that is what that's transition to.
It is paid. It's and you know what?
Again, I don't care if we go from six thousand.
I don't care. By the end of the week, we go from six thousand
two hundred people in the free group.
And I only have fifteen people inside of that community
because those fifteen people are the ones I want to work with.
Those are the people I'm going to give my time to my attention to.
Those are the ones that want to work because they're putting their money
where their mouth is.
And I promise you, they're going to consume that content
way more than the people that are the lucky lose and the frickin parasites
that have been, you know, infesting this group.
And I'm not saying you guys, because if you're on this call,
then I don't necessarily think that's you. OK.
Hordy, ready to do some giveaways?
I'm ready. Let's do it.
Guys, who wants some free stuff?
Who wants some frickin free stuff?
Let's let's see.
Let's go ahead. I want to ask some questions.
I like to give away free stuff by asking questions.
By the way, Moza, what's up?
This is my buddy from South Africa.
He's he's at three a.m.
So he's even beat me.
What's up, dude? Been a minute.
OK, let's give away some stuff.
Let's start off by giving.
What should we give away first, Porter?
I want to give away some good stuff.
Let's let's start off by giving away the swag.
Then we're going to give away the
the two, the two, three month membership to rank in an engine.
And then I'm going to tell you guys what we're going to do
for the partial scholarship. How does that sound?
Oh, we also got to give away the copies of the exclusive trade.
OK, let me ask you this.
Who wants who's interested in the
I've got this 12 part exclusive training series.
We covered all kinds of different topics inside.
This is these are completely separate.
You guys never saw these unless you were on those trainings.
And I don't think anyone was on every single week.
It's a 12 part series.
It's about 12 hours, maybe closer to 13 hours on all kinds of different topics.
I'm going to give away five copies of that.
Let's get that away first.
Who's if you're interested in that,
drop the word training.
OK, if you're interested in swag, drop the word swag.
And don't you dare put swag in training.
OK, training or swag?
Which one? Which ones? What are you guys interested in?
OK, let's see.
Let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see.
OK.
Jahill says any hoodies available, the hoodies.
It's not because I don't want to give away.
It's because the hoodies are for it's the 10K club.
So if you see somebody rocking a hoodie, they're in the 10K.
So other than that, I would have I would have said yes.
OK, so let's go.
Carl. So, Ashley, I need you to be taking notes here.
Carl Giambri says he wants free stuff.
So let's do for him, let's give him a mouse pad.
OK, let's also do.
Jen's Linton.
Let's do a mouse pad.
By the way, if you guys don't want the mouse pad, you want the coffee mug.
I'm actually just going to say swag.
Ashley, you can give away a mouse pad,
a coffee mug, air pod case.
You can let them choose.
We have the stickers, whatever.
So we've got Jen's.
I just want you to write down the names.
Swag, Jen's Linton.
Carl Giambri, let me just hold my phone.
I'm just making a fool of myself.
Well, people, people want the training.
Mr. Chris Aren't, Chris Aren't gave him the swag.
Gina Benson swag.
And who else?
Carlos Braga swag.
Janet Bruno wants swag.
She wants the coffee mug. Give it to her.
Carl, you can get the coffee mug.
Just message Ashley.
She's getting you.
Guys, by the way, if you're a winner, reach out to Ashley.
She's going to get you sorted out.
OK. I don't see anyone else for swag.
Let's give away some training.
Porter, give me some names.
We've got five copies of the training.
Actually, I only gave away like five, six swag.
So I'm down to give away 10 of the training.
Boom, OK. So let's do it.
You give me a name, I'll give a name.
We'll go like that.
OK, Nate, farewell.
Nate, farewell for the training, Ashley.
Let's go Jeff Collier with the training.
Todd Johnson.
OK, Todd Johnson is training.
Gary Treister, I'm going to break my rules.
I'm going to give Gary Treister training
and I'm going to give him a coffee mug because Gary Treister, guys,
is actually funny enough, was one of my first clients
and he still works with me to this day.
And I freaking appreciate you, brother.
Good to have you on this call.
So Gary, message Ashley.
She's going to give you the coffee mug and the training.
And yes, if you're my client on this call, you're going to get both.
Let's give out who else?
You say Ali Borden already?
No, I didn't say that one. Ali Borden training.
Nick Kudlick, you're already in digital.
Just hit me up, bro.
Anyone in digital landlords, by the way, you just get it.
Anything we do in this stuff or the Rankin Academy, you just get already.
So don't worry about that.
So, Nick, I'll give you swag.
Nick, Nick, message Ashley for swag.
Kenneth Liu training.
Who else you got for training, Porter?
Let's do Kylie Sherman.
OK. Kylie Sherman training.
Todd Johnson says, I'll buy all your swag after training.
OK, Todd, take some swag or take the training.
Kevin Moss, your individual landlords, you already get the training message.
Ashley, I think we've got like two more.
Gina says she's working her ass off towards the hoodie.
By the way, that hoodie slaps.
It's not even the feel.
It's just knowing you got the hoodie.
Two more training Porter.
Moza, Moza, my man in South Africa, I'm going to choose him.
And then Porter, do one more.
Let's do Edda Chapman.
Is she an individual?
She's an individual. She might be an individual landlord.
If she is, I think she is.
She's an unemployable.
She's not. And OK, give her the training.
OK, cool.
Well, then, if I said she should be an individual, I was gosh dang it.
Edda, come on. Just kidding.
You should be.
It should be.
I think I think we did.
OK.
That's that. So, guys, we did that.
Now, what I want to know is we're going to give away
two. This is just two, three, three free months of RankinRan engine,
which I referred to earlier in the call.
OK, two copies or two memberships.
It's three months free.
And it's for two people only.
I have to be really stiff on this because Ryan, the one that created
the training, said it's good for just two people.
So let's see.
Again, guys, if you won, if I called your name, message Ashley,
she'll get you taken care of. We got this.
Then we're going to give away.
We're going to tell you guys about the partial scholarship.
We're going to wrap it up and we'll we'll go get back to work.
OK, yeah, guys, don't leave it on Ashley.
She's writing it down.
But if you want something, you got a message, Ashley, please.
So that she can get it to you guys and she's going to have a bunch of work.
So be patient with her. I'm giving her a ton of work.
Thanks, Ashley.
I'm going to leave it on Ashley.
She's writing it down.
But if you want something, you got a message, Ashley, please.
Thanks, Ashley.
Kevin Mead just says he never got his last swag.
That should be a confusion because that's that's that's
that's literally a drop shit like he just goes to you.
So just message Ashley, bro.
No worries. And we can tell, by the way, Kevin Mead, if you did get it before.
So we know if you're lying, bro.
And I will I will know we can, though, for real. OK.
OK. Let's see.
Let's see. Whoa, lots of comments.
Let's do.
Shane Noble, I think, is one of the
as a rank and rent engine, three month, three month free.
Moza said training one more time.
Moza, you already won the training.
Just message Ashley. I got it for you, bro.
Yeah, message Ashley just on Facebook.
And. Let's also do.
Who's this?
Christian Story, second winner on rank and rent engine.
You still with me, Porter?
Yeah. Crazy, it's two a.m., dude, and we're freaking cooking.
There's no way I'm going to be able to sleep tonight.
I love it.
Yeah, dude, you boy got dressed up today.
All right, guys, let's talk about the partial scholarship.
Just real quick.
We're going to talk about the partial scholarship.
All right, guys, let's talk about the partial scholarship
just real quick, just so that when the winner is chosen,
no one's like, oh, it's not this isn't an entire scholarship.
It's a partial scholarship.
So you are going to get a partial scholarship.
That's what it means. OK, here's what we're going to do,
because we don't know necessarily who's applied in the past, whatever.
So this is what we found to be the easiest thing as we discussed it.
If you are interested in the partial scholarship,
need you to do two things. OK,
I need you to send the following to Francesca on a message.
If you send it to me, we're not going to see it.
Send it to Francesca Ravinelli, our Italian stallion from Frickin.
I think she's from Trento, Italy.
She is amazing. She does all of the stuff for my agency.
She's responsible for a lot of our success, if not all of it.
I need you to message her if you are interested in the partial scholarship.
And I need you to say two things.
Number one is what you do for work right now.
It's a business. If it's a job, what the job is, whatever.
Just tell her what you do for work.
And number two, why you think you deserve the partial scholarship.
OK, that's it.
And I will tell you that I will let her decide.
I'm going to let her read all of them.
She's going to be able to.
I'm going to give her the the complete autonomy to decide based on the answers.
Who is the winner of the partial scholarship?
She will reach out to you. We'll announce it to just so everyone knows
that we actually did choose a winner.
She'll reach out to you, let you know you on the partial scholarship.
For me, just to choose someone randomly.
And then if, you know, they've already applied or whatever,
it just didn't make sense. It's kind of a waste of time.
So if you guys are interested in the partial scholarship,
digital landlords, partial scholarship and go message Francesca
and tell her what you do for work and why you think you're deserving of it. OK.
So, guys, with that said one more time, for those of you that are new,
just getting on the call, let me get some water here.
The free group, the art of pre-selling,
as it was formerly known right now, called the Art of Digital Real Estate
is no more. All of the training, all of me going live
150 plus times are done. They're gone.
It's done. It's over. It was fun.
We had a great ride.
No one appreciates what they don't pay for.
If you are interested in still being part of the community
and what it has evolved to in version 2.0, if you are not in digital lands,
if you're in digital landlords, you're not going to pay for it.
We're going to try to sort out how we get you guys all in there.
So don't worry. You're going to have access to everything.
If you're not in digital landlords, go to rankandretire.com.
You can also go to school.com SKOL and search for Rank and Rent Academy.
Either way, go check it out.
I've got a about little blurb on about.
There's a video, a nine minute video that explains a little bit more into.
Excuse me, bud, a little more into what we cover in there.
But guys, people that pay for stuff, they value it more.
And I'm telling you right now, I do not care about the numbers.
I don't care if there's three, two, one person, ten people, fifteen.
I don't care if we go from six thousand two hundred down to ten.
Does not matter because I know those ten people. I'm stoked.
I'm going to mess it.
We're going to you're going to get a very personal feel for me.
And for those of you that are wondering,
what's the difference between digital landlords and
Rank and Rent Academy, the new community, everything.
OK, just like the free group and the digital landlords, everything.
However, I will tell you, there's all new training inside of the Rank and Rent Academy.
We've got a bunch of stuff that we didn't have before.
And we are going to be loading every single live that I ever did.
Ever in the free group, 150 plus lives,
150 plus hours, way more than that, actually,
into the vault and also into the the interview series.
OK, community world map, all that good stuff.
I'm going to be going live once a week, which we used to do.
Now I feel excited to go live because if you're paying to be there,
you better be on the freaking live.
So, guys, go hop in there.
Rank and Rent Academy, Rank and Retire dot com.
Check it out. Now, what I want to do, Porter, you got ten minutes.
Yeah, we're good. Since this is our last call,
I want to just I want to see if anyone has any final questions.
Ten minutes. I'm going to give ten minutes any questions.
Maybe we'll give away a little more swag.
I don't know. But if anybody has questions, I want to just answer them.
I really, really, really.
I hope you guys know I really poured my heart and soul into this community.
I have spent so many freaking hours just just commenting,
just answering questions, just reading posts.
I don't know if you guys know of any other free communities out there
that had paid admins.
OK, fix it.
Felix was not a free, but it was somebody I paid somebody
on my personal team that I paid every week to go and service the free group.
We put a lot in that, man.
I put so many hours in that and it was a back and forth, back and forth.
Should we get rid of it? Should we not?
Guys, I wish we didn't have to get rid of it.
It was it was amazing.
It was such a good thing.
But all good things come to an end, just like when you give a business
owner free leads and they stop.
They think they can do it on their own or they stop appreciating it.
It kind of loses its sizzle.
It lost its sizzle, man.
It was it was a great run.
But let's go build an amazing community.
Let's go build the rank and run academy.
For those of you that are actually serious about learning this model
that want to go to the next level, I'll see you in there.
OK, let's see if there's any questions really quick.
Eight minutes. We're done. OK.
All right.
Pat says, if you're sending ads.
To a B.O.
And you fail to land the deal, what do you do with the ad campaign?
What do you do, Porter?
If I failed, read it one more time.
You're running you're sending ads to a B.O.
And you failed to land the deal.
What do you do with the ad campaign?
I find I find another business owner from getting leads
and I didn't sell the first business owner.
I'll go and try to find another business owner.
And most likely, it was something that I did.
It's not the area.
So don't give up on the area.
If you're getting leads, keep trying.
There's always an option to find a business owner.
Yep. Same same exact answer.
I knew I figured you'd answer like that.
So I said that, by the way, Chandler Christensen, how do we get the replay?
I would love to just post a link right now because
it would be the easiest thing, but we're still recording the replay, unfortunately.
So what you're going to have to do is anybody that wants it.
You're going to message Ashley.
Actually, I am so sorry.
She's going to get a million messages.
She's going to kill me.
Message Ashley as soon as this calls over and ask for the replay.
Give her a little bit of time.
Just say the word replay for the love.
Just say the word replay so she can just send you the link and move on to the next one.
But you can get it there if you're on this call right now. OK.
Carl says you talked about running ads and then building out a site.
We're starting with a small site, then transitioning to move to a permanent site after you.
Yeah. So that's what you do is you start out with a you start out with a landing page.
You run the ads through landing page, you get the deal, then you build up the site.
What I was telling you, if I was going to go to 20K, I would that would be my primary focus.
But I'd also try to go for my my most low hanging fruit project or due diligence.
And I would build that one out so I can get I could have one project
ranking while I'm running ads and landing deals.
OK, because I want to have both.
Right. I've started to realize, like, as an agency, you want to have all kinds of different stuff moving.
OK. Matthew says, no questions, been binging your podcast and learned a ton,
thinking about applying, but not sure on cost.
We'll think it over. No problem.
Matthew, send me a message.
Actually, you know what, Matthew, by the way, anybody on this call,
that is has a question or that needs any further help.
Porter, are you down to do a couple of calls?
Yeah, I'm going to drop my phone number in the chat.
Drop. Porter's going to drop his phone number.
Matthew, you specifically message Porter, jump on a call with him and ask any questions
that you have and he'll answer for you. OK, so don't just do that.
And that's actually Porter's cell phone.
So if you guys want to go drop it in, like, you know, those things in the mall, like you
you win a free motorcycle, go drop his number in those and then he'll get spammed for life.
So, yeah, Matthew, do that.
Edgar says you've done a great job with all the teaching.
Bless you, Edgar. Bless you.
Stephanie says, I just joined the free community.
Am I the reason it's ending?
L.O.L. Stephanie, no, please don't feel like that.
It's literally just a timing thing.
But I promise you that you will get way more out of this, even if it's 50 bucks,
because you're spending it, you are going to get more out of it.
I know it sounds like, oh, Nick's just making an excuse to make more money.
Guys, I've had people come to me that want to, you know, these are people that are really close to me.
Let's say family, friends, friends that are really close to me.
Want to, you know, these are people that are really close to me.
Let's say family, friends.
And I promise you and they're like, hey, I want to learn this business model, right?
I want to get into this.
I want to learn. I want to do what you do.
And I promise you on my kid's life, it's not about the money.
And every part of me wants to just be like, you know, just here's the password, homey hook up.
Like that whole thing.
But I'm telling you right now that it doesn't work because they never open it.
They never, they never, ever open it.
They never take it.
But when you have skin in the game, even if it's a little bit of skin, you're like,
I'm going to get into this community.
I'm going to go freaking do the like you're going to go through the modules.
By the way, in the first mini course, it has some homework.
Do all the freaking homework.
Has you go drop while you're in the group, blah, blah, blah.
Go do all that.
But you're going to go watch all the mini courses.
You're going to go do all that stuff because you've you've paid to be there.
Right. Even if it's a little over a dollar a day, you're going to go freaking squeeze
that thing for what it's worth because you spent money on it.
OK. So, yeah, it's not because of you, Stephanie.
Jahill says you should call this live, the giant pullback.
That's a cool name, but it's not a pullback because we're actually ending the group.
No question. Just thank you, Ali.
Thank you for that comment.
Let's see.
OK, Kenneth says, thanks so much, Nick and team question.
How would you respond to a business owner saying, why don't you do ads
slash SEO on my website instead of building your own separate site that I don't own?
How would you convince them about the business model?
Kenneth, what I would say is I can.
I can do I do both.
But the reason I'm doing this is because it's going to be a lot more
affordable for you.
And the only reason you want me to do any work on your website
is because you want leads.
So if you want, I can go and do a bunch of stuff and send you a report,
whatever on your website is going to cost you a lot more.
And it's going to be a 12 month contract.
Or I can build my own website, get you what comes from the website,
which is leads, and you pay a lot less.
You're renting it for me.
So but yeah, and if you want to, I'll give you a price on it.
And I'll quote them super high.
And if they say yes to that, I'll just do that.
And then I'll still sell them a lead gen it later.
Never say no, there's always an option.
100 percent.
Porter's number four, three, five, three, nine, three, five, six, nine, four.
Everyone drop it into a spam filter, please.
Just not the insurance one to the marketplace.
We can smoke you.
Steve Wall, have you been seeing exact match domains
getting smacked this most recent Google update now?
Not really, but I'm not super spammy like that.
And I'm not saying that spammy, but if I did get an exact match domain,
I didn't do anything else that was spammy.
Kevin says, if we're in DLL course, Kevin, what it means is you're going to have access.
But listen, if you're in DLL, that's the advanced stuff.
That's where you want to be anyway.
So you think you're going to have access to this, but it's not.
It's not it.
You're going to want to stay in digital landlords where the values are.
So you're not you're going to again, free access for life.
You get all the value if you want to go check it out.
But yeah, you're not you're not going to probably even spend that much time.
You can. OK, so you get it for free. Don't worry.
Brandon says he also just joined yesterday.
Awful timing.
And Annie says, I've loved your podcast, said I don't have them anymore.
Oh, they're coming.
By the way, I recorded one on Saturday night here in Africa.
It was a 22 minute podcast and 18 minutes in the power went out, lost it.
OK, unfortunately, I haven't had a time this week at all
as I've been preparing for this live to record it.
But you're going to see them again.
So keep an eye on it. And he appreciate that.
Steve says he appreciates all the freebies.
Yeah, Isaac did say Isaac says Nick's been doing a pullback
warning about this for a year. Finally, I'm doing it.
Everyone thought I was lying.
Guys, I appreciate you being on.
Ma says bike away.
You're welcome, brother.
Steve says, so we wouldn't be buying a bike.
We wouldn't be buying a bike.
We wouldn't be buying a bike. We wouldn't be buying a bike.
He says, so we wouldn't be buying both digital
landlords and the school group, or do you recommend them both?
Well, I know that question, guys.
This school is just the community is just like the free group, right?
It's not going to have every single thing that digital landowners are going to have.
It's not going to cover in depth.
It's a introduction to rank and rent.
It's a community. It's me going live.
It's it's it's got many courses.
It's got a vault with all the old stuff.
It is for all intents and purposes, the Facebook group
converted into a community.
But now, because I'm working with committed people,
I'm I'm ready to go at it again. I'm ready to come go live.
I'm ready to to give a ton of time, effort, energy,
throw a bunch of resources at it.
OK, digital landlords is like that's where you're going to end up.
When you're ready from school, you'll end up in digital landlords.
So if you're thinking about what should I do?
You definitely are going to want to do digital landlords.
The reason why we did school is because if you're brand new
and you want to check it out, you want to build the community, blah, blah, blah.
That's where that's at. OK.
But again, for those of you that didn't catch this,
if you're in rank and rent academy,
let's say for six months, 20 percent of the money that you spend
when you decide to join digital landlords is going to be credited
towards your membership
and you're going to get that discount off of digital landlords. OK.
Order anything else?
No, I would say, guys, if you join school,
you're going to get a message from me.
Reply back if you guys need help.
Feel free to message me.
I'd love to get on one on one calls with you.
And don't be thinking this is a sales call.
It's strictly to help you.
I already know eventually you're going to join digital landlords anyway.
So I'm not going to try to push that on you.
But I will give you the information that you need.
But again, reply back.
We're just trying to help you guys.
So yeah, orders in there. Jason's in there.
Guys, you have these people that are doing 10K a month.
They'll jump. They're giving you their cell phone number.
Hop on a call.
And this is going to be in the school community exclusively.
Hop on a call and ask them questions.
If you have a niche idea, if you have, you know,
I know Matthew had some questions about joining digital landlords,
stuff like that, any of that kind of stuff, jump on, ask them, feel free.
They're getting paid to do it.
And they're happy to do it, adding value.
So, guys, it's been freaking fun.
It's two seventeen in the morning in West Africa.
It's been a long week. I'm stoked.
I'm going to wake up tomorrow and crank out these last two days.
Twenty twenty five is the year, guys.
Finally time to to sally up and hit those goals.
So, guys, appreciate you.
And we'll see you inside of the Rankin Red Academy. I'm out.