All right, we are live.
Let's see.
I think just want to make sure I can hear myself.
All right, I don't think we have anyone on yet, but we're going to keep rolling along.
All right, looks like we just got a couple of people that hopped on.
Just so you know, Nick is going to be on in just a few minutes.
He's on his way to the office.
Don't worry, you're not stuck with me for the next hour.
Can you guys let me know if you can hear me?
I'm trying to get Facebook on my phone, but should be able to hear me.
Let's see.
All right, so see we got a couple people on.
Can you guys hear me?
Make sure I can't hear myself.
Nick's going to be on in just a few minutes.
He is on his way to the office.
So just hang tight real quick.
Thank you, Aaron Smith.
Appreciate that, bro.
Coming in loud and clear.
All right.
And dude, Aaron, I think, aren't you, didn't you just join?
I think I saw your post on digital landlords.
That's awesome, bro.
I'm super excited to have you.
How this normally works is Nick will just go live here at 7 a.m. MST.
But again, he just asked me real quick to jump in
because he's going to be a few minutes late on the way to the office.
But we're going to get this thing rolling.
It's going to be a fun topic.
It's going to be talking about second money.
And what's cool about that is some people might be like, well, I got a first.
Let's see, Stephanie says there's no link.
Stephanie, are you talking about our group message with like Kyle and fix it?
Or I'm not sure what you mean by there's no link.
I did message you, by the way, in our group chat.
But Matthew says, I hear you, Aaron.
Nice to be here.
Yes.
Thank you, Matthew.
Nice to be here as well.
I just sent Nick the zoom link, so we're going to get this thing rolling.
And again, we're going to be talking about second money.
And what's cool about second money is that even if you're still working on that first deal,
anytime you're learning about sales or just like business principles
or just pricing structure in general,
it seems like can be so applicable to just every aspect of whatever stage you're in in business.
So I'm looking forward to talking about it.
And so we're getting a few more people on.
Just as a quick recap, guys, Nick's going to be on in a few minutes.
So hang tight with me real quick.
And we're going to get this thing rolling.
Let me check my messages from him.
Awesome.
He says he's going to be there in a few minutes.
So while we're waiting, I don't want to have dead air.
I can do a quick little story of the Daniel says good morning.
Good morning, Daniel.
Good to see you, brother.
So again, we're just waiting for Nick right now.
He's going to be on soon.
But so as of right now, I don't have any active deals.
That's like 100% on me.
Like I've closed deals in the past.
I've done a complete A to Z on my own.
And then with winter, because it was in Michigan,
and we had to put a pause on it.
Anyway, that said, I've had deals.
And looking back on it, it's so important to qualify your business owners
because you can waste a lot of time.
Oh, Stephanie says, I thought this was a Zoom, but I hear you.
Yeah, I know this is just going to be the live.
I mean, if Nick has time, I know we've done this in the past,
but I'm like bring people on for Q&A, like onto the Zoom.
So we can actually see.
We'll probably be a little short on time today.
We can even see about starting to do that at the end of each live call each week.
Anyway, so what happened was when you're calling these business owners,
I would usually come from the perspective or the mindset.
I'm inconveniencing them.
I'm asking them, please take my leads.
And that's just the wrong way to approach it
because we're the one who's actually delivering the value.
And so this was like a year ago when I was still pretty insecure
about all this stuff didn't like sales, that much didn't know what I was doing.
I mean, I knew what I was doing, but just didn't have much experience.
So I called this guy.
It's his Hispanic dude, right?
And he was like, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
He was super excited as he should be.
It's free leads.
And so I don't ask him any questions though,
because I'm afraid to lose the deal.
I mean, looking back on it, it's absolutely ridiculous, right?
You should be asking like, hey, man, I'm happy to give you a couple of free leads,
but just to make sure I don't want to waste your time or my time.
Can I ask a couple of quick questions just to make sure this is going to be a good fit, right?
And so again, that's when it talks about the pullback, right?
And so I'm just reliving this in my mind.
Bottom line is I send this guy a couple of leads.
We go to hop on the Zoom call.
And by the way, for the few of you that just jumped on,
Nick's going to be on in a few minutes.
He's on his way to the office.
Anyway, I've sent this guy a few concrete leads at this point, right?
They're good leads.
I've live transferred them.
He goes, we have a Zoom call scheduled.
I start the Zoom.
I'm excited.
I'm ready to do this thing.
He doesn't show.
I text him.
I don't hear anything back.
Few hours later, this was scheduled for the morning.
He texts, sorry, bro.
I was late at a party last night with my brother and I slept in.
So that's a bit of a red flag, right?
Anyway, like, okay, whatever.
And I didn't like do anything to like do a pullback or whatever.
I was just like totally getting walked all over.
And I was like, okay, well, we can do it tomorrow or whatever when we schedule it.
So we go to schedule it.
And I had prefaced this when we, the day before, said, by the way, bro,
if you could be at your desktop or laptop, that'd be great.
In case I need to share my screen, it'll just help the call to go by faster, right?
So he's like, oh yeah, that sounds great.
So we have the scheduled Zoom call.
The dude shows up on his phone at the park with his like younger girl, right?
Let's see, I'm just checking the message from Nick.
He's going to be on soon.
So right then and there, I should have been like, dude, I should have done a pullback.
And like, it doesn't look like you're like actually serious or whatever.
We're here to do business or whatever, something, right?
Because he just did exactly the opposite of what I asked him to do, right?
Plus I need to share my screen, like that's a real thing.
And so he goes, it's like, yeah, man, sorry, like just here.
It's like, okay, whatever.
So I just do the call, right?
And I have no control of the sales process.
He's just stringing me along the whole time, right?
Go to find out.
This is where prospecting qualifying comes in.
The guy is, it was actually, it was crazy.
I go to hop on, turns out he, he doesn't have a green card.
So he's an illegal alien.
And like, I was like 16 at this point.
And so it was actually kind of funny because I was kind of like freaking out internally,
like, oh my goodness, am I going to get in trouble for doing business with like whatever?
Like, you know what I'm saying, right?
And so bottom line is I just kind of looked past that still see if we can make something work.
So I go to drop price and what do you know?
Boom, he's out.
I was going to charge like a thousand bucks a month.
And we were getting like, if I remember, it was like at least 12 to 15 leads a month.
What a nightmare.
If I was one year younger, I probably would have started crying.
And yes, Eman, that is the proper emoji for that.
So the moral of the story is to qualify these people, right?
Now there is a little trick.
Like if you ask too many questions on the cold call, it does seem like you will lose them.
But what I found to be helpful is that when you hop on the cold call,
depending on where they're at, it can be helpful to send them one lead to just like,
so you show you're legit and then they're interested in that and be like,
hey man, I'm happy to send you a few more.
But hey, let's hop on a quick like chat today or tomorrow or whatever.
And just so we can learn more about each other, right?
In case we just want to see if this is a good fit, right?
So then you're giving them permission to learn more about you.
That way they're not scared of like, who is this guy and have zero dollars.
Like we can be transparent with them, right?
And then vice versa, right?
So, oh, Eman says, just call me E homie.
Thanks, bro.
Appreciate it, Eve.
Um, yeah, dude.
Um, anyway, so let's see.
Like it's a few minutes late, but anyway, that's it guys.
Qualify these people.
We're the ones who bringing, like we are looking for a win-win partnership, right?
But we're the ones who are bringing the value to the table, right?
And so it's really important not to get walked over by these business owners.
I've lost a lot of deals from that.
It's taken me a lot than that.
Yeah.
Anyway, so prospecting is a really big one.
And I guess the biggest thing is like, just don't be scared to lose the deal.
Number one, you probably won't.
Number two, if you do, they probably aren't a good fit anyway.
As long as obviously you don't be like super like interrogation style with it.
But Jason, good morning.
Glad to have you here, bro.
Let's see.
Nick should be on moment Tito.
Sorry about this guys.
Oh, thanks, Mahmood.
Yeah, man.
Um, hope that call goes well, bro.
If you put in reps, I know you're crushing it.
That's really cool to see all the lives you're doing in the group.
So, yeah, that was probably like the worst sales experience.
Um, yeah, that was pretty crazy.
Um, all right.
So, okay, well, may as well.
May as well relive another sales story.
And what's really cool about this though, guys, is when we look at the sales process,
obviously when, when dealing with people, there's always variables, right?
Just with responses and this or that or triggers or whatever.
Right.
But there is like when Jordan, love him or hate him.
When Jordan Belfort says like every sale is the same, there is a truth to that.
Right.
Like when we look at the sales process that we have, it is a straight line.
And so all we gotta do is like check these boxes.
And it is really like, think talks about in the modules, baking the cake.
When we add these ingredients, 99% of the time, we should get a cake out the other side.
Right.
And so what's really cool about that is usually in sales, it can feel super overwhelming.
But for us, all we gotta do is just make enough cold calls to get someone on the hook.
Right.
All we gotta do is just live transfer enough leads to get them ready for the zoom call.
And then all we gotta do is the zoom call.
It really is like a three-step sales process.
Right.
It is the prospecting, the setup, and the close.
And so what's so cool about that is some of us are better than others at different parts.
Like I was really bad at all three.
I've gotten a little better at the closing.
But I still need to get better at the prospecting and the setup.
Right.
And qualifying these business owners and just not getting so nervous and all that.
But what's so cool about that is once we check off all the boxes, that's when it does become
a machine.
Right.
And that's when we can put in the certain inputs to get the outputs.
And that's when we can predictably grow our business.
Right.
So that's the state I'm in right now.
And by the way, for the few of you that just hopped on, Nick's gonna be on any minute.
Hang tight.
I have texted him the zoom link.
He's gonna be on soon.
So anyway, it's funny.
Like a lot of the, it seems like with this group, the main issues isn't, most people
struggle with the sales in this business.
Right.
Like so many people know how to rank a website or get leads.
But a lot of people just struggle with converting that to specifically flat fee deals.
Because that's really where you scale.
I mean, you can make money with commission and pay per lead, but there's just so much
maintenance per client.
It's really not, it's really difficult to scale that way.
But I was going to say the biggest issues, it seems like even me personally is just on
the tech side with getting Google ad set, getting the due diligence, which is actually
kind of cool to some degree, because once we get those things dialed in, then for our
personal agencies, it is just so much easier to scale because we have just the sales process
works.
Right.
And so I'm excited to be getting back into things.
I actually got another lead yesterday for my ad campaign.
So I need to be live transferring that over.
And so yeah, guys, it's a good business.
Like I was actually on a zoom with Jason Oliver the other day.
And it seems like a helpful perspective when looking at this is to look at it as somewhat
of a game, right?
Not that we want to be cavalier, irresponsible about it.
But when we look at it as a game, it seems like, for me at least, it helps me to kind
of like lower the emotional, like tension or anxiety or whatever, and just like look
at this as a game again.
Moving pieces like, OK, I got to check these six boxes.
What's the one thing that's holding me up?
OK, I need the ads are holding me up or whatever.
Or like, OK, I just can't get someone on the hook.
Right.
And so whatever it is, that is the dragon to slay at that moment.
And so Nick just said he's getting on now.
So anyway, guys, I'm just excited to be getting back with things.
And I mean, if it takes me a year to land a couple deals, the amount of progress you
can make in a three month period in this business once the processes are dialed in
makes it so worth it.
And so just because it's going slow now or for me like, man, a couple of months.
And to be fair, I really haven't been taking the action I should.
So that's on my end.
But again, just like looking at long picture, like a six month sprint, you guys have no
idea.
Like the people that are making like 10k plus a month in this business, a lot of them
got there really fast once they kind of got through the weeds or got through the mud
of the first couple of months or whatever.
Like I know that's what happened with Jason.
And I mean, obviously, we've all seen Ryan Dalton and his insane scaling in just a few
short year or two.
So Nick is stopping on now.
All right.
Aaron, can you hear me?
I can hear you.
Let's see.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Let me try the mic.
Hold on.
How about now?
I can hear you.
Yeah, you're good.
Everyone, can you hear Nick?
You should be able to.
Let me know as soon as you can hear me.
I'm gonna pull up my notes.
Yeah, yesterday, my mic wasn't working.
I don't know what's going on, but good to hear.
Yeah.
Awesome.
They say that they can hear you loud and clear, which is great.
Let me see if I get my camera.
Let me check on Facebook.
I'm not seeing your screen on my screen.
It might just be the.
Oh, no, hold on.
There we go.
Can you see me now?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
So not to cut anyone off.
Are you recording?
Not yet.
Here we go.
Amazing.
Thanks for starting this call, Aaron.
Welcome to the call, guys.
Aaron, did I cut you off in the middle of something?
No, you're good, bro.
Just reliving some sales deals and all that.
Beautiful.
Okay.
Well, that said, guys, welcome to the call.
If this is your first call, then just know we're going to be doing this forever.
You're going to see this call at this time forever.
I know it's a tiny bit early for some,
but it's the best possible time we can do to get as many people as possible.
So, Aaron, are you going to be able to stay on for this call?
Yeah.
Okay.
So real quick, before we get started, did you talk about the podcast?
Not yet.
I'm just going to leave that to you.
All right.
So, guys, we decided that it would be beneficial for...
I would say it's a bit selfish as well,
but we decided that it would be a good idea to do not the classic,
let me interview the random people in my town who are nobodies
and let me have interviews with people that are not interesting.
That's really bad.
I hate those.
We decided that there's so many nuanced things to this business model
that it would be a good idea to just have an entire podcast,
entire series, an entire show dedicated towards every single nuance
and every single facet of this business.
So we have launched the Digital Real Estate Secrets podcast.
It's just basically 100% all things this business model.
We're going to be talking about everything that you could think of,
every single angle, whatever of this model.
Obviously, we're not going to be teaching what we teach in the program,
so don't think that that's going to be the same material
or that we're going to replace or we're going to be talking about that,
but we are going to be talking about high-level stuff.
There may be some interviews-style stuff
where we bring on guests that are in the space,
but for those of you that want to check that out,
you're going to see a new episode every single week.
So, Aaron, I actually have the link.
Let me go ahead.
Hold on.
Let me see.
This will work.
You can still hear me, right?
Yeah, you're good.
Okay, let me just make sure this is going to work here.
By the way, while you pull that up, just a little shout out to Adair,
locked in a 2,000 a month, six-month contract just this week.
Okay.
Making moves.
A little $12,000, not a bad gig.
I like that a lot.
Okay, let me see if I can get this going.
All right.
Hold on.
By the way, I see a few new faces
that look like this is their first call,
so welcome to the call.
But anyway, congrats on the deal, Adair, by the way.
That's what this is all about.
It's getting that first deal.
That's the most important deal,
and then getting the next, and the next, and the next, and the next.
So anyway, guys, check that out.
Appreciate you guys, if you want to check that out,
great if not, no big deal.
But I may be asking some of you guys to come on,
share your experience, share some of your tips, strategies, et cetera.
So if we reach out, that would be super, super helpful.
Also, Aaron, you had talked about the support and everything else, correct?
I have not talked about that yet.
I was going to wait one more week with...
I'm warning we can't talk about that though, but...
No, no, no, no, no, no problem.
That's fine.
That's completely fine.
So last thing real quick, and then let's get started.
I want to give away some stuff, dude.
Let's give away a few things really quick.
Aaron, I'm going to have you choose...
So for those of you that don't know,
we just have some items that we put together that you guys can use every day.
We have these mouse pads.
We have an AirPod case.
We have a coffee mug.
We have a...
What am I missing?
AirPod case, coffee mug.
What's the last one?
Besides the shirts.
The...
Is that it?
Mouse pad, AirPod case.
I think that's main four.
Well, what am I missing, bro?
The mouse pad, the coffee mug, the AirPod case.
There's a fourth one, I thought.
And the shirt, yeah, those four.
Okay, I thought there's another one.
I could be crazy.
Bro, are you sure?
Shopdigitalandlords.com, I guess we can take it.
Yeah, let's look, dude.
But while you're doing that, just keep the ball rolling.
I will just have to give it to Aaron Smith.
It looks like this is his first call in the game.
So congrats, bro.
Good to have you back.
Jared Bell says, Fanny Pack.
Gotta talk to Ashley and get back.
It's the sticker, bro.
Oh, I gotcha.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
So Aaron, what am I gonna have you do?
I'm gonna go turn on my AC because I seem to forget every single time.
Will you go ahead?
I want you to choose, let's just say five winners.
I want you to give away, or four winners.
I want to have you give away a sticker, an AirPod case, a mug,
and a mouse pad really quick.
And then let's get this call rolling.
Okay, so real quick, let's just see.
You know what we'll do is, I'm not sure what you guys want.
So we'll say, Aaron, you can just message,
message fix it Felix in the group.
And he'll hook you up with getting you a promo code for the merch store.
So Aaron Smith, you got it.
Let me just quickly reply.
We'll say, and then we'll get this ball rolling with, again, 2D.
Usually the intros don't take this long, by the way, guys.
We had a few hangups with getting the call going, but it's all good.
So we'll say, message fix it for your swag.
Your swag.
Okay, congrats, Aaron Smith.
We'll say, Matthew, you're always here, bro.
Let's give you something.
Matthew Torres?
Yep.
Yeah, he's always showing up.
I like that.
Let's see, Daniel, how's it going, bro?
You got something too?
We got two more that we're going to give out for your swag.
And then let's see.
Stephanie, I think you've already gotten some items,
but it's always great to have you here.
Stephanie's always got that good energy.
Give her something.
I like that.
We appreciate good energy.
We appreciate positivity.
We appreciate people that have the can do,
I'm going to make it work attitude,
not everyone else's fault that I'm not making a million dollars a second.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Nick, it might be a little late.
If you do want to do the everyone tag,
you have to do it on your mobile phone, I guess.
So I can't because I'm not logged in.
I'm not even, I'll download Facebook on my phone,
but you know me, man, I'm like a drug addict.
I have to take everything off my phone or I just spend all my time on it.
I'll tag everyone as soon as it downloads.
Did we give away four?
We did do four.
Yep.
So I just messaged the winners.
Let's get this thing going.
Okay, guys, today we're going to be talking about the truth about second money.
I get a little bit fired up about this topic
because I felt like I was given misinformation.
And so I am excited to talk about this.
And I'm also excited for Aaron to give his feedback as well.
So let me go ahead.
I'm almost logged in now.
I may as well just go ahead and finish this off.
Hold on.
Let's see.
Okay, we're in the world groups.
By the way, guys, life hack, if you want to get stuff done,
just to get social media off your freaking phone,
I promise you guys, even if you don't think it helps,
just not just knowing you can't,
you don't even have the ability to click on the stupid app
is enough that I swear to you, it gives you superpowers.
So what I try to do now, I fail weekly at this
because I'll download it to post and then I'll leave it on like an idiot.
But I just try not to keep the apps on my phone.
And it's amazing that you start to use your brain.
You start to think creatively.
You start to have real conversations.
You start to plan.
And I think social media is such a powerful tool.
I'm never going to be the guy that's like, don't use it, don't be on it.
I think that's stupid, too, because you need to use it.
I've made a lot of money from social media.
I'm going to make a lot more money.
I think you should be building a brand and an audience.
However, I think that you should be like,
hey, if I'm going to be on social media, I'm producing.
I'm putting out content.
I'm creating networking opportunities, et cetera.
To sit there and scroll.
And again, I fail every week, so I'm not saying I'm perfect,
but it has been a huge deal to just delete it off my phone.
So that said, guys, second money.
Aaron, I'm curious.
When I say second money, what do I mean?
Do you have any idea what I'm talking about,
what I'm saying with second money?
I'm assuming you're saying something to the effect of an upsell
or selling a current customer more.
Correct.
So when I say second money, I'm talking about
you have a client and you go and you get a second money from them,
a third money, a fourth money, a fifth money.
They're already your client and you're going to go get money.
Now, guys, I want to tell you that the idea and the theory of second money,
it sounds so genius on paper.
It makes all the sense in the world, right?
Because they say getting a new client is the hardest part.
I don't know who's they.
I don't know where it's said, but I've heard that many times.
The hardest thing to do is get a new client.
The most expensive thing to do is get a new client.
So in theory, taking a current client and just selling them something else,
getting another chunk of money makes total sense.
And it's kind of like paper lead, right?
For those of you that are brand new to this group,
we hear about, you know, I always talk about how much I dislike paper lead.
And some of you guys are like, well, why?
You know, you get paid according to how many leads you produce and blah, blah, blah.
And I'm telling you guys on paper, paper lead sounds so good,
but in theory and practice, it doesn't work.
And I'm telling you guys on paper and in theory,
second money sounds amazing, but in practice, that's not how it works.
So long story short, guys, is like, I think it was back in 2000.
I don't know.
It was early in my career doing this.
It was like 2018, 2019.
I was in part of...
Actually, let me back up just a little bit.
Let me give you guys really quick the game plan of what we're going to be discussing today.
And I'll start by saying that my goal with this live,
my goal with this training is that by the end of this live,
I want to basically expose to you the truth about second money, okay?
And give you guys enough information to show you that it's not exactly how it appears
and you need to consider all the costs before just going and focusing on it or asking for it, okay?
So here's kind of the things I'm going to cover today.
I'm going to be talking about this theory of second money and how genius it sounds on paper.
I'm going to be talking about why I decided to try it, okay?
And what I learned from it.
Then I'm going to be talking about my experience and how it went.
Then I'm going to be talking about what happened when I stopped doing it.
Then I'm going to be talking about how I actually tried to do it again
after I did it the first time.
Then how to properly...
Sorry.
Yeah, you know, how to properly do second money
because there is a proper way, I believe.
Then I'm going to share a friend's story with second money
and then I'm going to give you guys a challenge, okay?
So that's kind of going to be what we're going to cover.
I'll get through it pretty quick and then if we have questions,
we're going to get through those at the end as well.
So basically the theory of second money is you have a client, you go ask them for more money.
You have a lead gen client, you go ask them to do their SEO with you.
You have a lead gen client, you go ask them to go and use your white labeled software
that you're doing with go high level.
You have a client, you ask them to manage their Facebook account where you post every...
And guys, Aaron, doesn't it make perfect sense?
Literally on paper, it's like we don't have to go call.
We don't have to go cultivate any new relationships.
We just get new business.
We just get new money from current clients.
Am I wrong or does that not sound attractive to you?
It's attractive.
Have you tried it?
I have not.
To be fair, I haven't had that many customers to test it on, but I still hopefully wouldn't
because I know what you're going to say.
I believe it.
So I just want to say this and just real quick before we get into why I decided to try it.
Guys, going for second money, third money, fourth money, fifth money,
any money outside of your original lead gen money before you are printing
money with your first money.
Okay.
Obviously, if you're in this group, you should be focusing on lead generation.
Now, I know some of you guys are in a situation where you need to get some cash coming in
so you can quit your job, in which case I think the best way to do that is to do SEO,
just FYI.
And that's why if you guys heard me bring in Zach Powell, he has a really good process
for getting SEO clients and getting that.
But that should just be to quit your job.
And if you don't need to quit your job immediately or you have enough money,
I just think the long-term strategy, it's so much easier to just build a business
where you quit your job on lead gen money because I was in a position
where I didn't have money coming in.
I had to go and do SEO and it's very easy to get sucked down the SEO trap.
As sexy as it sounds, it's not scalable and it doesn't have the longevity that lead gen does.
There's just, I don't care how you set it up, it's just not the same.
But you guys are shooting yourself in the foot.
You guys are crazy.
If you guys are trying to go for second, third, fourth money
before you are printing money with your first money,
before you have your entire process automated and dialed in to the point
where you don't even have to be involved.
Because guys, what ends up happening is like this second money concept,
you know, it's actually the same as starting another business.
It's actually the same as distracting yourself with a completely separate business,
but it disguises itself as a complimentary service.
And I'm going to get into my experience doing it,
but I'm just going to start and tell you upfront that splitting your attention,
splitting your focus is so detrimental to growing your business.
It's insane and sometimes you don't even recognize it
because you won't see it immediately, but it's taxing to your bandwidth,
it's taxing to your focus.
And it's going to be the death of you.
It's going to come at the expense of you hitting your goal, okay?
So anything that I say for, I'm going to use the term second money,
but it goes for third, fourth, fifth, sixth money, right?
Second money would be like SEO.
Third money would be like social media management.
Fourth money would be like white label software.
Fifth money could be doing swag, you know, I don't know what I'm on,
sixth, seventh could be consulting.
I mean, there's so many different layers to this because again,
the theory is businesses spend money on all these different things.
Let's go and get as many pieces of the pie as we possibly can.
And again, we look at some of these examples like a Warren Buffett, right?
And Warren Buffett, I think they said when you go and buy something at the store,
he's making money on the credit card.
He's making money on the Coke.
He's making money on like four or five different things.
And so we want to sit there.
We want to mimic people like Warren Buffett, but we forget that Warren Buffett,
he made his initial money by focusing on one thing.
And then he's now diversified into how many income streams.
So we confuse that when we hear we need seven income streams.
No, you need one to get rich and you need to then diversify to keep your money
and to grow your money.
But you need one and you should focus on one to get that initial capital, okay?
So again, guys, I want you to know that I understand that the theory of second money
sounds sexy.
It sounds fun.
It sounds like, hey, I've got 10 clients.
Like for example, Adair, I know he's gotten three, four, five deals
because I've announced all of them.
And congratulations, by the way, bro, that's no small feat.
But it becomes very attractive to stop doing what we know works because it's hard.
It's hard to go find new areas.
It's hard to pick up the phone and do another cold call.
It's hard to go and set up another ad campaign.
And it sounds amazing to take our five clients or seven clients or 10 or 20 clients
and say, hey, bro, hey, Joe, I'm going to do your SEO.
It sounds very, very, very attractive.
And I'm probably going against things I've said in the past.
But that's the beauty of business is that I'm evolving and I'm growing.
And maybe I'll even talk about this on the podcast this week or next week.
But this is from experience.
And that's the thing that I can sit here and tell you with conviction is that
I've tried this and I've tried it multiple times.
And this is how it works.
So guys, I'm going to tell you now why I decided to try it
and then what I learned from it.
So again, back in like 2000, I think 17, 18, 19, somewhere in there,
somebody that I was in another group, I was in multiple groups,
but I was the course guy.
I bought so many programs.
I think I spent around 23,000.
They have calculated 23 to 30,000 somewhere in there.
That's only on rank and rent programs.
That's only on marketing.
That doesn't include any type of like one-on-one coaching or whatever.
This is just with rank and rent specific marketing programs.
And there was a piece of advice that I got from somebody in one of these programs.
And that was that I was a fool for not going for second, third, fourth money.
And the thing that tricked me, the thing that confused me is this person
actually does make a lot of money.
They just don't make a lot of money doing this.
They just don't make a lot.
And they never did.
And that's the thing that we need to distinguish, guys,
is that there's a lot of people out there that are making money
by teaching things and not doing the thing that they teach.
That's basically every other person out there teaching rank and rent
because I know all of them.
There's an exception or two.
But majority of them, they made $10,000 one time
and they decided, hey, I'm going to throw together a program
and I'm going to teach people how to do this, which is cool.
That's great.
But how do you coach somebody past your skill level?
I talked about this a few weeks back.
How do you convert someone past your own conversion?
How do I train you how to get to $100,000 a month
if I've never been there?
And so be very careful because I know some of you guys
are in other groups.
Some of you guys are in multiple groups
and especially those of you that are in free groups.
I see you.
I see some of you guys pouring yourself out
and jumping at every single free piece of information, free PDF.
It's from some no name in a group.
If they're in the model, you don't even know if it's a human.
You don't even know if they even know what money is.
You don't know any of this stuff.
And I see you guys getting all these free things.
And guys, just because something's free
doesn't mean you should take it.
I had a dog took a freaking dump in my front yard.
That cost me no dollars.
I'm not going to keep the dung and sprinkle it on my garden.
It was free.
I was so pissed.
By the way, Aaron, I know you have dogs, right?
We doubt.
I thought you had a dog.
OK.
So I was going to make this announcement.
Maybe you guys could tell me.
I was so pissed yesterday.
We brought the boat in and I saw three piles of shit.
And I'm sorry because I wasn't going to curse.
But I saw three piles of shit on my front yard, right?
Is this on the artificial grass?
On my artificial grass, paid for by Dre, by the way.
But on my artificial grass, thank goodness
it was artificial grass.
I could spray it off.
But I swear to you, I have a Facebook group in my community
and I'm going to put on there.
And if you guys love dogs, you could be offended.
I don't care.
I'm going to take a picture of all three piles.
And I'm going to post it on our community group and say,
we just installed new cameras.
If I catch your dog taking a shit on my front yard,
you could pick it up at the crematory.
Ha ha ha ha ha in an ash box.
OK.
So don't eat shit on my front yard.
Anyway, just because it's free does not mean that you guys
should actually take it.
OK.
So I listen to this guy.
He gave me free advice and the dude makes a lot of money.
But he doesn't make it doing this.
That's the whole point of this conversation is that, guys,
if they don't make money doing this, why are you listening to it?
OK.
Why are you listening to it?
Dave Ramsey, perfect example.
Everybody listens to Dave Ramsey.
Dave Ramsey does not make his money by following his own advice.
That's the irony behind good old Dave and his program and his radio show.
He does not make money doing what he preaches.
So I don't know how that guy goes to bed at night.
It would feel really weird to me to be making a lot of money
and have never made a million dollars.
That's why I just shake my head at people that are like,
I'm going to start a program.
Good.
That's your choice.
Good luck.
OK.
Anyway, I decided to give this a try.
And the mistake that I made, guys,
is that I followed somebody's advice that wasn't in the game.
I followed somebody's advice that was making money
by doing something different than what they were talking about.
And so that's the biggest thing that I learned, guys,
is that you have like the number one thing I learned,
apart from the fact that it's not a good idea,
is that it taught me that I can't listen to anything
that this person is saying past $10,000 a month,
because I think this person had made like $24,000
in one month or two months,
but they hadn't made anything past that.
And so that was the biggest thing it taught me,
is that just because the thing that they're teaching me
worked for them in this other business,
it's not necessarily applicable to this business.
And so I want you guys to remember
that if nothing else inside this group, guys,
I've been to the place that you guys like so far,
no one has passed where I got to.
I got to $124,000 per month.
I do not know anyone that has gotten to that point.
And I know I see people on social media
talking about making $140,000.
And dude, in fact, there's a couple of brothers right now,
they live in my hometown,
and they have a program apparently, okay?
Never heard of these guys, never heard of them.
And they're posting about making $140,000.
So they watch all of my stories.
They follow me, they have for years.
And I've tried to reach out to them a couple of times
to just have a conversation
because I think that they're a scam.
So I'd messaged them literally the other day.
And I was like, hey guys, Nick here.
Love to hop on the phone and chat
and see what you guys got going on
since we're in the same town.
This is my second message.
And it says active like four minutes ago.
These guys don't read my message.
So I just messaged them like, hey, it's ironic
that you guys watch all my stories.
You guys are fanboys, but you can't,
you're pretending not to see my message.
Anyway, long story short,
these guys aren't making $140,000.
I promise you that.
I posted my tax returns inside the free group, okay?
My tax returns are inside the free group
for those of you that doubt the money that I've made.
Because it really bothered me
and does bother me when people just make false claims.
So that's the biggest thing that I learned
and that's what I want you guys to take away
is it drives me nuts when I see you guys commenting
inside of these other Facebook groups
and inside these other programs that I'm also a part of.
And you guys are just getting free stuff.
I just got an email today from another rank and rank group.
It's a program that I bought.
It's a friend of mine.
And he's like promoting this.
The dude doesn't make any money on this stuff, okay?
So just freaking listen to people that you are like,
if they haven't been somewhere you want to go
and stop listening to them.
So anyway, that's why I decided to try it
and that's what I learned, okay?
Now, let me tell you about my experience.
When I did this, when I implemented this,
what ended up happening is first and foremost,
I became very relieved.
Because I remember sitting there thinking,
wow, I hate cold calling people.
And yeah, I've made it to this point,
but I don't like to call people.
And if I didn't imagine,
if I don't have to call any new business owners,
I don't have to talk to any new people.
I don't have to meet anybody else.
That'd be so nice because guys, it's scary.
Even to this day for me to pick up this phone
and call strangers, it's still uncomfortable.
It's always gonna be uncomfortable
because it's always easier to talk to people
that you know, right?
And so I remembered my initial reaction to this is like,
I had a big sense of relief because I was like,
oh my gosh, this is gonna be so nice.
I'm not gonna have to talk to anybody new.
I'm gonna take my 10 clients.
I'm gonna sell them SEO.
Then I'm gonna sell them social media marketing.
And dude, I'm gonna triple my revenue, Aaron.
I'm gonna triple my revenue.
I'm gonna go from, you know, 10,000 a month.
Then with that first hit, maybe not even quite triple,
but let's say I sell 70% of the people on SEO.
You know, I'm gonna go from 10,000 to 17,000 like that, right?
And then I'm gonna sell them social media.
Maybe I'll only get 50% from there.
So I'm gonna be at like 22,000 bucks in a month
by just selling them these other services.
Aaron, what do you think happened?
You didn't triple or even double.
Not only did I not grow, my revenue actually went down, dude.
It actually went down.
Why?
Because, well, number one is I took my eye off the main thing
and the main thing is Legion
and that's the only thing that scales.
And so my service, my core service suffered, okay?
And because my core service suffered, guess what happened?
My referrals that I wasn't once getting
that was helping me grow my business completely dried up
because now those little tiny touches that I was making,
those checking in here, checking in there,
you guys saw me post this recently,
sending flowers to my customer's wife
because I had the mental bandwidth to do it.
Not that that's gonna necessarily grow your business.
Getting clients success and getting them results
is the number one thing,
but just those little touches,
I didn't even have the bandwidth for them.
So not only did my business not grow,
but it actually went down.
My core service suffered.
My referrals completely dried up
and I actually had and struggled to have a hard time.
I had a hard time retaining the clients that I did have.
My current clients then became a challenge to even keep those.
There was literally no growth and there was just frustration.
And actually my bottom line number went down
because guess what?
I added another service
and here's one of the services I offered.
I was so smart, guys.
I was like, I'm gonna do white label Go High Level.
Aaron, you haven't done that?
I barely know what that is, yeah.
So Go High Level is a software that used a CRM.
They have this program, it's genius.
You can go and you can pay to white label their software
and anything you sell above a certain price point
you get to keep and it's so scalable
and you're gonna promote it
and all this different stuff, right?
So that was a really cool service that I offered.
Curious, is there anybody that's like confident enough
or secure enough to admit in the chat
that they've tried that scam of a business model?
Has anyone done that?
I would love to know.
By the way, Aaron, if somebody's comments
that says they've tried it, cut me off and tell me, okay?
Yeah, if not, you guys are, I'm happy
because you guys are smarter than me.
But guys, guess what?
I didn't know how to do Go High Level.
I didn't know how to sell soft, like that kind of software.
I didn't know how to set it up.
I didn't know what, like whatever.
So guess what I did?
I went and hired somebody that was familiar
with Go High Level and I paid them, wasn't crazy
but I think I paid them like, for me at the time
it was really crazy.
It was like 3,500, 4,000 bucks a month.
So I basically, 50K a year to do this whole new service.
That was 50K that I had to make up
just to be at the same point net.
So that was just one service.
I also was offering SEO, third money maybe.
Then I was offering social media management.
Hey Joe, yeah, we actually are pretty good
at managing Facebook.
Check this page out.
We've grown our evergreen page to a thousand likes
and we're getting a lot of views on our videos.
We can actually give you a quote
on managing your Facebook page.
What do you think?
Six service, huh, Aaron?
Yeah.
Six is better than five.
Dude, we were an all encompassing agency.
We offer every service, bro.
A to Z, soup to nuts.
We were the full pack, dude.
We were the Michael Jordan of agencies, bro.
You come into our agency, we got you, dude.
We're getting you leads.
We're building you a new site.
We're going to do your SEO.
We can manage your Facebook.
Need t-shirts, we got you.
Need a CRM, check that, baby.
Dude, you want consulting, call your boy.
Dude, it's so funny because you think I'm joking, dude.
You want merchant services, got a solution for you, dude.
We're a full stack marketing agency, bro.
That's it, dude.
That's what I thought.
How long were you chasing the non-leash end services?
Stop, bro.
Stop, stop offering these services.
I like seven businesses, seven, dude.
And I was telling myself that I was just a full stack
marketing company, dude.
A to Z, bro.
Come in, dude, I got you covered, dude.
There's something else.
Oh, there was a point.
Hold on, hold on, 2020.
We were offering masks, masks, bro.
I can't make this stuff up.
You guys think I'm making this for like comic and dramatic effect?
I promise you, you go ask anyone that was working with me, Francesca.
Kyle wasn't with me at the time, but Francesca, go ask Francesca.
This is real stuff, dude.
This is pathetic.
Luckily, I've moved past the point where I can like laugh about this stuff.
Dude, I thought-
That wasn't long ago, 2022?
That 20, it was, so 2020 was the year we started doing this.
Sorry.
So 2019, so this is the embarrassing part that's funny, right?
So 2018, 19 is when I first started doing this.
And then 2020, not to cut ahead of myself, is when I stopped doing it.
Scaled, go figure.
Then end of 2021, I did it again.
Then I just did it again this year and it was a completely,
and I'll talk about that here in a second.
Anyway, guys, long story short, I didn't grow.
Now, the interesting part, I know there's probably somebody on here
that's like, yeah, I actually just did that and I made some money.
Cool.
But I guarantee that it's coming at the expense of a much bigger payday
that you could have got if you would have just focused on Legion.
Because guess what?
I initially got a deal or two too.
I got one or two people that said yes to me.
Yeah, I got a couple SEO clients and that's what gave me the confidence
to offer the next six services, okay?
So here's what happened.
2019, you guys know the story, I almost quit.
I was tired of this.
I was like, you know what?
I'm not cut out to be a marketing agency.
You know, six months earlier, I was full stack, baby.
I was offering everything, dude, everything.
And then six months later, I was like,
I don't know if I'm ready to do marketing.
I don't know if I should be in business.
I think I should just be a sales guy.
So you guys know the story, 2019,
I just about walked away from doing business for myself.
I was going to be a sales guy for somebody else,
had everything lined out and I luckily pulled my head out
and I was like, you know what, Nick?
No, you have to figure this out
because that's how you're going to get rich
is you have to have your own thing, right?
It's back to the Naval Ravicon, his book.
And he talks about like how to get rich without being lucky.
You have to own the business
or at least a part of the business, right?
That's the only way to get to the true money.
And then I was like, well, this also is recurring.
This also is asset-based.
And I started checking all the boxes and I'm like,
yeah, this is the right business.
I just have to figure this out.
So 2019, beginning of 2020, that's what I did, right?
Is I got rid of everything.
I got rid of every single thing except for Legion.
And ironically, eight months later,
I hit a hundred thousand dollars a month.
No BS, no like it wasn't, you know,
August, it wasn't June, it wasn't October,
July of 2020, we hit a hundred thousand dollars per month.
And eight months earlier, 2019, December,
we barely hit like eight to 10, okay?
So you'd think I would learn, but that's what happened.
As soon as I got rid of everything, I started growing.
Now I'm going to jump ahead a little bit.
One of my buddies, I guess I'd call him
more of a business acquaintance.
You guys probably saw this photo I posted recently
on my personal page, maybe you didn't,
but I did a podcast with this guy named Dan Henry.
He's a really sharp dude, whatever.
It was when I was in Dubai and he shared this reel
just the other day.
And he said that when he started in business
and he did really well, he got up to $250,000 per month.
He had one program or one service
or one product he was selling.
I can't remember what it was at the time.
He got to 250 and he's like,
I'm going to add more products so I can get to a million
or whatever he was trying to get to.
And I think you might've heard me say this yesterday, Aaron,
but dude, he went down from 250.
He added 12 or 13 products and it dropped him to 70,000 per month.
Which is still a lot of money,
but when you're making three and a half times that much,
it's a kick in the pants, right?
So apparently he joined this mastermind
and the guy's like, tell me about your business, blah, blah, blah.
He's like, yeah, 13 different offers.
The guy was like, get rid of 12.
Or he had 14, he said, get rid of 13.
And he's like, okay, he got rid of everything but one.
And he scaled up to 500,000 a month.
Okay, guys, he's done it.
I've done it.
Hermosy's talked about it.
If you guys are offering multiple services, you're stupid.
And I hope someone could clip that and whatever, that's fine.
But until you are printing cash,
until your first service is an automated cash juicing machine,
you guys are losing and costing yourself
thousands and tens of thousands, hundreds of thousands of dollars
by offering multiple services, okay?
So 2020, I scaled.
Beginning of 2021, I started to think about the same idea again.
And that's why you guys hear me talking about selling masks, right?
2020, 2021, everyone is starting to make money and selling masks.
I had some friends that were making supposedly big money in masks.
And I think some of them actually did.
And so I don't know how,
but I forgot that that was the thing that caused me not to scale.
And so I started offering services again.
And I started doing this whole BS again, guys.
And in 2021, what ended up happening is this time I made more money.
So I went from 7,000 or 7 figures, like just over a million, to 1.4, 1.45, 1.5 million.
This has nothing to do with this program.
This is just on my business.
But I actually did not make any additional money, bottom line.
I made the same amount of money.
I did 50% more work.
And I made the same amount of money.
How much more time did I spend away from my family?
How much more stress did I have?
How many more employees did I manage?
How many dinners and golf trips did I miss?
And I made no extra money, like literally no extra money.
I could have done the exact same thing I did the year before,
and I would have made the same amount of money,
and I would have had 50% more time.
So guys, I've heard Hermosy talk about this.
He talks about this concept of the woman in the red dress from The Matrix,
where it distracts you, and it's the very thing that will kill you.
And he says that as you get bigger, as you grow,
the woman in the red dress becomes more attractive, becomes more sexy.
And I will tell you that that is true,
because guess what?
When I did it in 2021, I now had 30 clients.
And the idea of offering a new service was way more attractive to me.
And it was actually in 2021 that I did offer the Go High Level White Label,
and it sounded like such a good idea,
because now I have 30 clients instead of 8 or 10,
and it became more attractive, right?
But guys, all that it was was a freaking distraction, okay?
So I want to tell you guys really quick in these last few minutes
is how I think you should properly do it, okay?
Number one is you need to make sure that your core business,
your lead generation business,
again, for those of you that are trying to get out of your job,
I'm not necessarily talking directly to you,
because I would rather you do SEO to get out of your job and buy your time back,
and then do lead gen to replace that,
then I would have you stuck in your job.
But for everybody else, if you're just building lead gen
and you're okay in your job and you have a pretty good schedule
or you work from home or you don't mind it,
I would highly recommend you just build your income on lead gen only.
And basically what I'm saying is until that money,
that first money pays your bills and a lot more,
like it's spitting off cash,
it's to the point where mine is right now,
where in the last six business days,
we've gotten two deals.
I haven't talked to the clients.
I don't know the client's names.
I can't even remember the second one.
Francesca got like a small $300 a month deal.
I have no idea where it's at, what kind of service it's in,
what the business owner's name is.
I don't know what state it's in,
because I don't have to touch it anymore.
Francesca does it.
The only thing I have to do is approve when we spend money on new stuff.
That's the only thing that I really do in the business anymore.
Until you've gotten to like that point, then don't touch it.
Now, that's number one.
Number two, I personally think that you shouldn't go chasing second money.
I think that with second money, when it starts to come to you,
that's when it's the time.
When second money comes to you, not one time, not two times,
but like five times, that's when you start to go,
all right, I have an opportunity here.
Let me give you an example.
I didn't start digital landlords.
I didn't start this program until 2021 and at the end of 2021.
And guys, it was literally, I'm not saying it was by force,
because I clearly chose it.
And obviously, you guys can do the math.
There's great cash in it, and I'm never going to hide that.
But I didn't seek it out.
I was completely content.
Of course, I thought it was a good idea.
Of course, I knew that it would be a good idea.
But guys, I had five, sometimes 10 people a day reaching out to me,
asking me questions about how I was doing what I was doing,
asking me specifics, asking me if I could jump on a call with them,
asking if they could pick my brain.
And I'm not saying this to sound cool.
I'm saying it because I was trying to just send people videos and answer questions.
I had this opportunity knocking at my door,
and that's when I realized it was the time.
So the way to do it is get your first money,
humming like a machine, firing at all cylinders,
making sure that you're basically completely detached from it.
And then the second money is knocking at your door.
And then, guys, what I would highly recommend is if it's not something
that you have to be involved in, obviously in this,
I have to be heavily involved because it's my process.
It's my face on this thing.
But let's say it's SEO.
Let's say for some reason you got people just knocking at your door for SEO
because all of your clients are so impressed with how you rank
and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
You just have droves of people asking you for SEO.
If that's the case, because SEO is not scalable
and you're going to have to add new employees,
you're going to have to add new systems and processes
and all this different stuff to scale,
guys, what I would highly recommend you doing
is finding a strategic partnership
that you can literally just refer the business to
and never talk to them again.
This is what I did in 2020 is I got rid of my SEO,
which made up almost half of my business,
about 4,000 out of the 10,000.
I created the partnership.
I went to someone and said,
what if you start your own SEO company?
Here's the split.
I don't even want my name on the company.
I just want you to give me 50% of the net profit.
I don't want to talk to them.
I'll sign the deals.
I'll refer you to business.
What do you think?
They said yes.
So when I'm talking about making seven figures in 2020,
that had nothing to do with SEO.
I made $6,000 to $10,000 a month that year,
and that was completely on just basically commissions.
That was basically on splits.
I didn't talk to the clients.
I didn't deal with the clients.
I didn't do anything like that,
and that wasn't included in that seven figures.
That was completely separate money.
That was just gravy money.
That was blow on golf money.
That had nothing to do.
So I didn't have to deal with it.
I didn't, and it's not even that I didn't have to do the service,
but I didn't have to deal with the headache or the bandwidth
or my customers being pissed off that I wasn't ranking.
It wasn't even attached to me.
They called me and tried to complain about it.
See, I'm like, that's not my deal, dude.
That's him.
That's not my business.
I just told you he's good, and I'll text him for you,
but that has nothing to do with me, sir.
And I would text him like, yo, this person's unhappy.
Can you deal with it?
That's the way I think you do second money.
That's the way that I found that works.
Get your business firing.
Wait till the second money is knocking at your door
and then find a strategic partnership.
Now, in the case of this program, it is scalable.
I can create the videos.
I could create the training, and then I could sell the training.
Obviously, we have to do the support and all this different stuff,
but I've committed to doing this.
I figured this out.
It's been a work in progress.
It is a work in progress.
It's a big commitment, but the opportunity was knocking at my door.
That's how I think you do second money.
And guys, I want you to remember, for those of you that are like,
I'm going to go start a court.
I did this in 2016.
Nine months of 2017, I got distracted, but I did part of 2017, 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021.
I did it for five and a half years and made over a million dollars two years in a row
before I even thought about this.
So for those of you that are like,
I'm going to go rip some all-encompassing services.
I'm going to go do the full-stack marketing agency.
Could be a stupid, okay?
So guys, here's my challenge to you guys is get focused.
Get stupid.
Get simple.
What's this kiss?
Keep it stupid simple, right?
Keep it stupid simple.
Focus on one service.
Stop doing second money.
One service, one offering, one niche, one deal structure, one sales process,
and a bunch of money.
That's what I want to recommend to you guys.
That's from experience, not from theory.
Thanks for being on the call, guys.
I will see you guys next week.
Thanks, Aaron.
All right.
Take care.