Alright guys, I appreciate you being on, welcome to the call, we're gonna jump right back in.
I wasn't recording but now I am. Porter was just explaining about how he's trying to double
dip on one of his business owners that's already buying Concrete Leads for him, from him. This
is a really good hack for anybody that has multiple clients and the easiest place to
get new money or to get more money is to get money from your current business owner. And
I always used to hear this term about second money, third money, fourth money and I was
a little bit confused because I thought with second money, third money, fourth money you
had to go and you had to get it from, let's say you are getting lead generation money.
Second money in my mind was you go and get their SEO, that'd be second money, then you
go get their social media. But I also think second money is when you go and there's a
lot of these business owners run multiple companies, they're doing multiple services
because they have shiny object syndrome. So there's that, but more often what you'll see
is you'll find opportunities to get deals in neighboring cities. And so yesterday I
was talking to Jason, me and Jason and Porter were on Zoom and he pointed something out
that I knew, but I didn't realize exactly how, he said it really well. The thing about
the eastern United States, it seems like more in the east you find cities that aren't just
one big city and then a bunch of tiny little suburbs. You find a lot more smaller cities.
And that's what's nice about the east coast. So to give you an example, let's talk about
North Carolina. North Carolina you have Charlotte, that's a big city, but you also have just
north of it, you have Winston-Salem, you have, what else do you have, you have Greensboro
and you have Raleigh, I believe it is. And so those are three, and those aren't huge
cities, but you have opportunities and most businesses would cover all three. Probably
not Charlotte, but they might cover the other three. So that's one thing to think about
when you're starting to look at areas, guys, is looking at areas, yes, when you get your
first deal sometimes you just want to find that one that's close to home or whatever,
but if you can be strategic and find cities where there's more than one opportunity going
forward, you can, you're literally setting yourself up to get easy second, third and
fourth money. So right now it's December 10th, leads are going to be harder to come by, business
owners are going to be a little bit less motivated to work. I mean, if it's hard for us to get
out of bed, to go from the bed to put a beanie on, to come to the office, it's going to
be pretty tough for Bob to get in his truck and do some actual work. But right now is
a good time for you guys to go and get second money, third money, fourth money, et cetera.
So Porter, really good strategy, it's easy, they already trust you, they already know
you, I can't tell you, I've done this so many times, not as many times with a different
service, although I have done that, but a lot of times with the same service inside
of a different city. So how did you actually discover, by the way, that he did fencing?
Well, I remember last year, it was actually a little bit slower. It was seriously about
this time of year and he's like, and I was trying to prep him because I had lost business
owners at this point. So I was like, yeah, like the leads are going to be a little bit
slower in December. And he's like, yeah, he's like, we've been staying busy with, so he
kind of was like, yeah, well, we're okay. Like I expected that, like we're doing fencing,
we're doing, you know, we're still doing concrete jobs or whatever. So we kind of like mentioned
it, but I was like, huh, that's interesting. But it's always been in the back of my mind
to do it. But I was always hesitant because I was like, gosh dang, I don't want to, you
know, do all this work and not work out, you know, so I was always nervous, but I was like,
I don't know why I don't just try it. And after losing those two deals, I'm like, gosh,
the leads have been a little bit slow for the niches that I've been going after in the
area. So I'm like, let me just see if I can just get a quick, you know, quick deal. Cause
this guy's awesome. He, and he's like, yeah, just let me know how much it would cost. He's
like, I, I've been getting fencing jobs, like on his business card, he says he does fencing.
So every time he does like a concrete job or whatever, he'll give him his business card
and it says fencing. So he's got like three or four jobs already, just like doing fencing
jobs. So he's like, yeah, if you can get them to me, he says, yeah, I mean, I'll get it.
I'll get a crew together.
Well, there you go. So just like guys, go to your business owners that you, that you're
doing a great job for, and they will spend second money with you, third money, fourth
money. I don't recommend you to necessarily go and get money in different services. Although
if you do that, I wouldn't do the work yourself. Like if you have a strategic partnership set
up where you can take an SEO deal, for example, send it to somebody, they'll give you, you
know, 50% at least of the deal and you don't have to do the work. That's great. But again,
I think it's easier to get another lead gen deal. So anyway, that said, that's a really
good strategy. The other thing, guys, is just to put in a plug and to remind you guys, just
like the fact that we have rank and rent engine and we can do due diligence with rank and
rent engine, it's saving you so much freaking time. I, I just, I don't even know how many
hours I have spent in my life doing freaking due diligence and doing it by hand, doing
it on a Google sheet, whatever. And now we can literally go in. All you got to do is
you got to find the competitors really quick. Boom, you push one button and it's calculated
in two minutes. And if you guys haven't used it, Porter, you've, have you done due diligence
yet with rank and rent engine?
Yeah, it's so, I was so surprised. I was expecting to have to get out white sparks and
we can look at my, my citations.
And the beautiful part is the, the, the backlink tool is getting beefed up where you're
gonna be able to, you know, take a deeper dive into the backlinks. But guys, real quick,
if you are, I want to just share this little nugget really quick and then we're going to
get in to what the topic is today. But it's very, very easy. What I do is I have my keyword
list, I have rank and rent engine open. And then what I do is I just go clear a browser,
whatever, incognito mode, I have my five to seven keywords, I type them out, I add the
city at the end, boom, boom, boom, push for search on all five to seven searches. And
then I flip through really quick and I look at, you know, now I'm just taking a peek at
the organic. I don't pay as much attention to the maps, but I'm looking who's the top
organic person and do they show up on all five websites? If they do, or at least three
to five, three to five, if they do check the box, boom, I'm grabbing the domain, I'm putting
it in rank and rent engine. I'm doing this for the top three competitors. And I try to
exclude usually the big national players, the not the Zillow, the home advisor, the
Angie's List, that kind of stuff. I'm looking for the local people. And you put it in there,
the three websites, you push the one button, beep, and literally, it's calculated and it's
done. It's frickin ridiculous. So if you're sitting there and you guys are like waiting
for leads, not sure where to go, go look at the deals you already have and look how you
can turn it into two deals, three deals, four deals, those are the easiest thing to
do. Go get the second money, the third money, the fourth money. I promise you that's gonna
be a quick win. And nothing's better, guys, than when you finish the year on a strong
note because how you finish is how you're gonna remember the year. Even if you've had
a terrible year, even if you haven't hit your goals or whatever, if you go and just put
your foot on the gas for the next two weeks, I guess three weeks, you're gonna look back
on this year and remember it and go, man, that was a great year. I promise you because
I've done this with other things too, but it's how you finish is how you remember the
year or how you remember the experience. And also if you've had a phenomenal year, you
go ahead and take your foot off the gas and say, I'm gonna pack it in. That's how you're
gonna remember the year. It's gonna give you zero momentum going into the new year. And
I think it's the worst possible way to start the new year. Now, if you are somebody that's
been very intentional, you've said in your head, I'm gonna be taking off this week, these
two weeks to go and travel and I've earned it, whatever, that's completely fine. But
guys, go and get a deal. Even if you can get one more deal before the first year, two more
deals, it's the best thing you can do to jumpstart your next year. Okay? So let's go ahead, get
started real quick. And let's talk about the topic at hand. Oh, by the way, there's one
more thing I wanted to share. Hold on. I think there's a new code. If you guys, let's see.
By the way, guys, do you guys like in this, dude, look at this mad pic that we got going
on here, dude. This is like three years ago. I'm looking sweet, dude. What's pick are you
talking about? Look at look at this. The the little teaser here. Check this out. Look at
Jason Jason's all fresh shaving, dude. Look at this. Yeah, that's a good Yeah, me too,
dude. That's like two years ago, I think. Or maybe at least it's at least a year, dude.
Freaking glow down. Just kidding. Okay, so let's get let's go ahead and get into this.
We're gonna pardon Jason off of this call. I'm not sure what came up. I'm hoping he got a deal.
He's very rarely not on these calls. But we're gonna go ahead and give him a little bit of an
excuse. Hopefully pops in at the end. If he did sleep in, you know what, we're gonna give him a
little bit of a slack because he's human. Okay. All right. Here's what I want to do, guys. Oh,
what I was gonna say is if you have not signed up for Rankin and Ninja, and you wish to do so,
and by the way, you don't need to use Rankin and Ninja. You can use whatever you want. Just so
you know, by the way, the way that we train this up until now has been use whatever tool you want,
whatever one floats your boat, whatever one frickin different strokes for different folks.
But it's going to be much easier for you guys if you want to use Rankin and Ninja because our
version 3.0 is going to be built entirely off of that because that's what I use exclusively now.
But if you didn't want to get that or sign up for that, you guys can message me. I have a new code
for those of you that haven't ever signed up for the 20% off for two months. Send me a private
message. I'll give you the code. So just as a heads up, Gina Benson just got into the house.
What's up, Gina Benson? Good to have you. Okay. So the reason I wanted to bring Porter on is,
and we're gonna talk about the commonalities of winners, is Porter's in a unique spot because
most of the people between him and Jason, most of the people that join our program, most people that
join this community now are going through Porter and Jason at some point. They're talking to them
on a phone call before they get on a call with Kyle. And also, for those of you that have been
in this group a while, you guys remember last year Porter was doing, he was the accountability
coach and he was jumping on calls with people who would, basically he was holding people accountable
and he was getting to really know the group. And we actually, there's a good chance we're gonna be
bringing that back because we're redoing the training and going into 3.0 and changing the way
we do everything. He's not doing that this second because we don't want to start and stop. But
anyway, I wanted to bring him on because he has a unique perspective. He's talked to a lot of the
people in this group. And so I wanted to go ahead and talk about some of the things that he's seen
that are the commonalities, and I said it in the group or as the title, the commonalities of winners.
One of the things that all the people that are having great success have in common. And then we're
gonna talk about the things that people that are not having success have in common and we're gonna
kind of dissect that a little bit. I hate when people use a bunch of quotes and that, you know,
oh and so and so Napoleon Hill said this and freaking MJ DiMarco said that and you know that
bugs me. But I will say that some of these quotes, as annoying as they are, I believe that they make
sense and I've lived by them. And so one of the quotes that I heard many years ago, it was really
cool when I heard it because I hadn't heard it 7,000 times. But the quote is success leaves clues.
So forget about it being cliche, it's true. And it's like if somebody else is winning,
just freaking do what they do, right? If somebody's making a million dollars a month,
then I just need to look at what they do and I need to figure out what are those clues and the
things that they're doing that I'm not. And, and this is Hermosy that really taught me this,
what are the things that they're not doing that I'm doing? I used to think there's things that I
wasn't doing enough stuff I needed to start doing and I realized a lot of times it's the things that
I am doing that I shouldn't be doing. It's the extra stuff, you know, that I just need to cut
out. What do I need to cut out? So yeah, Porter, let's go through that. What's the first thing
that comes to your mind when I ask you like of all the people that you know that are successful,
that you've talked to on an accountability call, on a call before they sign up with Kyle,
what is the one, what is one thing to start that you would say most everyone has in common
out of curiosity? I would say the people that, that you're mentioning, I think they all have
this, this strong desire and like this faith that they're going to be able to make a lot of
money. Like they, they're pretty gung-ho about making it work and they're tired of the
circumstances they're in. Everyone I talk to, they're like, you know, I have this job, it's
not paying enough. I want the freedom. I'm not able to go on the trips. I'm not able to do the
things that I enjoy. And so that's like the number one leading motivator. I feel like for mostly
everyone is just having that, you know, that money. But I think the hardest thing from holding them
back is just their own heads that they're afraid to spend the money to make money. They're so in
their head that I have this money and I would rather go on a trip than, you know, invest in
myself sometimes, even though it's, it sounds stupid, but it's hard to, you know, go out and
start your own business. So Porter used a very strong and interesting word. He said the word
Whoever's read Think and Grow Rich know that that word has got to be used. I bet there's a statistic.
I bet that word's used so many hundreds of times. I'm going to ask Google how many times
is the word desire used in Think and Grow Rich? Somebody out there has, has looked this up.
Okay. No one has put, wow, hold on. I would, I would have thought that, oh, by the way, dude,
if you guys are complaining about Think and Grow Rich, you can literally go online, type in Think
and Grow Rich, and you can get the freaking PDF. So, okay, I'm not seeing any number, but I will
say that there, that thing has got to be used probably in the first chapter 50 times. Just so
everybody knows. The point being, though, to tap into what Porter said, guys, is that
I'm not going to give away Think and Grow Rich, but that's a very important word for this book.
But this is what I say, you know, I used to do all the calls when people join. I'm thinking,
I'm looking to see, Luke says it's exactly 47 times. How do you know that, bro? I trust that
that's the case, but how do you know that? I was pretty close. I said 50. Some of the people that
are on this call right now, I was the one that brought them into this group. And I will tell you
this, guys, is that you would think that the difference between the people that are crushing
it and the people that aren't is like something like they have sales experience, they have,
you know, I don't know, they're, they grew up a certain way, they, their parents are this,
their parents are not that, you know, whatever. But the truth is, guys, and I always used to say
this to people is that the people that succeed are always the ones that have the greatest reason
why they should succeed. And I would also say that you could use the word desire. And I used to always
say to people like, and this is the thing I would look for, I wouldn't get on these calls or look
through applications. And this is the same with business owners, by the way, but I wouldn't look
at it and go, Oh, have they had sales experience? Have they had technical experience? I would be
looking at someone's application. And I was looking to know, I was like, what the heck is
driving this person? What is their why? What is the reason why they want to do this? And the greater
the why, the stronger the why, the more confident I was, and the more flexible I was willing to be
to get them inside of the program, because I knew that they would have success. And on the contrary,
I didn't care if they were making dog crap for money, because I knew that they would start
making money if they had that strong why. And I always used to use this example. And I would say
this to people, I'd say, and I used to say this to business owners, this is a little one, a good
one liner or good little example you can use. When you guys are talking to your business owners,
you want to position it like you're almost interviewing them. Like you have a stack of
people lined up and you're trying to decide why you should work with them. This is, you got to
put yourself in a position of leverage. And I would always say to people, I would say,
if I asked you right now, Mr. Business Owner, or let's say I was talking to a potential student,
I would say, if I asked you, let's say we're at the top of a skyscraper and there's a skyscraper
across from us that's 20 yards like over into the other skyscraper. And I put a, let's imagine
there was a really strong two by four that wide going across into the other building. And I said
to you, I'll give you $10,000 to cross into that building and go across the wood. Important,
if I asked you that question, let's say we're on the 47th floor, we're in New York, we're in Vegas,
skyscraper to skyscraper, $10,000 across the two by four, two by four is going to be sturdy.
You're not going to shake off the two by four, but it's this thin. Would you take the deal?
Yeah. For $10,000?
Yeah. Dude, I don't know if I'd do it for $10,000.
I wouldn't. Heck no, dude. My life is way too valuable.
The downside is too valuable, dude. The downside is way too valuable. So then I would always ask,
I'd say, okay, let me change the scenario. Same exact situation, two by four, no $10,000,
but your daughter or your mom is in the other building and it's on fire.
And the only way that you're going to save them is if you get over there. Now, obviously that
probably wouldn't make sense in a real scenario because you're not going to be able to fly off
the building with them. But let's just say it solved the problem. If that was the case,
every single person, I imagine, unless you just hate your mom or hate your kid, which I
never really met anyone that hates their kid, but every single person, if it was $0 on the line,
but it was someone's life at risk that they really loved, they would take that deal.
They wouldn't even think twice about it. Right? Very true. Same situation, same risk, actually
there's no money on the line, but the Y is greater. That's the only difference. And guess what? You
are going to see people move mountains to get across there. So the point being, guys, is that
the people that are successful in this business, they have the greatest reason to be successful.
So here's a question I want to ask Porter. And by the way, if you guys have comments,
you guys have input, if you have whatever, go ahead and ask in the comments. I would love to
hear the feedback, but let's just say that you're somebody that's in the group or you just joined,
you've been in a while and you've kind of lost the reason. You've kind of lost the reason for
whatever the case, maybe it's just gone away. The desire has gone away. Maybe you've achieved
a certain level and you're not as motivated like you were. Like it's really exciting to get that
first deal, to get that first 10,000, for me to get that first million, for me to get, you know,
there were certain benchmarks that really got me excited. But let's say you've achieved them
and you don't have that strong Y anymore, or maybe your Y was something that was superficial
and it was like, I want to get that car, whatever, which by the way, isn't a very strong Y because
once you get it, then what, then what? How do you get, how in your opinion, do you acquire
that strong Y if you don't have it? That's hard because I think everyone has their own goals,
because I mean, you join this and maybe it's like, hey, if I get to 10,000, that's going to
supplement me enough. And like, you know, I'm not looking to make a hundred thousand a month.
It's hard to motivate that person. But what I would say is I think goals are so important,
especially like monthly goals, weekly goals, daily goals. I think if you're setting yourself
up for success and you're like, you're always checking things off the list. I know when you
set a goal out for eight months away, it's pretty hard to measure that. You need to set your long
goal and then your monthly goals and then, you know, your weekly and daily goals. But I would
just say like for me in that situation, when I've gotten stagnant and I feel like I haven't been as
focused, it's, I got to come back to the, I come back to the training. I start back over. I almost
rewatch the whole training again so that I can like catch this new fire. Cause every time I listen
to it, it's like, why am I not doing more of this? Whenever I land a deal and like, if I just do this
10 more times, I'm going to be at this point, you know? So it motivates me just to get that one more
deal. But I would say get one more deal. Just do, you don't need to get to 10 or like 20 more
thousand dollars. Just get one more deal and then one more deal. Like just keep, keep putting that
stuff in front of you. And that may work for some, but I do think goals for me is the only way that
I could ever stay motivated and think about what would my life be like if I stopped doing this?
And then that kind of motivates me to keep doing this, you know? Like I don't want to go back to
where I was. I want to keep growing. I don't want to lose my deals that I have. And so yeah, I would
say that would be like my motivating factor. I really like that a lot. I know that we're not
going to talk a ton about goals, but one thing that really helps, and we talked about this many
times and it's something that I did and I stopped doing and I regret that I stopped doing it, but
not just writing your goals down, but actually reading them and reading them at least twice a
day, one in the morning, one at night. It sounds stupid. It sounds cliche. It is, but it works.
And there's a reason why people do it. Okay. Another thing I want to mention, and this is
something that I think changes everything because some people are like not, let's say some people
aren't motivated. They're like, I don't know. I just don't really have that fire that I used to
have, or I never really had it, or I don't know how to get it. Guys, one thing that I know is that
if you get around people that are playing at a much higher level, you are by force going to
either be inspired or discouraged. And depending on the type of person that you are, some people
get discouraged. Some people get inspired. If you're a discouraged person by other people's success,
then that's probably indicative of your entire life. For me, when I get around people that are
freaking crushing it and just bawling out, it shows me how small I am, how insignificant my
quote unquote success has been. And I'm like, dude, I got to freaking pick this up.
You know what I mean? When I'm thinking I'm big shot because I make a couple hundred thousand
dollars a month, and then I'm around people that are making a million dollars a month,
and I realize that, dude, I'm just to pee on, dude. These people are dropping millions of
dollars into projects and into companies and starting new companies, sometimes quarterly
with multi-million. Dude, that gets me freaking fired up and shows me how small I'm playing.
And then when I sit there and I'm with my same group of friends or I'm with a group of friends
that make me comfortable, that are a bunch of freaking screw-offs that I've known forever that
aren't going anywhere, or maybe they are, but they're just not going anywhere right now,
it's really easy to get complacent thinking you're the big hog on the saddle. You know what I mean?
For you, Porter, you live in Parowan, which is a great spot, it's nice, whatever, but you got to
be careful for those of you that are in towns you grew up in or around. Parowan, the downside
with somewhere like that is there's just not a lot of people doing anything. You get married to
somebody from the hometown, no beef there, as long as they're not your cousin, which happens a lot as
well. Which could happen. That's a win, but that's the biggest win of their life. I married
someone not my cousin. It's like, no, dude, no. But it's this complacency of like, dude, you got
a little house and whatever. And so you've got to force yourself to get around people
who are playing at a bigger level. Some of you guys are in situations and in cities and in
environments where it's much easier. I know when I go to Dubai, I see five Lamborghinis a day.
I realize like, dude, I'm nothing. And by the way, I'm not sure if any of that money's real.
I think it's a lot of drug money. I'm not really sure how people make money in Dubai. But nonetheless,
I'm seeing Lamborghinis. They're coming from somewhere. And that inspires me. I'm seeing
the price of a villa being $6 million. Like these things, I see that going out for dinner,
you're spending $300 every single time. And these things inspire me. And some of you guys that live
in cities like that, it's easier to get inspired. Some of you guys that don't, like for example,
when I'm in Freetown, it's like, you don't have to have a ton of money to be the biggest dog in town.
So you have to be careful. And it's one of the things I think can really, really help you. So
as you guys are setting your goals, you're thinking about next year, you know, one of the goals that
I have so far is I want to network with, I think I put 10 people that are making a certain amount
of million dollars per year. Like their net worth is $10 million plus. And that's one of my goals.
And there's different ways that you can do that. And there's different things that you can do.
There's different strategies that you can have. And by all means, please, for the love,
do not start messaging people and asking to pick their brain.
Please lunch. Hey, you want to go to lunch? You want to grab lunch and I can pick your brain
like you're doing me a favor to buy me a $7 meal. Come on. You know what I mean? You got it. You
got to think about what can you do? This is the this isn't a by the way, this isn't a live on
networking, but you got to think about what what do the people that I want to connect with,
what do they all need? And what's something that I can add value to them by doing? What is something
that they all would need? Because there's some people, you guys know this, have really,
really strong networks with high network individuals. And there's certain people
that are in certain businesses that by nature they are in, they have just amazing networks.
There's actually a student in here that just joined. And he does, he goes and he buys
exotic cars. And he has a dealer license and all this stuff. And he has he's super young,
I'm going to try and get him on. He's stud, super young kid. I think he's 21 years old.
This dude has one of the strongest frickin networks that I know he knows that all the
big players in town. He knows he is like, I bet you his Rolodex is frickin ridiculous.
But it's because he's in a business that is attractive. And again, this is there's a reason
why he's in this business because that business is not recurring. But that's something that he
does. That's like his job, right? That's his business before he got into this, where he's
something that is attractive to people with money, right? There's people that do jet charters.
There's people that are in the luxury watch business. These are all things that a lot of
wealthy people are interested in. And I'm not saying by all means, don't do not go and
shiny object, I'm going to start flipping watches and this and that's not what I'm saying.
What I'm saying is think about how you can add value to these people, start building a strong
network and start frickin getting outside of your little teeny life. One of the reasons I like to
travel is when I do my mind is blown. My mind is expanded. I look at all its levels, man,
and you meet some most interesting people. Like I think I told you guys this story. I met
somebody from the royal family or whatever, the oil family in Saudi Arabia,
looking at their car collection, looking at frickin kids 18 years old driving a yellow
Canary yellow Lambo just for fun. He didn't buy, of course. That gets me pumped and I'm like,
okay, his parents are frickin ballin out. You know what I mean? So anyway, that's a really
important point, guys. What I would do this year as you guys are thinking about your goals
is revisit your why. Revisit your why. Sit down with yourself, turn off the distractions, sit down
with a pen and paper, maybe put on some light concentration music from Spotify and ask yourself
why, why, why? What do you want is the most important and hardest question to answer in
this life? Ask yourself, what do you want? For me in 2019, I said I want $100,000 per month
and I said, why? And then I answered it. And then I said, well, why do I want, why, why to that
answer? And why did that answer? And I just tried to dig like really far down. And by doing this,
I discovered some things about myself that like how I tick, what drives me, all these different
things. And it allowed me to just like, for every time things got tough, I could just remember,
okay, that's exactly why I'm doing it. So anyway, this isn't about a why. So that's really,
really interesting. So basically everyone that you've seen accountability, like in these
accountability calls, on these calls before they joined, they are, they have a strong desire,
but I would guarantee it's linked to a strong why. Is that fair to say? Yeah. Okay. What do
you think on the flip side is the commonality of losers, the commonality of the people that
get in the program and, you know, within a month, they stop doing it. Within a month,
they're distracted. Within a month, they're messaging me. Oh, I can't find the answer to
this. Or I can't, my ads, they're just not cranking. It's like, dude, what'd you expect
it just to work perfect the first time? It's like, bro, I'm sitting over at 1.5 million,
like just relax, it's going to come through. And they want to blame everything else, every other
situation under the freaking stars, except for themselves. What is that the commonality of the
losers, bro? I would say they, I don't know what the right word for that is, but they don't,
they definitely don't take enough, they definitely don't take enough risks. They definitely don't
work as hard because I think a lot of people get in this group and they don't find the city within
the first couple of days. And they kind of are like, dude, there's just no cities. Like it's too
saturated. And they've tried, they've tried one niche, they haven't think outside the box. Like
everyone's thinking the exact same thing. And if you can't find a city, you guys start thinking a
little differently to find a city. And so I would say a lot of it's in your own head and it's like
a dumb answer, but it's so true. It's like, you guys are just so afraid to work hard almost. Like
you're afraid to give this everything you have and make this the only thing that's going to make
you money. Like you can do have part-time jobs, but you got to treat it as if this is your only
thing. And when you do that, you really start taking more seriously. Like when I was like,
okay, I'm going to make this work no matter what. And I don't care how long it takes me. I got to
deal with in the first month, you know, but it was just my mindset of like being fearless enough to
be like, Hey, I'm just going to spend the money. Like, I know I don't have an excess amount of
money. Like I'm not just going to throw it against the wall, but like, it's okay. Like if I lose a
little bit of money, it's fine. And when I had that mindset, I, you start to just piggyback off
these deals that you get. Yeah, I agree. I think another thing I want to mention really, really
quick is the people that struggle the most, they have, they have this mindset. I'm going to call
it the, if it works mindset. Okay. That's a, if this works or if this thing happens, then blah,
blah, blah. So, you know, if I'm at a thousand, if I'm at my first deal within 30 days, then I'm
going to keep doing this. You know, if this thing happens by the end, it's like this, if it's like,
no, no, no, no, no, no. If you would just change that guys, the moment that I change this, and I,
I'm trying to not sound like Mr. Frickin rah rah, because I promise you, when I get on Instagram,
when I see fricking YouTube videos and every person is now somehow a guru motivational speaker.
Have you noticed that by the way, just as a side brand real quick? Definitely feel like there's a
lot more in the last couple of years. And I want to just publicly apologize if I ever came across
like that, which I know I did. I really hope at the time I wasn't trying to be that person. I was
just passionate because I literally, last night, even some of these people that have a lot of
followers, like I was listening to, oh, what's his name, dude? Okay. It was, I found this,
I found this podcast. I was looking at my area, St. George, Utah, and there's this podcast
interviewing like, basically it's a hyper-focused podcast on St. George, Utah. And it's like,
because it's only focusing on St. George, Utah, their pool to pull from of interviewing of guests
is very small. And I'm looking and I know, I recognize some of the people and I'm like,
why the hell are we interviewing the fricking secretary of the local real estate office?
Like, let's have some standards. And I don't know who, I think it was this guy,
this other guy, I have the best account for you guys to follow. He just makes fun of influencers.
And I promise you, if he made fun of me, I would probably just share it because there's
videos he could make fun of me. But he's like, dude, you don't need a podcast, spoiler alert,
you don't need a podcast, you don't need a podcast. It's just annoying at this point. Okay.
It's very annoying. So I just wanted to throw that in there. Guys, we're not trying to be on
here thinking that we're fricking bee's knees, hot crap. We know everything. Dude, we're just
trying to figure this out like you guys are, but we have learned a few things. We've observed a
couple things. So I just, I'm trying to just let you know that I know how cringe some of the stuff
I probably have said. I'm just trying to be the fricking messenger. Shout out to Kanye, right?
He's the messenger. He's the espresso, as he says. But dude, in 2019, this is from experience,
not from me reading a book. 2019, I had my back up against the wall, $60,000 in debt,
thinking about quitting, thinking about going to be a salesperson, which by the way, no shame on
being a salesperson. But the reason why I had shame around it is because I was thinking about
quitting. That's really what it was. I was thinking about quitting. And I sat down with myself,
yellow notepad. You guys know the story. What do you want? Just shared it. And I changed my
mentality because I realized at that moment, this was the model. I had the right model.
I just needed to figure a few things out. And up until then, although I was doing it,
I still had one foot out, one eye kind of on the streets. And I was never all in. I was never
faithful. Let's just use an analogy of being faithful in a relationship. I was cheating on
my main thing. I had my eye in the streets, and I was always looking for that better thing.
And it made it so I could never succeed. I could never go all in. And the only thing that had to
happen is I had to just look at it and go, this is the right model. I just got to figure this out.
And I changed from, I remember, I got this new energy. I got this new excitement. I had this new
energy to like, this is it. I just have to do it long enough. And I have to be willing for this to
take forever. I have to be willing for me to just realize I'm going to be doing this forever,
period. And as soon as I did that, guys, everything changed. The way that I approached
my day changed. The way that I approached doing due diligence. I no longer felt like it was this
thing I was trying to check out the box. I was like, no, I got to master due diligence.
I started looking at my ads, and instead of being annoyed, I was like, I want to master. I want to
become so good at ads. I want to get a little bit better, a little bit better. I want to be able to
do them in five minutes and 31 seconds, which I used to be able to do when we were doing the
smart campaigns. And every fast of the business, I became obsessed with. And you guys know when
you've met someone or see somebody that's obsessed with whatever they do, and it's just contagious.
I just changed the mentality to instead of, I'm going to do it for a year. I'm going to do it for
three months. I'm going to do it whatever, until I'm good. I'm doing this until it works.
I just knew deep down this is the right model. And here's the advantage you guys have that I didn't.
I didn't know anyone that was doing $100,000 a month. I didn't know anyone that was doing
$30,000 a month. I saw people posting checks, but I promise you that they were lying. You know when
you can tell someone's lying when they say it and it's like, bro, how much you really making, right?
People in here making freaking $70 million a second these days, according to Instagram,
right? They're full of crap. I didn't have anyone. I didn't have Ryan Dalton making $87,000. It started
two years ago to be like, yo, if Ryan did it with a full-time job, kids and dog and jujitsu and all
this stuff, I can do it. I didn't have that, but I just knew deep down I could do it. But as soon as
I changed that, dude, everything freaking changed. I started just approaching the day different. I
started attacking the day different. I started getting up with a new zeal. I started staying up
late. I cut the Netflix during the week. Dude, everything changed, dude. All the other stuff
fell out, dude. I didn't care. I wasn't looking at other businesses. I wasn't ready to start other
businesses. That was all I had to change. That mindset shift was huge for me, okay?
Real quick, I want to talk about this as well. What do you think? This could be from people you've
talked to, people you've interacted with, but I think that one of the issues nowadays is that we
try to add all these extra things. We try to add... I got to do... And this is an extreme example. I'm
not trying to steal from Formosy or any of these guys, but they do a really good job making fun of
it. The cold plunge and this freaking one-hour routine and the meditation and the affirmations
and all this different stuff. I think it was a really fresh idea when Formosy was like,
you could also just wake up and walk into your office and work. That also works. Anyway, by the
way, I got nothing against cold plunge. I actually think it's rad. I just don't think you need to
post about it. That's it, okay? For the record, Ford, I know you got a cold plunger, but don't
be hiding that from anybody. Dude, consistently, dude. It's good for the joints. Dude, I would do
that. I'm all for the cold plunge. The point is, don't think that you need to do cold plungers to
make $10,000 a month, $50,000 a month. What I want to talk about really quick are what are some of
the things that you see people, they have a misconception about, what are some of the things
that people think they need to be doing that are just distractions, right? That's another thing
that I went... The years that I've really grown, dude, are the years where I sit there and I think,
what can I eliminate? That was another huge thing for me. I know we're talking about the
commonalities of winners, but I'm going to put myself in that. I've got to observe myself,
retrospectively, looking at that. One of the things that I did, and I've shared this before,
is I cut all the BS. I eliminated, I simplified, I simplified, I simplified.
I'm going to share some of the things that I simplified, but what do you think, Porter,
are some of the things that people, from what you've seen, need to simplify in their life,
need to get rid of to have the success to become a winner? Guys, it's ridiculous to know. If you're
watching this call right now, and you know that Porter's at $9,400 a month, and he's also farming
full-time, and you're not at five, you're not at one, you don't have a deal, and you've been
doing this for anywhere close to the same amount of time, that should really piss you off. It should
inspire you, and it should piss you off. No way, dude. No way I'm letting Porter do this, and I'm
not. You know what I mean? I used to do this about people as well, dude. It's good to have people on
your radar. Anyway, Porter, what do you think are some of the things that people need to cut out
that they're doing that they shouldn't be doing? Because we always talk about what you should add,
routine, 10 pages of a book, gallon of water, cold plunge, this pill, that pill, freaking
grounding, sun on the face, dude, watching Liver King, listening to Joe Rogan, like all the freaking
cliche stuff that all of us do, but some of us think that it's necessary to have success.
What are some of the things we need to cut? Again, observing other people. We're not being
influencers here. We're not being Tony Robbins here. We're just observing. We're just country
folk that are observing. Dude, I don't know if it was just me, and I guarantee if I say this,
if this is you, comment below, but how many times do you think you have to have this mile-long list
the next day? I would sit down and I would write and I would write down the most small things that
would not do anything to get me closer to moving the needle. It would be like doing due diligence
or like, I mean, that was, but like at the time I was doing so much due diligence that I wasn't
acting. I wasn't actually taking initiative. So I think simplify your list. And if you do a list,
if you do it to do list, pick three things or pick big things that you're going to be able to
do and just do them because you're going to get them done a lot faster. I would say,
eliminate social media. Like during your work, when you're working, I found that I look at my
phone a lot when I'm on my computer, I'll have my phone sitting and I'll be on computer. And if I
don't like set a timer or something to try to work for a certain amount of time. And I know
Hermosa does that. And he says, every time you get distracted, if you pause your timer,
you'll actually realize that you can do the same task in half as much time. And I'm like,
so the other day I was doing, I was setting up a campaign and I was kind of dreading it because I,
sometimes I have to go through, look at the training, you know, go back and forth.
And I really sat down and just did it. And it literally took me 15 minutes. And for whatever
reason, I thought it was going to take me an hour or whatever. It was 15 minutes and I got so much
done. And it just took getting started for me to realize like, what am I doing? Like this is,
this is so simple, but I had to create, I create these long lists. So I think that I need to start
checking things off. And naturally you want to go after the smallest things possible because it
makes you feel good. It's like, make your bed. It's like, go to the gym. It's like, read, read
a book. And those are things that are pretty easy to do and you can check it off, but they're not
really getting you closer to your goals. So I would say for me, and I don't know most of you,
probably simplify your list, get rid of social media and just realize that it doesn't take you
as long as you think to get stuff done. That's a really, that's a really strong point.
And by the way, as you said that, Sean said, my biggest waste of time was doom scrolling. I deleted
TikTok and Instagram at seven AM this morning. Yes, yes, yes. And yes, guys, one of the things
that I do and I, I, I'm not perfect at this. And sometimes I catch myself like going a few days
and realizing, oh my gosh, I wasted a bunch of time. Even at, even where I'm at, I still catch
myself doing this. But one thing that I think is very important is to get, just get social media
off your phone, get it off your phone, turn it on to post, delete it, and then give yourself a
certain time every day where you can go and you can feel, you can not feel guilty by just scrolling
and just kind of unwinding if you want. Okay. But literally you got to set a 15 minute timer.
So what I try to do again, try, because I didn't even do this yesterday admittedly, but I did a
pretty good job last week is I delete it. It's deleted all day. And then I have this little time
timeline where I want to get on and post. I don't even write my post on Instagram.
I write my post in the notes app. And I also think of which stories I want to share
on my thing. So then what I do is I download Instagram, I copy and paste, I put the picture
in, I paste the, the, the, whatever the body of the text. And then I put the location, boom,
I post it. I go share a few stories. And within 20 minutes, I can have a nice post, all my stories.
And then guys, if I just delete it right after, cause I know some of you guys, it's so tempting
to sit there and go, who liked it? I wonder how cool they think I am. Like, let's be honest,
we've all done it, dude. Who's looking at my story? You don't pour it on admit you haven't done that
last week, dude. We all, we all, we're all guilty of it. Stupid dude. Like that gets us anywhere in
life, but we all do it. Right. And you're just sitting there and you're waiting for a little
freaking comment. And it's like, dude, you know, it's interesting. Just delete it. And then you go
in to make your post the next day, make your post, and then give yourself an extra five minutes to
read the comments and be like, Oh, I looked at who liked it in 15 seconds. I replied to the one
comment I got. Thanks mom. And that's it. And I just saved myself, not only the time of scrolling,
but the distraction of every single time. Oh, wonder who texts me. I wonder if they're following
me back. It's like, dude, freaking come on guys. Okay. I'm speaking to myself. So true.
It's freaking happened. By the way, Sean said I give props to TikTok because it's how I found
the program. I just don't need it now. Yeah. A hundred percent. But by the way, when you do your
15 minutes, if you guys assume to do 15 minutes a day as of consuming, there's different levels of
it. Like there's stuff you can add value. I like to go and like listen to Theo Vaughn cause he's
freaking hilarious. Um, that's to me, that's value. That's entertainment. I'll take that over
Netflix. But also I think there's some interesting stuff like you can find on some of these
platforms and you don't just sit there and like consume or, you know, inspiring, interesting
educational. So there's different levels, but guys, let me just share this. Um, in 2020,
when I scaled up to a hundred thousand dollars a month, let me share some of the things I did.
Okay. Is social media. I basically just got rid of it. Okay. Like I don't even, I don't even know
if I posted. I'm sure I did, but I don't think I posted much. I don't think I consume much. I was
just tired of being broke. I got rid of that for the most part. Um, but more than that guys,
I got rid of a bunch of the things that you, they're, they're the silent killers.
Let me give you an example. Lunches with your, but with your business buds. Okay. I was because if
you guys work in an office, it's really easy to be like, dude, let's go meet for lunch, blah, blah,
blah. And guys, you, it takes two hours to meet for lunch. Like it just does. You got to drive
there. That's 10 minutes, 15 minutes, depending on where you live. You're going to order your food.
You're going to want to talk. It's going to be about an hour. Then you're going to do another
15, 20 minutes, get back to the office. And of course you got to grab you a soda, right? Pour
a little swig ski on the way back. There's another 10, 15 minutes. Then when you get in the office,
you got to chat, right? Jessica's at the front. She's got to ask me a question where I'm asking
her when she's going to Italy, dude, I'm two hours of my day to go and get lunch with somebody.
So in 2020, it helped that there was nowhere open, of course, at the beginning of the year,
because, you know, what restaurants were closed, there's only takeout. But even after things
started opening up, I just didn't do it. Okay. So I got rid of the BS lunches. Number two is I got
rid of all the hobbies. And I'm not saying that you need to do this and be fanatical forever,
but if you guys are not where you want to be, if you guys are not free or, and especially if you
haven't gotten your first deal, guys there that you can have a season of your life where you just
go locked in. You kind of do that. Like people call it monk mode or they go away in the wilderness
for a while. But if you just got into this program, you don't have a deal. I highly,
highly, highly recommend that you guys eliminate as much as possible. Not that it needs to be
forever, but for a season of my life, I did not do golf. I did not do pickleball. I did not do
fricking basketball. Only thing I did is I went to the gym because that helped me with my business.
But I got rid of everything else. Okay. Another thing I got rid of is I got rid of watching
Netflix. Okay. I, by the way, I got rid of watching Netflix during the week, Monday,
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday night, Saturday night, I can watch it. And boy,
did I watch, I blew through seasons, dude. I was times I woke up, I was like, dude, it's 4 30 AM,
dude. Eyes wired like I had taken, you know, five packs of Marl bros. I had a Zen in each
little pouch, dude, watch it. Just, I would hit seasons, bro. But at least it was,
it was very channel. Okay. Nothing during the week. Nothing's messing with my week. Okay.
Further than that, I kept eliminating. I got rid of all the extra services. I was done with SEO.
I was done with fricking social media management. I got rid of all of that.
Then I got rid of all my extra niches and I dialed in on one niche and I'm like,
I'm going to go one niche and then I'm going to sell these other websites that I,
that are generating leads. I got rid of all of my deal structures, paper lead gone, commission
gone. It was never really there anyway. Only flat fee. I got rid of all my pricing options,
a thousand dollars plus. I got rid of all my contract options. It's one six months at the
minimum. That's it. Boom. And guys, I had such a simple life. I would wake up,
gym was closed. Luckily my buddy, about a block away invited me. 7 a.m. I'd be at his gym.
We would work out for one hour. I would come back and get to work. I would work. I'd have
some lunch midday. I'd work some more. I'd be at the kids two, three hours. They'd go to bed.
I'd come back up to the office and that's it. And guys, in my work, like Porter said,
it wasn't fricking stupid stuff. Checking boxes. It was literally make calls, find new areas,
hook new business owners, close deals. Like that's what I focused on and everything else,
find someone to do it. And what do you know from 2019 December, eight to 10,000 bucks a month,
July, 2020, a hundred thousand dollars a month. No coincidence.
Simplicity is more simple and more. Yeah. Less is more. More is less. 100%
Gina says, I'm totally guilty of using Instagram, especially as a distraction,
beating myself up right now, along with you right now. It's such a waste of time. I get so much done
when I had my phone. Yeah. And guys, I think if you're intentional about it, like give yourself
some time, maybe if it's 30 minutes at night, say, Hey, every night when everything's done,
I plan my day. I would recommend not doing it in bed, but like, I'm going to give myself 30
minutes. Maybe sip on your fricking nightly lemon and ginger tea with a little drop of Manuka honey.
That'll put you to sleep. That'll put you on your behind. While you're doing that,
you give yourself 30 minutes, 15 Instagram, 15 TikTok, and then delete the apps. Okay.
And I promise you when you wake up and you don't do fricking check your phone on who liked my post,
you're going to get a lot more done, but Gina, don't beat yourself up. We all do it. I fricking
did it yesterday. It's just one of those things we've got to remind ourselves. Jason says,
setting up a separate device for social media and removing them entirely from the device I
carry all day and the process that I speak. I love that. You know, when I shared this last thing
in 2022, I did this, this worked for a period of time. I don't know why I stopped doing it.
Maybe I should do it. And this isn't something that's necessary, but I actually went and got
a completely separate phone, separate number, everything. I actually got this from dad because
he does it too, or he was getting a bunch of calls from his church stuff. But I had this little
fricking tiny, I had another, it was a smartphone, but it was the little tiny one and it was a
different number and it had nothing on it and no one had my number. That's it. The only one that
had my number. I didn't even have it. You didn't have my number. My wife had my number in case
there was emergency. I think, I think, I think my dad and mom had my number. I think there was like
three people that had my number and guess what? That was the phone I used during the day. So I
knew that there was no emergencies happening, but I was, I was locked in, baby. I was locked in.
So again, that's an extreme example. If you, you can do that, but you don't need to do that. You
can also just not look at your phone. You can also just fricking turn it off. And that's it. And if
you have a spouse or a significant other that doesn't understand that you need to have a serious
talk, cause it's like, dude, we're making money during the day and then I'm going to be with you
at night. Okay. That's it. So guys, I hope you guys are excited as I am about 20 fricking 25.
We have another year ahead of us. We have, we have, we can, we can set new goals. We can go
achieve new things. This can be the year and you guys, your whole life can change in a year. You,
you can go from being somebody that's just getting by, having to calculate every time you take a
flight to literally owning the car of your dreams or owning an apartment complex that makes you
a certain amount of money. You guys, these are like, there's so much possibility and it's
fricking insane how much your life can change in one year. We have a new year ahead of us.
Let's not end this year. Just take our foot off the gas, but let's, let's, let's go strong and
let's get our goals done now. Let's not wait till January 31st or December 31st to have our goals.
I hope you guys are pumped. I hope you're excited. We have things that are making this
easier. We have people to show us Ryan Dalton, myself, you know, Mike V, some of these big
players that are making a lot of money that we can look to as examples, look at them for inspiration,
look at them for wisdom, look at them for what to do, what not to do. And just go and eliminate
everything and let's go and fricking do it. By the way, we also have tools that are helping us
rank and run engine, which again, I'll just quickly, if you guys do not and have not already
messaged me for a discount code, if you haven't used one of those already, there's a new code
that Ryan set up. That, that can get so much more work done in such a shorter period of time,
just with the due diligence feature alone. So we have all these things, all these examples,
all this support. We're going to be coming out with a new version of the training that's going
to help us even more with accountability and everything else. A lot of exciting stuff. This
is the greatest business model on the fricking internet, guys. Let's see. Jason says, so how
many carriers these days give away a free phone with new lines and lines are cheap to add?
That's so true, dude. It's actually really true as you can easily do that. Freedom of time.
Leanne says the Opal app blocks anything you want for whatever hours you choose. That's dope.
That's a good little hack ski. Thanks, Leanne. I like that Opal. Also, if you guys don't already
do that, what's this app that I've had on my desktop for however long the,
hold on, I'll tell you exactly what it is. It's called the
the News Feed Eradicator. News Feed Eradicator. I can't even, like if I go to Facebook because
I have to be on Facebook, I can't see my timeline. It gives me some cheesy quote.
I can't see anything. I'm not scrolling because you guys know how easy it is to get it. And by
the way, Jason just said, oh yeah, brick too. By the way, if RIP, if RIP can use a brick phone,
Porter? With a flip phone, dude? You can do a flip phone and your stuff is bad freaking RIP,
you can use a flip phone. Dude, a flip phone's a vibe, dude. I'm going to go back to a Blackberry
at the very minimum. But yeah, Luke says plus one for the News Feed Eradicator. Guys, appreciate
you hopping on. Porter, thanks for hopping on. Sharing some nuggets. Hopefully we didn't come
across a bunch of freaking guru Tony Robbins wannabes. We're just a bunch of, like I said,
country boys with some moderate to crappy education that just are trying to be simple,
trying to make money, trying to make a little dent in this world. And hopefully you guys got
some value from this. So guys, appreciate you being on. Porter, thanks for being on.
We'll see you guys next time. Yeah.