Okay guys welcome to the call Monday August 26th. Again we apologize for a
little bit of a delay. We got a little bit of a confusion with the link so
we'll make sure that doesn't happen next week but I want to let you guys know
first and foremost the only thing that we require on this call is that if what
what we do at the end of every one of these calls and this is your first one
is we're going to take all the information that we give you guys and we
are going to put it into a digital resource that looks pretty that's
condensed and then anybody that stays on this call with their camera on till the
end we're gonna take a screenshot and then we're gonna send you guys this
digital resource and the reason why is it because we're like power hungry it's
because we want to make sure that people are paying attention and they're sitting
there or you could be driving too but we want to make sure that you guys are
actually the ones that are are here for the right reason and so in the past
we've had people jump on these lives and all they're they're just here to consume
and take and take and take and so I've said this before but I would rather four
people be on this live I'd rather one person be on this live that really wants
to take action than have a hundred people that do not and so that's all
that we ask keep your camera on we understand you got to be moving maybe
you've got to be doing this or that or the rest that's fine at the end of this
live we will take a screenshot sent in send you that digital resource so then
you don't have to take sit here and take notes on everything that I give you
you can that'll come as a digital resource what I would rather you guys do
is take notes on the things that come to your mind so I'm gonna say things today
that are gonna give you ideas they're gonna remind you to reach out to this
person or oh that person has this business or I should do this those are
the things I want you to take notes on because all the information I'm gonna
share today I am going to be sending you as long as you just stay on this call
and keep your camera on but guys welcome again once again to the call my
goal for well let me just say this first I I I don't believe you guys should
listen or believe anything that I say and that's not like some catchy phrase
whatever but I truly anything that I share with you I want you to ask
yourself why should I listen to this guy and then I want you to go and test it I
don't ever want you just to take my word because if you take my word you're
gonna take the next guy and the next gal and and that's a scary place to be
because 99% of people are full of crap okay all right so um but for those that
don't know me I've been doing this eight years made in 2020 made my first
million dollars doing this and that's not from selling a coaching program
that's literally from building simple websites ranking them on Google and
renting them out and that's that my business was built brick by brick it was
$500 a month thousand dollar a month $500 a month $2,000 a month $2,500
thousand dollar all that first thousand dollar grew to five thousand and it was
literally just brick by brick by brick by brick and the difference between
barely scraping by and getting to a hundred thousand dollars a month in
July of 2020 and never looking back is that I figured out a few key things that
made all the difference in the world and some of you guys on this call have been
thinking about this business model or doing this business model for years or
months or weeks some of you guys have known about this business model for over
ten years and some of you guys have been in other programs and you just can't
have this you haven't had the success that you want and I feel your pain and
that's why I'm doing these calls okay so I so wish that when I was trying to
scale that I would have had somebody that had done what I wanted to do and
what I wanted to do was make a hundred thousand dollars in a month doing this
and nobody that I knew and to this day I still do not know anybody else besides
myself that has done a hundred thousand dollars per month doing this now I know
some people have messaged me oh this guy in this country and this guy in this
state but personally I do not know anybody else that has made a hundred
thousand dollars per month doing this business model and so for me this is what
I wish I had okay what I want to mention really quick before I forget is and I'm
gonna have either Aaron or Jason share this we actually decided to start a
podcast based based on and completely around digital real estate all things
it's it's very niche it's very nuanced it's very in the weeds it's complete
it's not just taking lives and putting it on a podcast these are separate
episodes these are separate topics this is taking my my time to do this but we
just launched a podcast on Spotify it's on Apple podcast as well so Aaron or
Jason here shortly if you don't maybe I can do it really quick hold on I don't
know if you guys have I'm gonna drop it in the comments so that you guys can
check out the first episode and I would love to get your feedback on this
digital real estate you can type in digital real estate and you'll be able
to find it digital real estate Nick would so let me go ahead and share this
really quick and I'll put it in the comments hold on in the chat I can post
the link if you want I got it there's the Spotify Jason if you want to go
ahead and grab the Apple one that's fine too but yeah there's the podcast again
these are these are episodes specifically for the podcast this first
one is is my story if you guys haven't heard my story already if you have you
guys can skip through part of it but it's a 34 minute episode it's my story
what is digital real estate and we actually have another episode already
filmed that we're gonna be dropping this week and it's gonna be a weekly show so
go ahead if you would like again no pressure you could subscribe to that and
check that out as well that's a nice format to listen to at the gym while
you're driving whatever okay so my goal guys by the end of this call is that
you're gonna have multiple ways that you can use to generate literally
unlimited niche ideas okay niche ideas until you're blue in the face and it's
funny because I like how Aaron started he's like we're gonna answer the
question once and for all is is rank-and-ret saturated right and the I
also hope by the end of this call I don't even have to talk about that I
have made like three four videos on saturation because everyone's number one
question is is this model saturated and I promise you I'm probably gonna do a
podcast episode called the saturation of rank-and-ret because everyone it's like
once we get into something we always want to know am I too late to the game
and so I'm not gonna answer that question right now I'm gonna let you
guys answer that question but just based on what you're gonna hear from me today
you're gonna be able to answer that question okay there is so there's so
many ways there's so many niches out there it's extremely exciting a couple
guys weren't on I literally pulled this out of my desk and this is one of the
methods we're gonna talk about today but I pulled this out this little flyer out
of my desk that came to my mailbox like two years ago and I was like yeah and I
was like that's a really interesting niche and somebody on the call it was
one of my students I believe was like yeah I actually make money in this
niche it's I think the term would be like sheds or portable sheds and the
average ticket price is five thousand dollars and so that was literally just
like an example and I'm gonna I think Francesca's actually built out a site
for this already or we're doing the the the ads for right now but there are so
many niches out there guys it's insane so let's get into this guys also what I
would like you to do is if you have a specific niche in mind I would like you
drop it in the comments and I'm gonna try and save about 15 minutes to do Q&A
and as part of that Q&A I want to be able to let you guys know my opinion on
certain niches and I'll tell you guys if I have personally done it or if it's
just my opinion because I have done a lot of niches but if I haven't I'll give
you my opinion on why I think it would be or wouldn't be a good niche okay okay
so guys here's the plan for today's call number one I'm gonna talk to you guys
about why you should stick to boring niches until your bills are paid number
two why I think you should let other people pay for you to test niches then
we're gonna talk about different methods I've got one two three four five six
seven eight nine I've got ten different methods and that there are so many more
than that but I'm just gonna give you ten ideas of places you can use to go
and find niches that's not ten niches that's ten different places you can
look for niche ideas so there should never be a shortage of ideas for
niches okay so starting off by the way Aaron Jason I'm gonna let you guys be my
eyes and ears if you guys see something that you think is relevant to what I'm
saying cut me off and just unmute yourself and just say hey Nick I want to
you know ask this question because it's pertinent to what you're saying right
now please let me know okay but if not guys start dropping your questions start
dropping your niches inside the comments and let's get going so number one guys
three weeks ago four weeks ago I talked about going vertical versus going broad
you know you know basically going into multiple different niches versus going
into one niche and how I've done both I started off by going into multiple
niches and then I honed into just one and then I told you guys at the end what
I would do if I was starting today which is neither it's a kind of a combination
of both and if you guys didn't get that training sometimes in the free group
we're giving away like you know the stack of trainings so keep an eye out
for that kind of stuff by the way hold on okay I thought that was somebody
unmuting one of my guys okay so um but guys what I mentioned that training the
reason I bring that up is I spent the first I would say well it was it was up
until 2019 I just was testing niches I was literally just testing niches I was
trying anything and everything if I if I talked to somebody I would write it down
and I was like let me try that niche and if I saw you know a business card at the
gym or an advertisement at the gym I would write it down and I would test it
and guys I I probably tried I don't even know man 20 20 to 30 different niches
maybe more and I was making eight to ten thousand dollars a month okay and it
wasn't until the beginning of 2020 when I just had this realization that I was so
spread out I was so my attention was so spread thin that I needed to just focus
and my brain doesn't work like that I I thought you know well Elon Musk has three
companies he's got Solar City he's got Tesla he's got SpaceX I could have a
couple different companies and it's like no I'm not the same as Elon Musk I'm
freaking just as average as can be and I got to stick to one thing so unless
you're Elon Musk my advice to you is simplify get very very simple get very
focused on one thing and I've heard so many different people say this again and
again and again I've heard Alex Hermosy say this I've heard one of Alex Hermosy's
somebody that is a friend of Alex Hermosy that I know I just did this
podcast with this guy in Dubai this is a couple weeks ago and his name is Dan
Henry and this guy he's a 10 million plus type of a guy he's he's a smart
dude he's he's kind of in this space to some extent not in rank and rep but he's
in online marketing and he same thing happened to him he he started off he was
crushing it and doing one thing he was selling one thing and he said he scaled
up to two hundred and fifty thousand dollars per month and then what he did
is he in his head he's like well I'm gonna go add another offer and another
offer and at one point he had 13 different products that he was selling 13
he went from one to 13 and his revenue went from two hundred and fifty
thousand dollars per month to seventy thousand dollars per month and I guess
he joined this guy named Sam Ovens mastermind and Sam Ovens basically told
him he's like get rid of twelve of them keep one or maybe at fourteen and said
he said keep one and he got rid of he got rid of everything except for one
offer and he scaled up to five hundred thousand dollars per month so guys my
number one thing I want to tell you guys is as we're gonna get in we're gonna
talk about a bunch of different niches it's gonna be exciting it's gonna be
fun it's gonna stimulate the brain juices my advice to you is stick with a
couple niches and stick with the boring niches until your bills are paid okay I
would personally recommend until you've gotten one to three deals I would I would
stay air on the side of three do not go into multiple niches stay in pick a
boring niche okay a boring it's a concrete a tree surface a fencing a
spray foam insulation a masonry you guys know all these gutter installation
all these ones that we always talk artificial grass pick one of those go
get your first one two and three deals that's my number one piece of advice
okay don't go build and I know I know I'm contradicting what you guys are
hearing in other groups other groups are telling you to build ten other groups
are telling you to go build ten different sites in ten different cities
and ten different niches and I'm telling you that's a bunch of malarkey
and and most the time the people that want you to build more websites are the
people that benefit from you building more websites if I sell website building
material aka hosting if I sell a white labeled web web builder if I sell
tracking numbers if I sell images if I sell done-for-you services of course I
want you guys to build more websites but I'm here to tell you guys I think
that's very stupid I don't think you need to build more websites I think you
need to be smart about the websites that you build and instead of having a
shotgun approach I want you to have a sniper approach and I want you to know
that when you build a website you have a client and the clients paying for that
website and you can just knock them out and you know you have one in the bag
before you start building the website so again this comes back to why I said this
at the beginning don't just listen to what I'm saying think about it and I
want you to the person that's telling you to build 10 websites I want you to
ask them how much money they're making in this business not from selling their
program not from selling their done-for-you services or their web
hosting or this and that the rest I want you I want you to ask them how much
they're making from doing the actual business before you take their advice
okay because most these people are like the ones in the California gold rush
that sold the picks and the shovels but they don't they're not actually making
money from mining gold so for me I made my first however many million dollars
mining the actual gold and then I saw an opportunity that people would
actually pay for my knowledge because I changed the way this was done and then I
started selling the picks the shovels aka the program so that said guys number
one stick to boring until your bills are paid if your bills are ten thousand
dollars a month go and make sure you're making ten thousand dollars net before
you even think about going into funny niches or you know what you call
obscure niches that's number one okay number two I don't think well this is my
opinion is when in 2020 when I decided and my goal in 2020 is I was like all
right I'm gonna become very focused I'm gonna go into one niche and that was
tree service right that was the only niche I the only niche I dealt with in
2020 in 2020 was tree service now because I had been in these other
programs and I'd build all these these websites that didn't make me money but
that were whatever I had a handful of niches a handful of websites in other
niches so I had a concrete site I had a this side I had a that side I had a
towing site but that's because they were already ranking they were already
getting leads and I was like I'm gonna sell those but I'm gonna focus on tree
service so overwhelmingly most of my I would say 90% of the deals that I did
inside of the year 2020 were in tree service and if it wasn't inside tree
service it was because I already had a website ranking and generating leads
that I built three years before two years before that I probably wouldn't
have even done but I'd been working on it for so long that it was getting leads
so guys if you're new to this pick a niche pick a freaking niche and stick to
it now for those of you that are like oh my gosh concrete saturated yeah you're
gonna start seeing more lead generators than you were two years ago because
we've been talking about concrete for years but you know what's funny is if
you guys aren't following me on YouTube or subscribe to me on YouTube you don't
have to but if you want to we also put out different content and I have this
new series it's gonna be an 8 to 10 part series and I'm literally going me and
Francesca she is going from A to Z on closing a new deal okay A to Z from idea
to deal in the bag to credit card collected and we're gonna do this eight
parts we did part one in fact Aaron or Jason one of you guys go on to YouTube
please get that first video part one and share it in the chat we did part one and
the reason I'm bringing this up is because the guess what niche we're gonna
use freaking concrete concrete and she came to me with this niche and she's
like hey I have this city in this niche in concrete now and I literally Aaron
can testify to this I was like no no there's no way there's no way that this
is that because if you guys once you guys find out the city you're gonna be
like there's no way that's that's that's available there's no way because it's a
well-known city sure enough looked at the CPC it's less than three dollars or
something crazy like that the search volumes over 120 she did the research on
the competition it's low yes there's a couple lead generators in there but
nothing that's that's scaring us off so I want you guys to know that number one
again and there's a reason I'm sticking on this point you guys should not be
going into weird stuff until you guys are paying your bills okay so your first
one to three stick and do one boring niche after you get one to three deals I
think you could you could probably go to like two or three total niches but I
would still stick to boring or tried-and-true niches until your bills
are paid okay and then what you're probably gonna find out this will
happen with me is once you have you know $10,000 a month coming in with tree
service concrete spray foam you're gonna go why would I why would I change what's
working you know that saying if it ain't broke don't fix it that's kind of what
it was for me I was like dude I already know this niche I already know what the
good search terms are I already know that the big companies in this you know
in this space I already know the gossip guys there is gossip on the interwebs
inside of these different niches and I was so familiar with some of these
niches I could call a business owner up and I could I could drop I knew what the
conferences were I knew what the you know obviously the keywords were I knew
where all the money was made I knew who just came into the market I knew the big
marketing companies that were calling all of these guys trying to get their
business I knew all these details and it allowed me to become the expert in
these spaces so again stick to boring until your bills are paid so secondly
okay and then we're gonna get into the different ideas secondly guys is I don't
think until you get to about I would say minimum thirty thousand per month up to
fifty thousand dollars per month I don't think you should be paying out of your
own pocket to test new niches I don't think you should be paying out of your
own pocket to test new niches until you get to thirty to fifty thousand plus per
month what I mean by that guys is what I would recommend and I'm saying this
stuff up front because I don't want you guys to get off this call and start
going into weird niches and blowing a bunch of money on ads and blowing a
bunch of money building websites in niches you shouldn't be a part of but I
don't think that you should be spending your own money to test out niches the
reason being is once you start to get into business once you've been doing
this a long time once you crush it for one to five clients you do a really good
job they're making money you're happy they're happy what's gonna happen is
you're gonna have business owners are gonna come to you with ideas they're
gonna come to you with niches they're gonna come to you with their partners
they're gonna come to you with their family members and their referrals and
they're gonna say hey I know you're crushing it for me in concrete but my
brother-in-law he's got this he's got an XYZ business in the same city and I was
wondering if you could help him out as well and guess what now that person's
coming to you you being the expert you have leverage because they're coming to
you you're not going to them and now you get to use their money to test out this
new niche you're gonna make money and you're gonna get an education at the
same time and if you just stick to the boring niches and you just focus on
getting to where your bills are paid and scaling up to 30 50 thousand dollars per
month I promise you if you're doing a good job you're gonna get a ton of
people that are gonna reach out to you whether it's current business owners
with you know complementary businesses other businesses partners friends
whatever this is going to happen I've had this happen so many times so I'll
give you an example and I've shared this before but I had a guy that we were
selling fencing leads to in Arizona okay and this deal that we had currently
it was it was at least $1,000 a month he might have been paying us $1,200 I can't
remember but we had this deal and we had a goal that month to get you know an
extra $10,000 per month in monthly recurring revenue and I said it with my
team and I said hey if we do this here's gonna be the bonuses so we're gonna go
do this as a team whatever and I remember we were getting near the end of
the month like our 30 days and I was golfing which is always where greatest
the greatest things happen by the way I played twice last week it was amazing
and every single time by the way golfing when you're golfing and you make money
on Stripe it just it just hits differently by the way Jason already
started golfing so I wanted to mention it once you guys get that stripe
notification and you're like dude I just made $250 while I was golfing
something about that's just amazing anyway I was golfing and I remember the
whole I remember everything about it it was like my second or third shot and I
get a call from my sales guy 2020 midsummer sorry late spring and he's
like hey I'm like what's up dude I'm golfing he's like yeah I know and he's
like I have this deal but I'm not sure you're gonna want it I'm like tell me
talk to me and he's like so we have you know X you know so and so I'm like yeah
he's like well I called him I asked him about this other area doing fencing he
doesn't really cover it however he has another business I was like go on tell
me he's like he does cactus removal and immediately I was like all right broke
I'm busy it's a waste of time he's like dude I think it might work and he's in
if you're willing to take a risk he's in and so literally I was like dude and it
was my guy's name was Lincoln by the way he's inside of my program right now
Lincoln hunt super good dude and anyway I said Lincoln here's what you're gonna
do you're gonna quote him high you're gonna quote him at like 1200 bucks a
month I'm like make sure the CPC is good make sure there's no company he's like I
already did I'm like okay let him know that we don't know what's gonna happen
however we'll take his money and I said just do a three-month contract because
that sounds like that's not gonna work but let's let's try it and so he calls
back like okay I got the deal I checked my my my contracts in my email sure
enough you got the deal and dude we tried this niche on his money we told
him we said look man we don't know how this is gonna work you're the first
person we've ever even heard of I didn't even know cactus removal was a freaking
niche you know and I didn't know people paid for the stuff and I basically said
it's on you it's your risk we're gonna do the exact same thing we did with
masonry or sorry with fencing but like we don't know exactly what's gonna
happen but if you want to try it be our guest we quoted him high and he already
trusted us so he's like yeah let's do it and so dude that that was one of the
best freaking webs I don't even know if we still have that that specific client
I know for at least two years we made money and the reason I don't know is
because I don't I don't run the day-to-day inside of my agency we still
do deals we got a deal last not last Monday it was a week ago from Friday
we've got a $1,700 a month artificial grass deal we also got another tiny baby
deal of $300 a month we got we added $2,000 a month in revenue in the last
ten days or not ten days eight six business days and Francesca did all of
it so I don't know if we still have that client I'll find out all I want to know
all I want to tell you guys about we made over $20,000 doing cactus removal do
not go and use your own money to test out niches focus on boring focus on
tried-and-true build out your freaking portfolio get up to your your ten
thousand fifteen thousand thirty thousand fifty thousand and then use
other people's money to test niches and then once you get to those kind of
numbers you can start testing stuff out okay alright guys that said let's talk
about different ideas for the next five seven minutes then we'll get into let's
get into some Q&A break down some niches that kind of stuff again if you're on
this call right now and you stay till the end which is only 20 more minutes
we're gonna take a screenshot if your cameras on we're gonna send you our
digital resource and with all the ideas and all the notes from this this call so
a couple ideas guys and I tried to put these in you know somewhat in order of
the way they came to my mind but also just know that you know you need to
remember that the most important thing is a hungry business owner okay so you
want to think what I'm giving you these ideas think about you know how is that
this person a hungry business owner well I don't know well the fact that they're
doing this thing does that make them hungry or do we not know that should be
the lens that you look at all these different ideas and you should prioritize
the the the hungry business owner is the number one thing okay and I'll give you
some examples as we're going so first one I'm gonna just toss out is mailers
okay guys if you guys get mail which I still do and I used to get so annoyed I
used to get so freaking annoyed at these and I was like dude what are they doing
there's there's these little cards there's you guys know those books I
should have brought my book up here but you know those there's always like the
local coupon book I don't know where mine's at there's always that local
coupon book in your city right sometimes they're paid books those are
even better which there's a guy one of my buddies names Tony here in my city
he has this book called Dixie Direct and literally his entire business guys he
goes to local business owners they pay him to put their ad in this book they
pay him like a couple thousand bucks a year to put their ad in this book and
basically they give a free offer so think about it they're paying him to put
their company name their flyer their ad in his book and on top of that they're
giving away a freebie that's how bad they want business guys mailers are so
good somebody went through the hassle of putting this together designing it going
and getting this you know they're paying who knows what this is a hungry business
owner right they're looking for more business this is a hungry business owner
so anytime I get these before you just throw them away I have stacks of these
things guys and I did this on a call a couple weeks ago but like dude as soon
as my duct cleaning client decides that he's done with me which he's been with
me since 2020 so I don't think he's going anywhere this guy right here duct
pros it's my guy I'm calling this guy he's spending money on on air ducts and
he's given 15% off and duct cleaning already is not that high much of a high
ticket item so these type of things look you know landscaping concrete
coatings like keep these I have stacks of these things laying around my my
office see if I've got any more in here these are great let me see if I have I
always keep these things I've got to have some more here somewhere hold on I
always just throw these in my desk I know at my other place oh here we go I
knew I had more um here we go
there's another one this is a Kerman concrete and landscape we got another
that's their whole flyer net this is another interesting niche tile removal
and demolition okay guys I told you look at this look at this
duct cleaning ah patio covers maybe be one or two more there's a reason I okay
here we go another patio covers
window coverings last one there's a reason I probably kept this one pavers
look at that flyer dude we love pavers that's a big old flyer full page okay
this is a great place to start if you guys see these in the mail keep them if
you're looking for niche ideas keep them these are hungry business owners okay
that's idea number one number two people that knock on your door you know like
somebody knocks on your door and everyone gets weird about it and you
want to drive them off the porch and you want to tell them to get lost and get a
real job well I used to be a door knocker so quit being mean to those
people okay number one but I have a soft spot in my heart for door knockers
because I used to knock doors I spent four years paying for my kids school and
food and housing and our entire lifestyle was was based on me knocking
doors so anytime somebody knocks on my door basically I bought like literally I
don't know the last time you knock somebody knocked on my door I didn't buy
and my kids get weird like everyone gets weird about door knockers these are
humans guys they're freaking humans they're they're way more scared than you
are go talk to them if they're knocking on your door then if it's their company
they're super hungry if it's the company they're representing the company they're
representing is also hungry because they're paying to have a door-to-door
canvassing program if somebody knocks on your door go talk to them get their
business card like have a conversation that doesn't mean you have to use their
service but you know what I like to do is if it's something that's interesting
that I think could be a good niche I'll say hey come back give me a quote and
while they're giving me a quote dude I'm pitching these people on on on working
with me there was a guy that knocked on my door and he did was it landscape
maintenance not a niche that I would ever do again but he knocked on my door
he's like yeah here's the deal and he was a very like he was like a good clean
cut kid I took his number and I only had this tiny little front yard at the time
I didn't finish my backyard but I texted him I said hey dude just wanted to run
an idea past you and I pitched him over text I was like I do actually do lead
generation blah blah blah would you be interested in talking and I actually got
him as a client I actually got this guy's it wasn't a huge client but I got
this guy as a client and he knocked on my door so when they knock on your door
know that they're hungry either it's their company or the company that sent
them they are hungry for business they are literally sending people door to
door to get your business quit being scared of people knocking on your door know
that that indicates it's a hungry business owner get their card these guys
will they would love to come and give you an estimate and when they do guess
what they're gonna listen to what you have to say let them come give you an
estimate on freaking doing you know a mobile car wash I know that I spend
every time my guy comes and he comes every single week or every other week I
spend between eighty eighty five dollars and a hundred and thirty or hundred and
fifty dollars every single week times that by four times up by two I'll send a
three hundred to six hundred dollars per month every single month on mobile car
detail okay let them give you quotes let them come now I'm not saying pest
controls the greatest niche I'm not in it but like dude let them you know if
something like that let them give you a freaking quote quit being weird about
people knocking on your door check that if you're worried make sure they have a
license they're not canvassing your house that's a great option I promise you
some of you guys are in neighborhoods and in cities that you get knocked your
door gets knocked on every single day and you're just being weird about it and
it's literally money knocking on your door okay they are gonna listen to you
they're motivated they're gonna be kind polite and if it's their company there's
a good chance that you're gonna get that deal okay so mailers people who knock on
your door some more obvious ones look in the free group look at what other
people are talking about if you guys aren't using the free group and scanning
through there and just getting updated on you know what was posted today guys
we have 6,000 members of that group 6,000 people trying to make this business
model work and guess what there are people they're making a lot of money pay
attention to what they're saying get ideas now I wouldn't listen to anyone
unless I you know if I see an idea an interesting niche I'm probably gonna DM
that person I'm probably gonna you know go and say hey does this person know
what they're talking about I might even search their name in that group and see
how long they've been in the group and if they post the deals and go okay this
person's making money maybe I should listen but guys look in the free group
look type in the word niche has anyone tried this niche type in just you know
smart words smart phrases inside of the search bar and look at what other people
are talking about do it inside of the art of digital real estate my group do
it inside of rank and rent domination which by the way is also a good group
Ryan Dalton has that group you guys can check that group it's some of you guys
that are inside of digital landlords if I don't know if there's anyone in here
besides Jason Aaron I didn't really pay attention but guys these are great
resources like look again we're just thinking of ideas right free group is a
great place to get ideas next this is one of the ones I really really like is
Facebook community groups local community local Facebook community
group so for example here in st. George I think I'm gonna tell you what my my
groups called I seem to always pull deals from hold on one sec so what you
could do is type in your city so type in st. George or Vegas or whatever and then
click on groups and look at the different groups so right here st. George
word of mouth st. George word of mouth 52,000 members that is literally a group
I'm gonna click on it and tell you the details here welcome to st. George word
of mouth the point of this group is to be a place where residents can come ask
or recommend businesses in the area okay now some of these groups are a bit
spammy yes but let me tell you some of the ones I'm a part of I'm not even in
that group there's so many groups in here I should be I should be hitting these
group I'm gonna tell Francesca hit these groups because I'm not even in them
right now but type that in look at them and then guys what you're gonna notice
I know I'm in some of these groups I want to find one that I'm a part of hold
on let me go to my groups um guys in these group people are going to ask for
recommendations hold on one sec let me go ahead and go to groups I've joined let
me find an example okay um st. George that's a yard cell group not my favorite
type of group let me see if I'm in another st. George group let me see if I
could search about the groups I'm in okay no that one never let me in let's
look at st. George classified okay st. George classified then I'm gonna go to
the search bar I'm gonna type in recommend okay typed in the word
recommend and I'm gonna see if anything pops up hold on this is kind of a weird
group it's more like just straight anyway we could scroll through let me
see if I can see anything I'll pop my head and then if not I won't waste any
time well guys you could scroll these groups you can look for you know people
that are recommending that group that I just mentioned though that sounds like
that the perfect group to be a part of I'm gonna actually request access right
now so again go to groups type in your city st. George Vegas whatever st. George
word-of-mouth I'm gonna push join it's probably gonna ask me questions there we
go blah blah I'll do that after okay that's a great place to come up with
ideas okay so another thing even not inside of groups is you can go to
Facebook and just search the actual regular search bar and type in you know
smart words so type in recommend and type in the city so I typed in recommend
st. George okay beautiful great example I typed in recommend st. George now this
is old but we could filter this I believe by by date but I'm just gonna
give you a couple ideas so like right here looking to put a pool in our
backyard who do you guys recommend okay and I actually like that post so I must
have reached out okay so that's somebody that is a lead guys I could literally
listen to this I could literally reach out to that person especially because
look with that person I have ten mutual friends I can reach out to that person I
could say hey I have this I have a recommendation for you you may or may
not know me it looks like we have ten mutual friends can I recommend somebody
for you guess what that is now a lead I didn't even have to pay for Google Ads
and I have a lead that I can use to go and find a business owner now pool
installation not loving that niche right now because of the recession it's
kind of dipped off but I've made some money in that in that niche okay let's
see what else we got need an AC guy who do you guys recommend that's amazing
don't love the niche but it's an idea right can anyone recommend a good bug
man oh here we go four days ago looking to get quotes for concrete in st. George
who do you recommend okay number one I have a lead Emma Taylor then I'm gonna go
to the comments and check this out I get all these different businesses right so
guys again we're just talking about generating niche ideas but this also
gives me an idea of who's good in town Bryce kid new edition concrete I've
never heard of them I can give you a free quote that's Bryce kid right there
so Bryce kids active that dude is is literally in the in the DMS Austin
McDonald trademark concrete Latson concrete Austin McDonald dude there is
literally this is one of the best it's it's unbelievable you could go here and
just scroll let's see what else we got let me give you one or two more ideas
guys looking for an architect that does home remodels that seems a little too
niche I'm not sure that I would do that one uh what else we got for
recommendations what else what else that's hair I'm not gonna be doing hair
plumbing says I need a plumber what else lucky looking for the best realtor
lender team that's not a niche that I like dentist again not all these are
going to be the ones you want but this is just a great place to start looking
for a videographer for an event this was July 31st less than a month ago okay
anyway just giving you guys ideas that's a great place to come up with niche
ideas okay let's keep going through these really quick so I can get one or
two questions another great place to come up with ideas is services that you
need done around your house services that you need done around your house you
need your carpets cleaned you need your house clean you need your pool clean you
need new concrete I just barely bought a new car about eight months ago nine
months ago and it's a very low car and so my my curb it almost scrapes my Tesla
and so I was like dude it's gonna scrape the crap out of this new car so I had to
go and I had to cut the concrete almost down to you know make it so it was
almost flush with the the ground that's it I'd never even thought out this
niche concrete cutting it's not concrete flat work it's not concrete decorative
concrete concrete cutting so it was something I needed done so now that's
you know that's an idea I never even thought about that right what else do
you need done at your house pressure washing I was just barely thinking about
how dirty my house like I'm gonna use that's that could be do I like the niche
no but if I did I could use that what else do I need obviously mobile car
detailing epoxy garage floor if you're looking to do that I just did that on my
townhome that's a great place services that you want or need done at your house
okay I think those are two different things services that you need done at
your house those are a little bit better I need my tree removed services that you
want done at your house I want my garage epoxy right the one that you need done
that's probably a little bit better because there's probably other people
that need it done and services that you want are still good but they're probably
not gonna be as recession proof so those are two different things the services
that you need done and the services that you want done I was looking up the other
day I was in my kitchen and I saw I had a really dirty ducts like I need to get
my ducks clean I need to get my ducks clean that's something I need to get
done I don't want to get it done but I need to get it done okay so services
that you need to get done service that you want call the company call three of
them okay have them come to your house give you an estimate while they're
giving you an estimate pitch them they're gonna listen to what you have to
say they watch your business they watch your business okay here's some more
obvious ones home advisor guys if you go to home advisor you can go I don't even
need to do this but you can go to home advisor you can go to their main website
even though I hate home advisor I'm not gonna click on their ad and you can
literally go and it says start a project and you can just go and browse guys
there's so many ideas dude put painting lawn care landscaping kitchen keating
and cooling garage gutters ceiling insulation there are so many ideas you
could just go and search on home advisor for days another idea Angie's list go and
look guys home advisor angel the one thing I don't like about these is there
so many ideas that you could become overwhelmed and I I generally like the
idea of like I would I would prefer doing like a Facebook recommendation is
more interesting to me because I could use that as a lead and I can it
literally proves to me that there's people looking for that service it kind
of gives me an idea if I see multiple people looking for pools in my area I'm
like okay pools is pretty popular in this area right you know the other good
thing is you don't have to do the Facebook groups in your city I could go
and look at recommendations Las Vegas recommendations whatever let's just think
of another city Glendale Arizona recommendations Queen Creek Arizona
right the reason I like doing your own backyard is because you have mutual
friends you can reach out to so home advisor Angie's list also guys banners
hanging at local sporting events they're paying to be there right they're paying
to have their name hung on the freaking chain link fence and then also I
mentioned car wraps people are paying thousands of dollars I spent like
$3,000 to wrap a smart car I've spent up to $5,000 to wrap these are expensive
wraps they want more business so mailers people who knock on your door free
groups local community and recommendation groups services you need
done at your house services you want done at your house home advisor Angie's
list banners hanging at local sporting events and car wraps those are ten ideas
you could not possibly go and list all the niches if you just looked at three
of those ideas okay so real quick I'm gonna stay on for like three four five
more minutes Aaron or Jason are one of you guys available to go through
questions comments really quick let's try to knock through some of them if one
of you guys are still on who's on right now yeah I don't see Aaron on here so I
can take care of it okay Jason we have any questions comments let's see if we
go we can get through in five minutes and by the way in one minute I'm gonna
have you screenshot because the people that stayed up until the hour I want
them to get the digital resource on anyone that wants to stay on the last
five minutes you're free to do so but you don't have to get the resource so why
don't you go ahead and actually just go ahead and screenshot everybody that's on
right now so we can send them the digital resource by the way Jason
already is on this call he is Donnie Dre inside the free group Jason you're at
13 or $14,000 per month well okay oh sorry sorry I just went into the
snapshot mode so one thing that happens are you at 13 or 14 thousand I was just
trying to make sure people knew so I actually lost a deal that was $800 per
month so I went back a little bit had a small setback now you're at 13 or you're
I was at 13 8 just probably went back to 13 this guy literally gave him 14 leads
in two weeks and he said they weren't good enough so I look at this as a very
good thing so small setbacks like this are actually really good things for your
business because it allows you to find somebody who's more hungry and will take
advantage of receiving 14 weeds in two weeks so $13,000 per month right now
beautiful okay so I'm just saying I'm just mentioning that so people know
that you're you're legit you're not just some whatever so Jason let's go to the
comments but yeah you're good bro yeah okay sorry had to take that screenshot
real quick um so we have uh Amy D. Hoog she's just referring to some niches
refrigeration for dairy wineries or distilleries so she's just bringing up
so is this for me to like give my thoughts yeah um I first and foremost
guys let me remind everyone that every niche you can generate leads for no
matter what it is I promise you I've done some really competitive what you
can generate leads for everything everything doing this model but it's
it's varying scales of success so I think about how many boxes does it check
is it is it phone driven if it checks that I go to the next one is it is it
branded if it checks that do I go to the next one or is it unbranded sorry is
it a high ticket and you just start going down the list so I'm gonna like
that one for example I don't know anything about that niche but to me that
sounds like something that's like you it's not mobile right that's something
that's like a brick-and-mortar or am I wrong like that fits more into the HVAC
right okay okay I thought it was like something to actually like these okay
so yeah that would that does sound like it was fit I don't know anything about
that Nick tell me what it's called again what she said it called you said
refrigeration for dairy and wineries and distilleries or so large
refrigeration systems I'm yeah industrial refrigeration um yeah I mean
so I don't love HVAC but this sounds like a sub niche of HVAC it's commercial
refrigeration so it looks like this is saying like I don't even know anything
about this but it's yeah this that could be interesting so um cold storage for
breweries if you're talking about the person that actually goes and fixes or
does the repairs and the maintenance on these type of things that could be very
interesting because that is a sub niche of a much more competitive niche I like
that because it's specific the only thing you could get into is because it's
so neat niche I'm not sure that there's gonna be a ton of companies that are
doing it which means that the one person in town that's doing it might be getting
all the business already but I like that you're taking a niche that is very
competitive HVAC and you're sub niching it's like going to plumbing and going to
what's the one that everyone does like sewage or you know what I'm talking
about right where they go and you know I'm talking about Jason not sewage you
talking about the septic tank pumping septic room is it septic tank removal or
whatever septic septic cleaning I don't know that yeah if it's a if it's a
competitive niche make sure you're going to submit so this one I'm not a know but
I just don't know anything about it I have to do more research but that's a
very interesting niche I've never even thought about it but that's very very
niche imagine it basically industrial refrigeration technician or whatever I
don't even know what the term is so I'm not a know on that one I know it's gonna
be high ticket the only thing that sounds a little bit scary for me is that
there might not be a lot of people so if you go into a big enough city and it's
low competition yeah that could be very interesting what else now Martin says so
he's recommending another niche it's water well installation that said that
is again I know that one's gonna be high ticket because my dad's a farmer and I
know how much he spends on doing a water well I don't know how much demand if you
can go into a city where there's demand there's a lot of money in water wells it
costs I don't know if you guys know the work that goes into that they have to
they have to figure out where the water where to drill and then they literally
like I think at my dad's farm they've they have to drill hundreds of feet to
get into these aquifers and it's expensive it's multiple ten thousand
dollars to do it's very expensive so I like it I just as long as there's volume
and then again the only thing I would think that might be a little bit tough
is I'm thinking like my dad he's not going to Google to search for somebody
to put in a water well he's gonna call his other buddy that's a farmer and say
hey Ken who do you use or hey Tony who do you use that's the only thing that
would scare me about that everything else sounds good I've never done it just
full transparency but that's the one thing I don't like it sounds a bit of
like a bit more of a referral type of niche and you want to consider a little
bit of the closing process too if it takes several months for a job to
process and for them to get all the licensing and stuff they need and then
pass code and stuff it's probably not a niche that's ideal because it's gonna
take several months to close the job yeah that would be one of those again
guys once you get into you know paying for your bills and you're good then then
you start tapping in this kind of thing but yeah write it down have a have a
note in your phone of interesting ideas and it's something you could look into
any other ones yeah um let's see so let's do two more we'll call it okay so
Ameya she is so roofing and house painters as two niches that's what
she's recommending I don't even know she's recommending because she might
have also she could be asking I don't like oh sorry yeah asking about that
sorry I don't like either of them roofing if you want to go into roof
repair or you want to go into metal roofing or tile roofing you want to go
to a sub niche niche of roofing okay painting I don't like it nor have I
found anyone that is in love with that that niche either so let me save you
some time last one Martin is recommending or asking about drilling
holes and like core drilling for concrete yes I again I I would look at
search volume I would look at job size like how much does it cost to do
something like that I don't even know what that service is you drill a hole in
the concrete for what do you call so I actually talked to a concrete guy and
because I was like hey dude I can get you leads for concrete and there's a guy
I knew and he he's like oh I only focus on cutting and drilling holes doing core
drilling and I looked at the search volume and there was almost no search
volume for that like yeah it is something people offer but you want to
make sure that you get a good amount of volume for these sub niches also maybe
if you're in a bigger city but I can't make my guy some niches you're gonna
have to go to a bigger city which isn't the worst thing okay I'm looking at the
service right now that would kind of fit in that same category as cutting just
like I had no idea that people I had no idea that anyone I was like I when I got
my sidewalk cut down I had no idea that that was even a service like who would
ever think that you need to call somebody and pay them $5,000 to cut your
sidewalk like for what and then you're like oh I see it now but again I I can
tell you there's not that many people that are getting their driveways cut
down it's it's probably bigger jobs it's probably you know few and far between so
guys with any of these sub niches you're gonna have to go into probably bigger
cities bigger markets because that's typically where you're gonna find more
search volume so the more obscure the niche or the more obscure the niche the
more the bigger the city most likely which isn't bad but again stick to
boring until you get to the 10 20 30 40 $50,000 I wouldn't even think about some
of this stuff until you've gotten to minimum paid your bills let's do one more
do you have any more we do one more okay I think we've kind of covered most of
people asking about the niches but James Curry says that he has a deal in the
concrete coring and cutting so there you go so yeah it's doable that that's good
news that if someone else is doing it and then my next question would be like
how many you do have one deal they have to do how much is that deal do you have
you done it across multiple because I also got a deal for let me give you an
example like I got a deal for stucco okay build a side got a deal but I can
tell you I haven't built another one because it wasn't that good so I would
be interested in James Curry to know and you could maybe post it or people
could reach out to James the Facebook group but yeah there you go there's
money in it it just comes down to how much money and could I use that same
time those same resources in another niche and get way more upside way more
bang for my buck way more juice out of my squeeze or is it worth it make sense
all right that said guys appreciate you guys being on the call what we're going
to do once again if you were on ten minutes ago we screenshot it we're gonna
send you the digital resource Jason we typically have that within 24 hours
roughly right yeah I so I've been kind of bad at going through and sending them
out lately excuse me I'll make sure to get that done though and go through and
send it to everybody who's been here we get so much so many response for the
recording that sometimes I kind of like going back and hitting you guys up but
I'll make sure to get that done beautiful so guys thanks for being on
the call again just a reminder stay in the boring until you hit you tell you
pay your bills and again you don't need I guess I'll end with this I've made my
first seven figures in five or less niches like I had if you looked at all
of my put my my properties and you looked at all the niches I was in I was
in five or less and majority of those were in three you don't need to have 20
different niches you don't need to have something so obscure that you've never
thought of you don't need to have some crazy niche that that you know no one's
ever even considered to make millions of dollars you can make millions of dollars
doing boring tried-and-true basic niches and doing it again and again and again
the money is in the buy not the sale make sure you're spending the time and
going into the cities that going into the cities that are low-hanging in the
sense that they're low hanging fruit in the sense there's not a lot of
competition there's good search volume and you can go in and there's there's an
opportunity for you to go and rank a website and sell those leads to hungry
business owners so guys thanks for being on the call and we'll see you next week
thanks Jason