All right, guys, let's jump into, I'm gonna get my notes here because I don't want to
miss anything.
Okay, so first and foremost, last week it was interesting and I don't want this to come
across wrong.
I used to be the screaming the mic guy and I realized that was just not me.
Actually it is me sometimes, but not always.
But last week was interesting because I was, you know, I woke up in the morning, I forgot,
I'm in Dubai so I forgot it was that even Labor Day.
It's weird some holidays that you kind of forget when you're traveling.
But I remembered eventually because my brother Porter, if you guys might know him, he's in
the free group.
He's about, he's at like 6,400 bucks a month.
It's his birthday, always on Labor Day.
So I remembered and I started thinking back to like previous Labor Days and I don't remember
any of them, like actually none of them except for one.
And that was in 2017 and I posted about this and I put 18, I think I said six years ago
but it was actually seven.
This is 2017 and this is literally about five weeks after I failed my first business.
I got started into RankinRent, I got a couple deals and then I got shiny penny syndrome
and I thought, man, I think I'm going to start a software company because that sounds cool.
I swear to you, if you think I'm lying, I promise you that when I say that, I literally
just didn't think it sounded cool to tell people I did marketing.
That was one of the main determining factors.
That's how stupid I was as a, how old did I have been, eight years?
I was like 25 and I was still dumb.
I thought it sounded cool to say I had a software company but now I realize it's cool, no matter
what you're doing, to make money because that's what really matters, that's what we're here
for.
Anyway, I had got shiny penny syndrome, I chased this software idea, I failed, I lost
tons of money.
I wasted nine months and it came to this boiling point on, it was either July 27th or July
28th.
I think it was the 28th because that would be, yeah, I think it was the 28th and I'm
in my living room and I'm telling my wife for the fifth, sixth, seventh time, she's
like, so what's going on with the business?
I was so annoyed at this point because nothing, at least for men, I don't know for you ladies
if it's the same, but when my wife would ask me about money, it's like she was questioning
me as a person and my abilities and it was really, really hurtful and she again was like,
so what's going on, give me an update and I didn't have one.
I was like, well, the developer said that we're like two weeks away from beta and he'd
been saying this for like six months.
She finally looked at me and she's like, you know this guy is scamming you, right?
You know that this is not happening.
I knew as she said it that she was right and essentially without going into too much detail,
I paid this guy 60 grand, 50 grand and we'd split it, me and a partner, but then I had
bought him out because I found some stuff out.
So now I was 50, 60 grand in of my own money plus nine months of my time plus the opportunity
cost of not going and doing door to door sales.
I had no money.
Like I literally had no money and we had bills due at the first of the month and she's like,
she basically was like, it's time for you to start taking care of this family and it
was like one of those like, my goodness, I needed to hear that and it took me a long
time to even be able to say that out loud, but it was very embarrassing.
It was, it killed my confidence, but it was that day that I realized like I have to change
and I have a failed business.
My first one's I'm all for one.
I have to make a change and so I went and did the only thing that I knew how was I was
like, dude, where's that program that I bought like a year ago?
Let me just go start selling something and I started watching the training and I was
like, what's the easiest thing to sell and I was like, I'm going to go sell a couple
of websites.
Let me go sell a couple of websites with SEO and I, so I told my wife, I said, you know,
she's like, I need, you need to call this person, this person, like maybe it's time
you just go get a job and I was like, I can't, like I've talked too much crap.
I'm not going back to my job and which was a door to door salesperson and I'm not going
to get a 95.
So I said, give me till the first of the month, which was three days from that day and I will
have however much we need and we needed $3,000 to basically cover our bills and she's like,
okay, sounds good.
I'll give you three days.
No chance I'm getting it and guys in three days out of desperation and it's funny how
humans are like this when our backs up against the wall, we are so creative.
We are so resourceful and in three days I came up with $3,000 cash, sold three websites
and was able to buy myself another 30 days and then so essentially I used SEO to kind
of get me out of that situation and then I transitioned and I just did it too slow and
I didn't do it correctly.
So whoever it was that said, you know, they're doing SEO, there's nothing wrong with SEO.
There's just a proper way to do it and there's a wrong way to do it and it's very easy to
get stuck in the wrong way and to chase the money only to end up in a year with nothing,
with no assets, with nothing that you can tie the clients to.
So anyway, the reason I'm telling this whole story, five weeks after this because that
would have been, you know, September, beginning of September, I just remember on Labor Day,
I'd been working my butt off like truly, truly, truly I'd been working my butt off and I made
good money.
I made $3,000 in three days and I made 10,000 bucks my very first month going all in on
SEO and that was cash collected because I needed to.
I had kids, I had bills, all this stuff and Labor Day, I remember it was Sunday night
going into Monday and I thought to myself, like, I want to spend time with my kids.
I was at my parents' house and I was like, I want to go to the parade and, you know,
like spend some time with them because I haven't spent much time but I was like, I need to
like, I got stuff to do and I just remember I woke up, I needed to write 3,000 words of
content.
Yes, I used to write my own content.
I wrote my first 300,000 words of content just for the record and I woke up at 4 a.m.
And I sat in my parents' kitchen with it completely quiet and I picked away the keyboard
and I wrote 3,000 words of content before I went to the gym and I showered and went
to the parade.
And I remember that because I was so tired, of course, because I woke up at 4 a.m., but
I was so excited to be making money.
I was so, it was so refreshing to know that like even if it was a thousand bucks, it was
my money.
It wasn't, it wasn't relying on somebody else and I was actually making money and it was
so exciting.
So, I had that whole, whatever, I made a post about it and then I got on the call and I,
you know, I was going to share this training and there was two people on.
And again, guys, you don't have to work on Labor Day.
Some of you guys aren't in that, most of you guys hopefully aren't in that situation but
I think that the rhetorical question I wanted to ask was like, you know, if you're not where
you want to be, should you be taking Labor Day off?
Like if you're not where you want to be, should you be, you know, taking off the Friday, whatever?
And so, I guess rhetorically, I want you guys just to be thinking about this as like either
stop complaining about where you're at or do something about it.
And my dad always used to say this quote to me, if you always do what you've always done,
you always get what you've always got.
And I know it's stupid, it's cliche, and I've heard it a million different times, a million
different ways, but it's so freaking true.
I do the same thing.
We sit and we do the same thing again and again.
We keep coming on these lives.
We keep getting our pencil and our paper and we keep saying, well, I'm going to start that
business but we keep coming up with a reason why we're not going to do it today.
You know, well, we're going to do it once so-and-so graduates.
We're going to do it once, you know, we finish the backyard.
We're going to do it when my job slows down.
You have no idea how many people have almost started this business, have almost done it
and then something happens and they don't.
And I just had a friend recently, he's been telling me over and over, I'm so bored at
my job.
Like, whatever, I don't, it's not, I can make so much more money complaining, complaining,
every single time I see him and I'm like, dude, do this.
And he's like, okay, let me move some money around, let me get into your program, whatever.
He pulls money out of his 401k.
He does the whole deal.
And when it comes down to it, I message him and he's like, it should be deposited on Wednesday.
I'm like, so like, are you joining or like, what's the deal?
He's like, he sent me this long text, something came up and I got to just spend some time
on this person.
And again, it's my friend, but and I didn't say a word back to him because it's my friend
and I just said, hope everything's good, man.
And good luck.
You know, I'm not going to chase you or whatever.
But it was just, it was a reminder that this is how we are as humans.
So rhetorically, I think about this to myself, like I complain that I'm not in a million
dollars a month.
I don't complain, but I said, why am I not a million dollars a month?
And then I'm doing the same stupid stuff that I was doing when I like that I've been doing
and if nothing's going to change and I'm still staying up, like I'll tell you guys, I'll
be honest with you guys.
Last night, you know, my most productive, when I go to bed early on Sunday and I plan
my son on Sunday for my week and I go to bed early, I wake up and I get so much done.
Like I start Monday so strong.
And yesterday I slept in, I didn't plan and I pushed it.
I'll do it later.
I'm going to get some food.
I didn't plan until this morning.
I did plan.
It's not till this morning.
And because of that, I didn't have any momentum.
So last night somebody sent something to me and all of a sudden I'm on x.com on just looking
at these threads.
I didn't go to bed till 3 a.m. last night.
That's so bad.
It's so embarrassing.
And I'm telling you guys because number one, I'm not going to lie to you.
Number two, I do the same stupid stuff you guys do.
And number three, it's like, how can I expect to be at a million dollars a month if I'm
still spending two hours of time that I can't get back?
So painful to say on stupid x.com on meaningless threads that I could have read.
I could have written a book or started a book.
I could have made posts.
I could read content.
I could have slept.
I could have called.
I mean, it was so dumb.
So again, guys, I just wanted you guys to understand it and maybe just to like relay
or to share my frustration.
And what I'm thinking about is if you're not where you want to be, are you doing anything
different than you've been doing?
And if not, then how do you expect anything to change?
It's actually, it's asinine.
Nothing's going to change.
So that's just a little quick thought.
And with that said, guys, I want to get into what we're going to share today.
Now, again, Jason, if you see comments that are pertinent, cut me off.
Aaron, if you need to cut me off, let me know as well.
And then at the end, we're going to do Q&A.
Okay?
How's it going so far, guys?
Going great.
I think it's going pretty good.
Beautiful.
Okay.
So when do you pull the plug on the city?
That's what we're going to talk about today.
My goal, by the way, is that with this specific call, is that by the end of this live, you're
going to have an understanding of my specific criteria for when it's time to pull out of
a city and niche.
But you have to remember that you're only going to perfect this through repetition,
by doing.
And so you can read about it.
You can listen to hundreds of hours of stuff.
But until you go in to an area and you lose some money on ads and you feel what it's like
to see that money going out the door and, oh my gosh, I might get zero return.
Should I pull?
Until you've done that a ton of times, you're not going to be able to perfect this.
And that's just kind of the reality.
So that is my goal with this live, guys, is to have you guys know this criteria doesn't
mean that you have to believe it.
And I don't want you to believe anything that I say without testing it, okay?
So here's the plan, kind of the outline I want to talk about.
Number one is I'm going to talk about how picking the right city and niche is the key.
We're going to be talking about, you know, deciding when to actually pull out is an art,
not a science.
We're going to be talking about if you are actually generating leads, there's always
a deal to be had.
We're going to talk about the fact that you don't lose money until you quit.
We're going to be talking about my criteria for winning areas put on the chopping block
and then my motto in life, but especially in business, okay?
So that said, let's get into it.
Number one, man, I always use like the number 17 or I don't know, something about seven,
I always use some random number for the number of times I've said something.
But guys, I have said this so many times.
The key to every part of this business, the make or break with this business is picking
the right city and niche combo.
If you do not, if you do not pick the right city niche combo, I don't care how good you
are at SEO, I don't care how good you are at ads, I don't care how good you are at sales,
I don't care how quick you can transfer leads, everything is harder.
On the other hand, if you get that right, if you get into a juicy freaking right, low
hanging fruit, you can do almost everything wrong and still win and it feels light and
it feels exciting and it feels, I don't say easy, but it doesn't feel heavy.
And it's like it's motivating because it happened and you did it quickly.
So I just want to stress guys that if you guys are, if you guys do not have the criteria
and you are not confident in what that looks like, you are going to be spinning your wheels
because you're going to, it's going to be hard for you to pull out of a city because
you're going to go, I don't know if that was the right city, maybe I just picked the wrong
city.
But if you know you're in the right city, then you're like, I know this is right because
of this, this, this and this.
It's like these other ones that I was in.
So obviously it's got to be my ads or my landing page or the way that I'm handling these leads
or my cold calling.
But it's so frustrating when you don't know if it's the right city, if you're not getting
leads or you're not having any success to know what the heck is freaking going on.
So really quick, what I want to ask, I'm going to have Jason, this is completely, I didn't
tell you I was going to ask this, but do you want to speak on that a little bit?
Tell these, I mean, maybe, maybe I'm completely in my own field here, but have you seen that
to be true?
Have you seen that, you know, certain areas it's like, dude, I could do a hundred of these
tomorrow and other areas, everything you do, it seems like you just can't move, you know,
can't move the needle.
Yeah, for sure.
And every time I try to go against that, then I end up losing that campaign.
So just stick to what works.
Don't, what is it, what's the, what they say in the South, if it ain't broke, don't fix
it.
I've heard that about a thousand times over the course of my door-to-door sales days and
it is so freaking true.
Okay, now next question.
How do I get the perfect framework?
Well, you can go develop your own or you can pay to get mine.
It's really easy.
Okay.
There's one that, there's 1.8 thousand YouTube videos you could go watch.
And how many live?
Aaron, how many lives do you think we've done inside the free group before we stopped doing
them in the free group?
It was like a solid three years straight.
So like every week, I think I missed two and I was, I was literally in a jungle in Africa
and physically couldn't get on and I didn't plan well.
Uh, there, there's probably a hundred, there's gotta be 150 of those things, right?
Cause I did it.
Yeah.
Three, like now maybe like 125, 130, 130 times, there's 130 times an hour and 15 minutes
I mean, do the math.
Plus all the posts.
So you either pay with your time or you pay with your money.
That's it.
There's no, you pay the piper.
That's how you get the perfect formula.
So I have it.
You want to buy it.
If you don't, you can go through all the material.
If you think that I know what I'm talking about.
Okay.
That's really simple.
Um, the other option is you go and just do what I did, but you guys have to remember,
even though I did all that I did, I spent four hours, four years, sorry, developing
and trying and testing the perfect due diligence formula.
What I think people forget is I also paid, I bought over $23,000 in programs on top of
the four years, four years.
So the fact that some people like, I'm just going to go, I'm just going to go, I'm at
the perfect formula.
That's like thinking that you're going to be like some of these investing companies
that look at a 500 deals a week and know exactly what metrics and exactly what the market should
look like and exactly, um, what the, uh, what the cap rate needs to be, the minimum cap
rate and the growth of the city and thinking that you're even going to play ball.
Absolutely not.
Okay.
So anyway, I just have to stress to you the importance of picking the right city in the
niche.
Cause you guys, I'm going to tell you all this stuff, but if you're in the wrong city,
it doesn't matter what you do.
You're screwed.
Okay.
So that's all I want to say.
Um, also I want to give you a little pro tip and I know I've talked about this before,
but I saw some of you guys said you were new, uh, in the comments.
If you aren't looking at CPC, which for the brand, brand, brand new people, that is the
cost per click, the cost that it costs you to go to Google and say, put me on page one
and I'll pay every time someone clicks on my ad instead of waiting for him to rank.
If you're not looking at the cost, the CPC guys, if you're not factoring that into your
decision of going into an area, that's your business.
Okay.
I've never been advised this from any other course and I've bought a lot.
I've been, I'm in all of them, all the ones that you guys have heard of.
I bought them all.
I'm in, I'm in friends with most of them.
Um, the ones I'm not, they don't like me.
That's fine.
But if you're not looking at CPC, then that's your business, but you should be.
Okay.
Even if you're not going to run ads, you should be looking at CPC and I don't have time to
explain all that, but that is just a pro tip.
Okay.
Next, this is an art, not a science.
I, I've tried to make this as scientific as possible.
I've tried my best with, you know, okay, when do we pull out of an area?
Because guys, when I, in 2020, when we went from eight to $10,000 up to a hundred thousand
dollars a month in an eight month window, we were running campaigns.
We were spending money on ads.
We were hustling and bustling and shuffling and we had how many in the queue and how many
getting set up and we, I knew to the second, it was like, I think it was like four minutes
and 32 seconds or five minutes and 32 seconds.
I could set up an ad and it was exactly the same copy and paste the keyword.
I knew exactly what I was doing to, to a freaking team.
And even then, even then I was always surprised here and there, even knowing every single
factor that I did.
I want you guys to understand that this is an art, not a science.
Okay.
When you spend X amount, then you pull out.
But the problem is, is it's like, well, maybe you spent X amount of dollars on ads in the
wrong city or in the right city, but the wrong time of year, or in the wrong right city and
the right time of year, but you didn't do the right ad, like there's so many factors
that you just have to understand.
This is an art, not a science and instead of being frustrated by that, I think you should
be excited by that because this is how I always think about things that are hard or that take
time and effort and thought and creativity and whatever.
Like when Google comes out with a GMB update, everyone's like, oh my gosh, I get excited
about it.
And I don't want to try and, I don't want this to sound like I'm regurgitating information
that people are saying online, but if you really think about it, if it's hard, it's
just pushing people away that aren't willing to go through it.
And so the fact that this is an art and a lot of this business is an art, there's a
reason we call the Facebook group the art of digital real estate.
And we call it the art of pre-selling is because no one wants an art.
Everyone wants to have an exact, perfect, when this happens, then do this.
Guys, that's just not life.
And if you need those answers and you want to live a life that's like, if this happens
then you're more going to be more comfortable, more secure in a nine to five type of a setting.
And I don't mean that in any disrespectful way because that's okay.
But this might not be for you.
This is an art, not a science.
And it's just like with stock market, guys, there's no exact science for how long you
should stay in a stock.
Guys, I invested in 2014.
I worked the entire summer door to door sales, sweat buckets of sweat, got rejected thousands
of times, all kinds of different stuff, lost sleep, got in fights with my wife because
of this, that and the rest and how tired I was, whatever, right?
Missed time with my kids, spent that entire summer doing door to door sales.
And Jason did some of that as well.
So he knows my pain.
Some of you guys might have as well.
And I made that year, I think it was $130,000, okay, basically.
That's gross.
And I think I probably put like one 10 in my pocket.
Didn't have a ton of expenses, but I did have some.
And I spent of that, I spent, I put 40 or 50, I think it was 50, no, it was 50, not
40.
$50,000.
So I lived on part of it.
Keep in mind, I lived on part of it.
And then I spent the majority of the money I had left and I put it on a stock, on one
stock that was going to IPO.
And it was the company I worked for, Vivint, it's called Vivint Solar.
And Vivint Solar, just before that, Alibaba had, if you guys are familiar with that, it's
like the Chinese Amazon, they had gone public.
And literally, I don't know, their stock like 13X or something.
And I started doing the math.
I was like, yo, if I put in 10,000 bucks in this team, 13Xs.
And if it does half of that, then that six, how can I lose?
And to be fair, our bosses, our regional managers, they were telling all of us, get all the money
you can get, put your entire back end of check into this company.
If you got to go to your dad and borrow money.
Anyway, I put $50,000 in the stock and this thing, I put it in and not only did it not
go up, it literally the day after it was down, it would have been better for me to buy in
at the regular price.
And for the entire time, guys, that I was in the stock, I was losing the money.
But the crappy part is, I didn't know when to pull out.
I didn't know if I should keep it in, whatever.
And I pulled out, this is so, it's embarrassing.
I pulled out at the beginning of 2020 and it was, instead of being worth 50,000, which
it had gone down to being worth about 10, it had bumped up to like 25.
So I swelled up a bit and I was like, dude, I'm going to take half my money and just get
out of this thing.
And I did.
I cashed out and I promised you guys like two months later, that thing was not only
worth what I originally bought in, but it was worth like 50% more.
If I would have waited two more months, I waited six years.
And if I would have waited six years and two months, I would have made money, like enough
that it would have been worth my money being in there the entire time, okay?
My point being, that's an art.
This is an art.
Some of the best things in life are art.
Life is art.
And you just got to get comfortable with that, okay?
All right.
Number three thing I want to say, if you guys are generating leads in an area, if you have
a website that's organically getting leads from the GMB, from the organic rankings, from
whatever it is, if you are getting leads, there is always a deal to be made.
If you're running ads and that ad campaign and that landing page is producing consistent
leads, there is always a deal to be had.
And in the same way that my stock, with my stock example, you do not lose money until
you pull out.
You do not lose money until you quit.
And what I mean by that is, let's say in a hypothetical situation that Aaron goes and
sets up a campaign for minneapolisconcrete.com.
And Aaron, he spends 150 bucks, right?
And he has no business owner.
He's gotten some leads.
He's hooked a couple of business owners.
He's tried to get on the Zoom with two of them.
He's 0 for 2.
Or maybe he's only, he's 0 for 1.
If Aaron quits and he's like, dude, this doesn't work, Nick's full of crap, digital real estate
is a baloney, I'm going to do drop shipping, I'm going to do freaking e-com, whatever,
I'm going to go to my 95, that's fine.
That is the only way that Aaron could lose money.
Because Aaron, let's say he's at $250 spent, he has no deal.
But he's like, dude, I'm going to double down.
This area is producing leads.
I know I'm going to get a business owner.
I just got to get creative.
I just got, it's just that next one.
And he spends $500.
He doubles his spend, okay?
But on the last person, he gets the deal.
It's $1,500 a month or even $1,000 a month.
He gets the deal, signs a six-month contract.
Guess what?
Every single dollar that he spent to get to that deal, he recouped instantly.
And he's positive.
And that doesn't mean he had to stay in Minneapolis.
That could mean he was in Minneapolis.
He determined, yes, indeed, this is too competitive.
I didn't listen to Nick.
The CPC was too high.
I'm going to shift to a smaller city in Minnesota or I'm going to shift states because this
isn't a great state.
I'm going to go to Tampa and I'm going to set it up.
And he spends $250 in Tampa.
As long as he doesn't decide to quit and he keeps doing it until he gets that first deal,
he doesn't lose his money.
Okay?
And the way I view it, guys, is you're spending money that you're spending the customer's
money.
Right?
Every time I turn on ads, I'm spending my customer that's about to sign with me is the
way I do it.
Why?
Because I'm not stopping until I get a deal.
Guys, I'll spend $1,000.
I'll go 0 for 20 because I know eventually I'm going to get a deal.
And even if I spend, by the way, I don't think I've ever spent $1,000.
I think the most I've ever spent is a couple hundred.
But I'm just using an extreme example.
I'll spend $1,000 because I know that even if I do get the deal, month one, I break even
and now I'm making money.
Okay?
So you guys have to remember that you get in and you start putting a little bit of money
on a credit card and you're like, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, I'm losing money.
No, you don't lose money until you quit.
Okay?
You don't lose money until you walk away.
Just like I wouldn't have lost that money until I pulled out.
If I would have waited until it, hey, just fix your head, dude.
It's got to come back up or you're leaving it in.
I would have made money.
Okay?
So that's the deal.
Okay.
So now we're going to get into the juicy stuff.
We're going to talk about my criteria for winning areas, put on the chopping block.
But what I'm going to do really, really quick, Jason, do we have any comments?
We don't have any comments yet.
Nope.
Okay.
So what I'm going to do, just one, give me, I just have to plug my computer in.
I'm at a nice 2%.
Hold on.
It's going to kick off one of my lights.
My bad.
Hold on.
Just a thought on why Nick has been saying this.
What he's saying is it's so important to actually find the right business owner.
So he's willing to spend extra money to find the right business owner and not just take
the first person who's going to pay him.
Very good point.
Just because you can get money, just because someone's willing to give you money doesn't
mean you should take it.
And I say this, this is just like, just because something's free doesn't mean you should accept
it.
Specifically inside the free group, when I see people, we try to get rid of all the clowns,
but like I see people like, oh, I have this genius landing page.
DM me.
It's like, bro, do you even make money?
And I call these people out.
I don't know.
Was it Aaron?
Were you on that thread with that kid that was like going ballistic on me because I called
him out on the group?
Was that you or that Kyle?
Must have been Kyle.
Okay.
Anyway, some kid, he did something like that and I called him out publicly and then he's
like, you're being a dick.
I'm like, don't come in my group.
Says right there.
Don't be a dick.
Anyway, let's talk about my criteria for when I put an area on the chopping block.
Again, guys, this is me.
This is my criteria.
What do I know?
Well, I know that real quick.
I know how to make.
Sorry, bro.
I was just going to say real quick, the audio is fine, but the video is really lagging choppy.
Just on a side note, you know, you know what, I don't know if that's what I think it is.
I think it's what I'm charging.
I just kind of said again, pretty rough.
How's the audio now?
What if I just turn the camera off for a second?
How's the audio?
Fine.
Yeah, it's fine.
You know, I think it's I think it's when I plug in my computer to charge it at the same
time.
We're just going to go with the camera off for a second.
Everyone can hear me.
OK, so, yeah, my computer is at two percent.
Otherwise, I do.
It's got to be some weird thing with because I got like a power converter and just all
kinds of stuff going on.
I got it's quite a mess here.
I'm going to start a fire in my in my apartment.
So guys, let's talk about my criteria.
What I was about to say, though, is I was saying, you know, these are my criteria.
What do I know?
And I was going to say, I know how to make a million dollars a year doing this.
So that could be important.
So here's my criteria.
I've got a couple criteria, but I think you guys are going to be a little bit surprised
by this.
OK, so and again, we didn't even announce this at the beginning.
But what we're going to do is, well, I think we've already created this, Aaron.
I don't know if you've included this in it, but typically what we do on these calls is
if you stay till the end with your camera on, we're going to screenshot everybody here
And we're going to send you the digital resource that we've created from this training.
So but just in case this wasn't put, I would I would write these things down.
OK, I just create that link, a Google Drive link.
So I'll drop it in the comments at the end of the column.
People can just download the PDF.
That's amazing. That's amazing.
And also, I think what we are going to do, too, is anyone that stays on, we were going
to do the the we were going to give them the early access to the next podcast episode,
which is going to is going to drop on Thursday.
So Aaron, if you want to grab that Vimeo link, make it unlisted.
We can drop that at the end as well.
Sounds good.
So if you guys stay till the end, I don't even know what how many of you have on 10,
15, 5, I see 21, including us.
How many?
21, including us.
Beautiful. OK, so there's 18 people, basically.
You guys stay to the end.
We're going to give you guys the digital resource and early access, three days early
access to the latest podcast, which what was the name of the latest podcast we did?
It was the oh, the perfectly the the the perfectly broken business model.
I think it was titles like that.
It's just recorded like two days ago.
So, guys, here's my criteria.
These are things I would consider writing down.
And this is when when these things happen, this puts the area on a chopping block for me.
OK, number one is I have spent at least one hundred and fifty to two hundred dollars on ads.
I've made adjustments to the ads.
And or the landing page, and I'm still not generating leads.
So I go, I spend 50 bucks, I got nothing, I'm still going.
I spent 100 bucks, I got nothing, I'm still going.
Even if I spent 150 bucks, if I see that there's a lot of impressions and whatever,
and it just looks like there's going to be there should be, you know,
like logically, there should be leads in that area.
I know there's volume.
So there's something that's off.
Well, you know, I'm going to keep going.
OK, so if I'm not getting leads and I've spent that kind of money.
And guys, remember.
This is like a totally separate training, but just be logic, be use your intuition.
If you're getting impressions on your ads, that means it's being shown to people.
But if you're getting impressions and you're not getting clicks, your ads either suck
or they're getting shown to the wrong people because no one's clicking on them.
If you're getting clicks, that means you're spending money, but nobody's calling.
You're not getting leads.
That means you're getting clicks from the wrong people, the wrong traffic or your landing page sucks.
And I want to say this because for me, when I say I'll spend 150 to 200 dollars,
I know that my landing page is going to convert because I've just tested it so many times.
I've spent over a million dollars testing it.
I know that it's going to convert.
I know what to what my audience looks like.
So it's very rare for me.
And I also know I've chosen the right area because I know how to choose an area
because I've done it so many times wrong.
But if I spend 150 to 200 bucks and I'm not getting leads, something ain't right.
OK, that's a situation where I would move to a new area.
OK, I ain't quitting. I'm not stopping.
I'm going to keep going, but I'm going to choose a new area.
Maybe I choose a different city that's near there, you know, that kind of thing.
Let's say I'm targeting Vegas or let's say I'm targeting Henderson, Nevada.
That might be a situation where I'm like, all right, I didn't want to target Vegas,
but maybe I need to target Vegas because Henderson's not producing any leads type of a situation.
But 150 to 200 dollars, I've made adjustments to my ads and I'm still not getting leads.
That thing's going on the chopping block and it's getting ready to get plugged.
They're getting ready to get pulled. OK.
OK, that's number one.
Let's see. Number two.
OK, that's it. That's it. That's basically my rule.
These other things, I'm going to go over them.
But like this is what this is the notes that I have outside of that, guys,
outside of me spending 150 to 200 dollars on ads and, you know,
tweaking the leads or tweaking the ads, you know, whatever.
I know I've got the right city because I know my process.
Unless that happens.
I am going to get a deal.
I like I just know and that was one of the things I said at the beginning.
If you are getting leads, there's always a deal to be had.
You might have to, you know, get creative.
You might have to go find somebody on a Facebook Facebook group.
You might have to go find somebody in a neighboring town.
You might have to go find somebody in a different business,
but that also does that service.
OK, you might have to make a post on Facebook and make a post on your story.
There is always a deal. If there are leads coming in,
there is always a deal to be had.
So for me, I ain't pulling out of no area because I can't get a deal.
If there's leads coming in, I am going to go there.
OK, now there is a small caveat because I know sometimes you do something,
you do something, you do something, and it's just like, gosh, dang it.
I need to just take a break.
I'm not if I'm getting leads, that area is mine.
I'm not giving up on it.
There have been occasions where I'm like, all right,
I feel like I pitched everybody.
I need a new set of eyeballs on this.
Let me go ahead and pause this campaign.
I'll set up another one in a neighboring city
or turn on one of my other ones because I've already got one ready.
I'll go and run that, get a deal, and I'll come back to that first one.
OK, maybe I'll wait for a different time of the year.
Maybe I'll wait for, you know, the election to finish or some big news
or tax, but I am not giving up on the area.
I am getting leads in an area with ads, with organic.
I'm going to get a deal.
And that's just the mentality that I have.
So there is there is one rule that I have, and that is that if I've spent
one hundred fifty to two hundred dollars and I know that I'm in the right city,
I have my landing page is good and I'm not getting leads.
Something ain't right.
OK, and and that's the only time I'm pulling out. Period.
OK, so the truth is, guys, is that
if it's if if I'm getting leads, there is always a deal to be had. OK.
That that's it. And if not, guys, if I'm getting no clicks
and only impressions, like I told you guys, if you're only getting impressions,
it's probably getting shown to the wrong people or your ads suck.
And if you're getting clicks, but no leads, then you're probably getting
the wrong people clicking on it or your your landing page sucks.
And you just need to start making adjustments. OK, that's it.
So, guys, like for me, if you find the mentality, there is always a deal.
I will always get a deal.
There was one of my first projects.
In fact, my very first one was towing huntsville.com.
I've since sold the website.
I got a deal. I got it's like 700 bucks a month.
And it was like two, three months. They paid me.
They wanted to pay me in a check.
I didn't really know how to do stripe, whatever.
And it was kind of cool to get a check instead of a stripe.
I liked getting them in the mail, which was stupid.
But that's just how it was.
I didn't want to spend three percent.
All that stuff. Two point nine seven or whatever.
Client cancels.
And I had to find somebody else.
And I did find somebody else for a minute.
And then I couldn't after that, I could not for the life of me find someone.
Guys, I went through every single business owner.
I was given every I could.
It's like I couldn't give away leads fast enough.
I was trying everybody and anybody.
And I almost just gave up on this thing.
I was like, dude, I'm getting leads.
Why? Why is no one taking these?
You know, this area just must not be good.
And finally, I I was in this cash crunch and a friend of mine offered.
He's like, do you have any websites you want to sell?
I was like, well, I have this one that's producing a bunch of leads.
He's like, yeah, but if you don't have a client, it's not really valuable to me.
And I was like, yeah, he's right.
So I just I remember it was December of 2019.
The same December of 2019 that I decided to frickin go all in on this
and to stay in this as I went.
And I went into a Facebook group and I just started cold calling people.
I didn't even I didn't give I was so done.
I was if there was a name and a phone number,
I didn't even I didn't even need to know the company name.
And I saw this one comment.
I remember it was a December day.
It was so bloody cold outside, because I just went for a run.
I came inside and I called this number.
And I didn't know the company name, and I just pitched them.
And I ended up frickin closing this guy for 500 bucks a month.
Put him in a six month contract.
And I flipped the site and sold it for nine thousand bucks to a friend of mine,
which, by the way, he's made way more than that.
So it was a win win for everybody.
But the point is, there is always a deal to be had.
OK, if I'm getting leads and I'm not hooking business owners, that's on me.
If you're getting leads and you're not hooking business owners
or closing business owners, that's on you.
If I'm getting leads and hooking business owners, but I'm not closing,
that's on me. OK.
And guys, to just wrap up on that point.
My motto is always either yes.
Or not now, maybe later.
OK, I don't let people tell me no.
Yes, or not now, maybe later.
We've done an entire training on this inside digital landlords.
But if I go if I if I cold call somebody.
I do not let them tell me no.
I have a way that I can I can leave that door open.
I never close doors. I never slam doors.
I never burn bridges. I try my best not to, at least,
because I know that this is a long game.
And guys, if you guys are in this to make legit real money,
do not get knows, do not burn bridges, do not freaking blaze through areas.
Because the people that tell, you know, today
that are going through something tragic or in the middle of a divorce
or in a financial in three years, those same people will surprise you.
They're in a completely different situation,
maybe in a completely different business, and they will buy leads from you.
And I've had this happen not once, not twice, but probably five different times
where today I almost had the deal.
They were interested and they said no, or they they weren't interested today.
And I said, OK, let's talk down the road.
And I followed up three years later or they saw my post
or they reached out to me and said, hey, can I get some leads?
And I got the freaking deal.
So my motto in life in general is I don't I don't take knows, man.
I don't I never take those.
I leave every single door open
because it's either yes or not now, maybe later.
And that's that's the truth.
So, guys, my my criteria for the chopping block.
Is basically unless unless I've spent 150 to 200 bucks,
made some adjustments on ads
and I'm not getting leads and I am getting clicks.
Then I'm I'm in that area.
And why why can I be this confident?
Because I know what a good area looks like.
I know what what it needs to look like.
I know what kind of search volume needs to have.
I know what the CPC needs to be.
I know those things, and that gives me the confidence
to stay in an area until I get a deal.
OK, Jason, let's go through at nine minutes.
Do we have any questions, any comments?
If not, we'll wrap it up.
Yeah, Kirk was just agreeing with the business owners.
He said he's one thousand dollars.
Looks like he's one thousand euros in on ads
for business owners, and he's still in it.
So he says spot on with the business owners.
I didn't validate mine and lost money on all of them.
Be good. He says it would be good to get tips
on validating the business owners.
So Kirk, maybe mean you can just jump on a call, man,
and I can just show you some tips on that.
So just reach out to Donnie Dre after this call.
That's a good idea.
And Kirk, you're crazy if you don't take him up on that.
By the way, I appreciate you doing that.
Yeah, that's so just real quick tips on that.
I'd need more context, but don't be afraid
to do a pullback on the initial call.
That's my tip.
I think sometimes we get in, we want to get some free leads.
If I'll give you some free leads, we'll do a call.
And we're so excited that they didn't like yell at us
and we're so excited, they're showing a little bit of interest.
We're like that person in high school that never went on a date.
And then the first person out, they like go bananas
because they show him some attention.
It's pathetic. OK, don't don't do that.
Like at the end of the call, if you're unsure, say that say,
Mr. Business Owner, real quick, I'll give you some free leads.
Like, shoot me straight, man.
Are you just looking for free leads?
Because if you're just looking for free leads, like, let me know.
I'll give you a free or you want to grow your company.
Like, are you going to answer my call when I call you?
Are you going to?
Because I'm trying to I'm trying to run a business here.
I'm going to let you try this for free.
There's no absolutely no strings attached yet.
But I am here to earn your business.
And if you're not interested in talking
and you're just telling me what I want to hear, dude, I'm a big boy.
I'm a big girl. Just tell me right now.
And that terrifies some of you to say that.
But guys, say it, because if they're interested, they're going to go,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm super interested.
Sorry, I'm busy.
Or if they're not, you're going to give them an opportunity to just
freaking walk away and go call somebody else, because that's as Jason said.
The right business owner is so important.
And you guys are going to it's going to happen to you.
You're going to get business owners that give you their money today.
And they're just not the right fit.
And you want to get that money.
You want to take it so bad.
But it's not the right decision, because if you get that deal today,
you're locked in a six month contract with somebody
who's not going to be with you in a year.
And then in six months, you're going to have to get somebody new.
And that might be the time.
It's like winter.
And you have to make these big boy, big girl decisions of
even though I can take money today, it's not the right money.
It's not the long term money.
It's not the big money.
And that's a hard, mature thing that you have to you have to learn.
OK, so anything else?
Um, John Fahm, he shared one of his areas with the CBC.
And then, yeah, so I just recommended that, you know,
if you do find a good area,
I would encourage you to kind of keep it to yourself also,
especially with like sharing it with people publicly.
It's a Jamesville, Wisconsin.
Does he say what what niche concrete?
Yeah, beautiful.
I'm going to text my team right now and get it.
No, I'm just kidding, bro.
But he says he doesn't really mind.
But to be honest, like, I like to keep my areas to myself
just because that area has potential making you money.
So personally, I like to keep my areas to myself.
I don't share with people because people jump on that and try and take it.
A lot of people are lazy about doing their their due diligence.
So just be aware of that.
Yeah, I know that.
I would just pop in real quick.
You said concrete in Wisconsin.
Just the thought that might not be great
because I think it gets pretty cold in Wisconsin.
And so if you are to go there, you might just possibly want to plan
on it being more of a nine months, a year deal,
assuming that concrete business is like practically shut down
during the winter month period.
You can I mean, still, like if you have a deal going like six
to nine months out of the year, that's awesome.
Obviously, even if it's only a thousand bucks a month, I'm just
that's just a thought as well.
It's a good point.
And I think there's a way you could do it for the year,
but you just need to go in with the right intention.
And what I would do, I'd still do a 12 month deal,
but I'd just pitch it really hard.
Like, hey, this is a year thing.
Like, I only sell a year contract.
It is going to be really slow during the year during December.
So I can either do one of two things
and you can make the one thing seem way better than the others.
I can either pause you for three months and charge you, you know,
fifteen hundred bucks a month for the other nine months.
Or we could just do a thousand bucks a month and you pay year round.
And there's a couple of months you're going to be shut down.
So now they have a perceived savings of a couple of thousand bucks.
They stay with you year round.
You've let them know up front that that's going to happen
and that is going to happen.
And they're just going to be somebody else.
So very important point.
Doesn't mean you can't go into these states, guys.
Doesn't mean you can't go to these areas.
But if you can, I would keep looking, looking to something that's,
you know, Wisconsin's probably good for something that's not that's not concrete.
But again, this comes from experience and nothing sucks more.
And as soon as it starts to get cold, people start calling you, hey, bro,
let's go ahead and pause this bad boy.
And you're like, dude, I can't pause.
Well, OK, I'm sorry.
So good point, Aaron.
Awesome.
And I'm just dropping in the chat right now, the link.
I know we're going to be wrapping it up here in a few minutes.
That's just a link to the Google Drive that's housing the PDF
for the cheat sheet for today's live.
And for those of you that are still on, let me put in the Vimeo link
for early access to these podcasts.
So that's kind of cool.
I've never been part of a when people leave review.
Can we see the name of the person that left a review on the podcast?
It depends on what I think you can only leave reviews on Spotify,
but I'm not too sure.
Well, I'll just let you guys know reviews help.
We appreciate it.
If you guys do leave a review, send me a screenshot posted in the group.
I'll try to hook you guys up with some swag on the next live.
Because those things mean a lot to us.
That's only if you like the podcast and you've actually listened.
I don't want you lying.
I don't want you saying it's good if you don't think it's good.
But we really, really appreciate that.
But yeah, that podcast, that that the one you just shared.
Do you guys go to Spotify or Apple type in digital realistic secrets?
That one is not out and it's not going to be released until Thursday
7 a.m. or 5 a.m. or something like that.
Awesome. Yeah, I just I'm editing.
I put in it was from last week's.
Let me put in the other link.
There we go. It's been edited now.
So you can just save that. That's kind of cool.
And get going with that one.
Yeah, it's why the rank and rent digital real estate model is broken.
Not sure where you're going with that, Nick.
But I will definitely give it a listen.
Yeah, it's it's click bait.
But I follow. I actually come through on the click bait for real.
It makes sense when you listen to it.
So any other questions?
So Kirk just says he has a not now.
Pause the ads was thinking of finding a new bio.
He's asking if you should do that, Kirk.
Yeah, go find a new business owner.
You know, if somebody asks you for a lead, you say not now.
Do you think they want to continue work with you down the road?
Probably not. Yeah, so I agree.
And not now.
Again, I've talked about this.
I've trained about this in digital landlords, guys.
We it's we think that it's like we go to a city and it's yes or no.
Right. It's not.
It's yes or not now, maybe later.
And I view it like an entire city like that.
So if I'm looking, if I'm working Las Vegas, I'm working Los Angeles,
which would be terrible to work.
But I'm going to use that in Phoenix. Right.
I might be working those areas and I might find out that like,
you know, dude,
Las Vegas right now, it's just it's a it's a weird time of year.
And I'm just not getting any traction.
And so I'm not going to quit on the area because I've done all the homework.
I know that's a good area.
But I am going to pause it and go look at other stuff
and maybe try to get a deal in L.A., try to get a deal in Phoenix.
Then I'll come back to it and come back with a fresh set of eyes.
Some new confidence, a new maybe another case study, whatever the case is.
Got it. OK.
Nadine says, Nick, I sent a guy leads this morning.
He seems keen. When do I follow up?
Nadine, are you is she in does that name?
Is she in digital landlords or she not?
I can check. It doesn't sound familiar.
You know.
It does sound familiar.
Nadine, are you in digital landlords?
Because if you are, I'm going to just refer you to a module
which will answer every single one of your questions in two seconds.
Well, we'll see what you answer.
Let's see another. Well, I get that.
Yeah, I don't know if you want to answer for the group still.
Just a quick synopsis summary.
So Nadine's not in deal.
Oh, OK. So just in the free group, then.
So a little summary, Nick.
Yeah, you want to, you're saying?
Yeah, you got it. You want to do that?
Yeah, you do it for the group.
Yeah, this would be the last thing that I'll answer, guys, is.
So it's again, it's an art.
It's it's first of all, when you say follow up, this is this is tough, right?
Like we're not talking face to face, but like you mean follow up?
Are you just sending it?
Because I'm I'm live transfer in all my leads.
So like I'm never not following up from the time that I call you.
Dude, I'm I'm freaking me and you are buds.
I'm calling you. I'm texting you.
I'm not being annoying.
I mean, every time I call you, you're going to you're going to salivate.
You know, I got leads, but you're going to be talking to me a lot.
I'm going to be sending you live transfers.
I'm going to be fine. Did you get that one scheduled?
Did you get that one hooked? Hey, can I call you?
Like me and you are like, I'm sending these free jobs.
They're lit. They're they're digital gold.
I'm not just going to send them and forget.
So the answer, if you haven't talked to him, was yesterday.
You're talking to this person.
You're like you are trying to get this deal
from the second you call until the second you close.
So I don't know what you mean when you say how soon to follow up.
Like you don't ever stop following up.
You're in constant contact until you get the deal.
That's the reality. OK.
Now, when to go for the close.
That's another art thing.
We teach that as I did to landlords to a T.
It's it's also something that you learn and it's there's not an exact answer.
But we have some criteria that we follow as well.
So maybe let's answer one more question if there is one.
Are we good? I think we're good.
Beautiful. Guys, thank you for being on the call.
I appreciate you guys being on the call.
I think we had 20 people, 18 people.
And I I really do enjoy doing these.
I don't care, to be honest with you, if there's two.
Last week, it really frustrated me.
There was two people and it was a Labor Day.
So I told the people that were on, I would make sure to hook them up
and we would run it with more people.
But like I love having 18 people that really want to try.
They really want to do this now to speak to a couple of you guys
that I keep seeing your face again and again and again.
I guess I'm going to ask you, like, what's it going to take for something to change?
Right. Like Jason's on this call.
He's at over thirteen thousand dollars a month right now.
He started in January. I've been seeing some of you guys for way longer
than I've known Jason.
And you're still doing nothing.
You're still refusing to to either take your own, you know, your own action,
spend your own money and pay the piper.
But you also don't want to spend money.
So I don't understand what you think.
Like, do you think that you're just going to wake up
and you're just going to get this business dropped to your lap
that's making you, you know, fifteen, twenty thousand bucks a month?
You're not going to have to work. You're not going to have to suffer.
You're not going to spend any money. You don't have to take it.
Like, I just don't get it.
So there's a couple of you I keep seeing you.
And I love you to death. But for the love,
let's go do something with the knowledge.
Let's quit taking notes and let's go do.
Like, if you're going to choose the path, you have two paths to choose.
Go spend your own money or pay me and get in my program.
That's your two paths.
OK, go spend your own money. Do it today.
And it's a win-win for me, because if you spend it today,
you're going to realize that, holy crap, I just spent a thousand bucks.
I could have just, you know, gone into Nick's program.
I could have paid, you know, started getting into it.
Like, and if you don't, then you're going to get all the information.
So whatever it is, guys, just start, just start.
Go spend some money.
And so you actually see that this isn't as easy as you think it is,
but it's also not as complicated as you think it is.
OK, and that's just for the people I keep seeing.
I love you guys showing up.
But like I said at the beginning, if you don't change anything,
nothing's going to change.
OK, so let's stop getting on these calls and doing nothing.
And I'm going to start.
Aaron, do we have a way to tracking who's on these calls?
Do we have any kind of a thing that shows us in the past
who's been on these calls?
I wouldn't know unless we just manually check the live recordings,
which we could do.
And we might do that.
I would love to see.
And I'm going to start being like, you can get on like three.
And then if you don't have a deal, I'm kicking you out of the entire group
and blocking you from anything I ever create,
because that's time, or at least show me you've spent some money on ads.
At least some of you doing something.
You know what I mean?
That's what I think. OK, guys, thanks for being on the call.
It's a beautiful September 9th.
Live in the laptop lifestyle.
We got we got we got people from Aaron.
Tell these guys where you're at.
I'm in Virginia.
No, what city? It's it's it's.
What's it called? Colonial Heights, Colonial Heights.
I'm going to do a couple of projects, digital real estate in that area today.
Just right in Aaron's backyard, just for fun.
Just kidding. Jason is in.
Are you in Lehigh, Jason, Lehigh, Utah?
Southern Utah County.
Basically the same place.
OK, Utah County. OK, beautiful.
And I am in Dubai.
And there's people all over the world.
And guess what? That's the beauty of the laptop lifestyle.
So, guys, thanks for being on the call.
Grab those resources.
We'll see you next week. Thanks, guys.