So here's what we're going to do, I'm going to pull up my notes, guys.
We are going to, we want to make sure these calls are very, like, we make, these are smaller
sessions, they're more intimate sessions.
We do that on purpose.
We want to deliver like a more intimate experience and only let certain people on these calls
that are serious.
And so welcome to the call.
We wouldn't have like sent you the link if we didn't think you were serious.
And obviously you had to jump through a couple of hoops to get here.
So one of the things that we are going to require though, is if you want to stay on
the call, you need to get your camera on.
The reason why we do that is because we want the people that are on this call to be paying
attention.
So put your camera on, we'll give you a few minutes in case you're laying in bed, which
by the way, if you're in bed and you want to keep staying in bed, we don't mind, but
if it's up to you.
So in order to stand this call in the next five minutes, get your camera on.
The reason being is we want people paying attention.
And if we just wanted a bunch of numbers, we would just put the link in the Facebook
group.
But we want to see your faces, we want to be able to interact, et cetera.
So that said, Aaron, you know what to do, we've got five minutes.
At the end of this call, those people that are still on the call, we're going to screenshot
and we will be putting together a, this one, because it's an interview, it's not necessarily
like a presentation or a training.
We are, we're probably going to just send out the replay.
So we'll probably be sending the replay itself to everybody that's on this call at the end
and we'll stick a screenshot and we'll get you that replay.
So but just as a heads up.
Okay.
I just want to pull up my notes really quick.
Did I miss anything, Aaron?
Sounds good to go.
Okay.
That's beautiful.
I just want to make sure I didn't forget anything.
Pull up my notes.
So yeah, guys, we'll give you a couple of minutes.
Get your cameras on.
You can keep it on mute.
We don't care.
We don't care if you're in bed.
We don't care if you're mowing the lawn.
We just want to see your faces.
We want to see what we're talking to.
And yeah, let's go from there.
I did see one comment popping up said that they spied the Alabama hat.
Yes.
And by the way, if it's like, that's why my voice is gone.
I went to the game on Saturday and it got crazy.
So I lost my voice.
So I apologize for that, but I'm not sick.
I feel great.
I just lost my voice at the game.
That's when you know the game is good, by the way.
Okay.
So guys, today, welcome to the call.
We've got Mike V on this call.
And before we get into the interview, I want to just let you guys know that I don't I
I never want to say that you should believe me.
I never want to say that you should just take my my word for anything.
And I want I want that to be the same case for anybody in the free group.
OK, I see a lot of people at this really irritates me, by the way.
Aaron knows this. Jason knows this.
I'm sure Mike senses this.
But when I see people in the group offering advice,
it drives me nuts because 99 percent of the time, those people aren't even making money.
Right. And I see people just raising their hand, saying,
yeah, send me your free landing page or send me your free script or whatever.
And guys, we don't take a second to think,
does this person even know what they're talking about?
And this is such an overused example, but I'm going to use it.
That's like literally having somebody randomly in the group.
Let's say we're in a fitness group and somebody randomly offers to say,
it says, hey, I want to give you guys my workout plan and my diet,
my workout routine and my diet plan.
Who wants it? Right. And everyone raising their hand.
And no one was saying, hey, let's see a picture and see if you're actually in shape.
Right. That's how crazy it is.
And so I this Aaron, am I wrong or is this the first interview that we've done on these calls
since we changed the format?
First one. First one.
I don't let people like in all the history of our group.
I think that we like unless I've I know for a fact that they've made money,
I don't think that we've ever let anyone on a call.
And I'm 100% sure of that.
Unless they've made money doing this, we've never let them on a call.
And we've never let somebody back twice unless they're making like real money.
So that said, guys, I think you guys know my story.
2016, I started and I'm saying this for the one or two people maybe that don't know.
Eight years ago, I started doing this business model.
Knew nothing about the Internet, knew nothing about online, was making my money,
doing door to door sales, and basically was just looking for a way to make money,
travel, be able to travel, be able to provide for my family, be able to have experiences
and start buying real estate, all these different things.
And I was looking for a model that had certain elements, passive.
It was it was passive in nature.
It was recurring. It was asset based.
It was Internet based.
It was scalable, da da da da da.
And this is the one that I landed on.
And I still, after all these years, have not found one that beats this or even comes close to this.
So in 2020, we did our first seven figures.
2021, we did another seven figures.
And then in 2021, December 1st, we officially launched Digital Landlords,
which is when we started training people how to do this.
Mike V being one of the people that came through our program, as well as Aaron, as well as Jason.
And that is the story.
So just to give you guys a little bit of context so that for those of you that don't know who I am or know much of the story,
I wouldn't be sitting here talking to you and I wouldn't feel right about talking to you if I hadn't made millions of dollars doing this.
OK, so the reason I brought Mike V on and I'm going to have him share his story a bit is Mike V is doing $40,000 per month
doing this business model.
And, Mike, that's US or that's New Zealand dollars?
That's big boy dollars.
Thank you. I love that.
Big boy dollars.
And I knew the answer to that.
I just wanted you to confirm that.
So the guy is 40,000 times 12.
That's almost half a million bucks.
Obviously, it's not all profit, but just just to give you an idea of what's possible, that's what's possible.
So I'm going to today we're going to be interviewing Mike and I want you guys to like we're going to save a good amount of time for Q&A.
This is somebody who is like a grassroots born like made from from the ground up.
He started doing this not that long ago, and he's at $40,000 per month.
And and he's also living a very interesting and really quite inspiring life with what he's doing.
So I'm excited to get into it.
So, Mike V, welcome to the call, brother.
Just having me on again.
Good to catch up.
I appreciate it, man.
I've hit him up a few times recently because he's he's it's such a cool story that I wanted to share it.
So we did have an interview a few weeks ago in digital landlords.
It was it was really popular with tons of people on the call.
A lot of people want to hear what you have to say.
So I'm excited. So today I want to go like, you know, Mike, we've talked before and we've shared like some of the higher level stuff.
I really want to go to like I think I'm looking at the audience here, some of these names.
There are one or two people that are in the in the digital landlords group, which welcome guys.
I see like Hill, he's he just barely joined.
But a lot of these folks are still just kind of like looking at the model, poking around, et cetera.
So we're going to talk about like more of the basics and why you decide to get into the model and some tips and that kind of stuff.
But before that, I want you to just share your just kind of like your two to five minute story of, you know,
where you started and how you got to where you're at right now, because I know there's a lot of people on here that don't know your story.
So let's start with that, man. And tell people where you're at, by the way, right now and where you're from as well.
Yes, we are. So I'm originally from Auckland, New Zealand, currently based in Thailand, just south of Bangkok.
But I mean, to keep it fairly short, about seven years ago, I went to Bali just on like a break after I finished uni.
And I was like, this is so cool here. Like, you know, why can't I just stay in Bali?
Like, why do I have to go home and get a job and go back to the kind of into the system and all that?
And since that moment, I was just trying to figure out how I could make enough money to go back.
So I got back and I basically did corporate marketing, like sitting at a desk, working a nine to five for about five years.
And I was trying to figure out all the side hustle stuff after work and in the weekends.
And I was making about a thousand bucks a month for like four years, which looking back is like this crazy to think about.
But and yeah, I was doing a bit of local regeneration, like some builders and stuff.
And I was like, hey, I'm pretty good at this stuff. You know, I just need to get more clients.
And it just never really happened. I didn't really know how to get more clients.
And that's when I came across what you're doing with the rank and rent.
I was like, this is so cool. I can just do the same thing, like get leads for these builder type companies.
But I own all of the all of the properties. And, you know, it's me.
You don't have to catch up with the monthly meetings like you just.
You just as long as you're getting them the leads, you're providing the value and you can just get paid and it just gives you so much freedom.
Like, as long as the client's phones are ringing, then mine are not.
So I was pretty sold on what Nick was up to, consumed all of the free YouTube videos and then eventually joined.
And when I joined on, I was on about thousand dollars a month and I actually had a ticket booked to go to Thailand in four months.
I was like, you know, I'm just going to book this ticket and make it happen, like whatever happens happens.
And, you know, thankfully, I joined this program and found out about digital landlords.
And within eight weeks, I was on eight thousand a month.
So it took me four years to four years making a thousand bucks a month.
And then within eight weeks of joining Nick's program, I was on eight thousand.
Just couldn't believe it, really. And since then, I had the best years of my life, personal growth, travel,
you know, and then obviously scaled up to forty thousand a month as well while still traveling.
And I've only got one contractor. So, yeah, that's the that's the story.
So you only have I'm going to jump in that last part.
So you only when you say you only have one contractor, what do you mean by that?
I just got one guy who does on my blog post for the SEO sites.
You're you're at forty thousand a month, you and one person.
Yeah, the contractor. Yeah, that's crazy, brother.
That is absolutely insane. OK, so I want to I want to go.
And I had a few questions as you were throughout the story.
And some of these are a little bit just curiosity because I've I've heard your story
and I want to dig in a little bit. And some of them are more on the tactical side.
So why what was it? I think this happens to a lot of us.
Like we we have an experience, maybe it's a trip, maybe it's a interaction, a conversation.
What about Bali was so I'm just curious,
what about it was so attractive to you when you went?
I think it was the main thing was the freedom, like.
I just remember having my scooter being actually in Lombok,
which is a much more quiet island.
Bali's very busy now, but I remember that moment of just like pure peace and like freedom
and just not knowing that I had to wake up to an alarm tomorrow or like answer to anyone.
And since that moment, I've just.
That's just been my mission to to have that freedom whenever I want.
And it's yeah, it's so so so grateful to have that like today.
I honestly felt really tired from traveling the last couple of weeks.
And I just did nothing, you know, just some just some basic stuff and try again tomorrow.
But if I was at a nine to five, I'd have to get up and like grind and go through hell and back.
It's it's crazy, because every single person on this call,
every single one of us, including me, if I if I so wished is like we could do whatever,
like we could change our entire situation.
Right. And I think that we we hear stories like Mike's, your stories like mine.
And they're like, they make you feel good.
They inspire you. But we just think it's not for us.
You know, like, man, it would be so cool if we could move to Bali.
And just set up shop and ride scooters all day and make forty thousand a month.
It sounds fake. It sounds like, oh, that's that's what you read about in the four hour
work week kind of thing. But truly, truly like.
Any one of us could do it, man.
So my question for you is, if you guys didn't catch this part of his story,
Mike went to Bali, he went back like in Bali, he's like, I'm coming back.
You went back and at some point you said, I'm just going to book a ticket.
And I'm basically forcing myself to go back to Bali.
I'm basically forcing myself to make it happen by this date.
Right. So how did you have the confidence to know that you could pull it off?
Because you you hadn't done you've done a little bit of like stuff on your own,
but you hadn't made the kind of money you needed to make.
What gave you the confidence to do that?
I don't really have any confidence that I was shutting myself leading up to leaving.
So when I booked the ticket, I was making a thousand dollars a month.
And that was probably enough to just have like three small meals
staying like a really shitty backpackers, you know, that was probably enough to
have freedom, no luxury or anything.
But I didn't really have any confidence doing it.
I was just turning 30 and I was reading a lot of like stoicism
about like Memento Mori and, you know, the shortness of life and everything.
And I was like, hey, I just I just have to do this.
What were you reading? Meditations?
Is that like the main one you're reading or some other ones as well?
Yeah, I was reading meditations.
I also read a Seneca book on the shortness of life.
That's a really good book.
Definitely recommend that one. That's a bit more about
Seneca, just like observing a lot of the people in Rome at the time
and how they were like squandering their time, he said.
He says so that that that definitely helped me.
I had some urgency to just to book the ticket.
Seneca, the shortness of life on the shortness of life.
Interesting. I just I typed it in, I want to look it up.
So and basically in that book, it was talking about how the Romans
were just squandering their life and he was observing this and going,
what am I doing? And that's I mean, what's the premise of that?
It was just observing like all the royals and the people that.
You know, lots of lots of money, but they were
always kind of like waiting for the future,
like living in the future, not in the moment and living in expectancy
and talking about when they do reach like the older years,
that all of a sudden they just have this not regret, but like,
sure, I need I need to go do all this stuff.
So when you're reading that, you kind of just internalize it.
And even at 30, I still feel quite old,
especially with some of the guys that I meet in Thailand
at a lot younger who made the jump earlier.
So I just wish that I did it sooner.
Yeah, I hold you 30, 30, 30, 31, 31, nearly 32.
OK, so we're I'm 33.
So I can relate. I feel when you're 30, when you're 20,
you think 30 is like you're dead because you think it's old when you're 30.
I've never I feel like I feel like when I looked at people that were 30,
I feel way younger than how I viewed people that were 30.
So so I know exactly what you're saying, man. So
for those people that are
let's just I don't know exactly, but maybe there is.
Maybe there will be some replays that we send out to some people
that are like, quote unquote, older that aren't in their 20s.
Do you think that anybody can do this?
And I don't need you to give me a real
an answer that you think I'm looking for, but do you think it's possible
that anybody can start this business and make money?
Or do you think that there are certain people that cannot?
And again, this is just pure based on what you think.
I think you know, I can tell you that I'm not going to be able to do this.
What you think?
I think anyone can follow the training and
you know, a monkey, a monkey could follow the training,
like, to be honest, the way you've laid everything out in the course is
it is extremely simple, like looking back, it's
it's just so simple.
I don't think everybody has the like the desire
or the mindset to
to go through the tough parts, especially when you're trying
to get your first deal.
Yeah.
You know, my opinion on it, sorry, I was going to give
I'm going to give Aaron cohost really quick
because he so he can control the
volume and stuff. Aaron, did you get the cohost
real quick? Yes. OK, beautiful.
My opinion is that anyone can do it,
but
the people like there are certain people that like have a
proclivity that are going to do better because they're more,
you know, they have more risk tolerance
or they have, you know, more
hunger or whatever. So, yeah, I'm with you, man.
I think anybody on this call, if you guys will
follow the training or the recipe
that's been laid out, which is like do this, do this, do this.
Anybody could do it. And it's funny
because I was having this conversation just yesterday on my flight
home with my dad.
He was asking me this. He's like, so, you know,
there's a specific person that he knew had just
joined my program and he knows this person. He's like, so how
do you think he's going to do? And I said, well, I
said he can do as good as he wants to. I like he's
like, so you think he can actually make good money? And I said, yeah,
I said I gave him some examples
and I'm going to give you guys the same examples. Guys, we have people
that have speech impediments that
are making fifteen, twenty thousand a month. We have people that have
health problems. We have people with accents, which and I'm
giving you guys examples of things that people think are
impediments to their
success or that are supposed to keep them from their success.
We have people that are in other
countries. We have people that
I'm trying to give you single moms, single dads,
people in college that are young, people that are
in their later years that are quote unquote
old. We have everything in between
college kids. We have all sorts
of different types. So, yes, I truly believe anybody can do it, but
it just comes down to the freaking like the will
to do it. And that's it. And so, Mike,
you're at forty thousand a month. There's people
that have been in the free group.
Some of them, I could see their names, still don't have a
deal. Heck, there's some
like, let's be honest, there are people that have even
gotten to the Digital Landlords program.
They got in and decided not to do anything with it that aren't making
money because they're not taking action. What's the
difference between you and people that are not making any money? Like,
how are you at forty K? Why are they not?
Are you more talented? Are you more special?
I mean, I started, I started off my career
walking in the mud, doing landscaping and excavations.
I think the formula
or the system, because I think there's
a formula and system for everything, is just having
the desire and the mindset. So I think that's
what I really had, if I look back,
was the mindset
and sorry, the desire. And I definitely got the mindset from
the book recommendations that you made in the
landlords. You know, once you sign up for the program,
you're committed, right? You're committed financially
and it's a lot easier to take action when you've made a
commitment. So I read the Think and Grow Rich book
back to front, you know, the first week standing
in the mirror there, reciting, you know,
how much you're going to make.
Yeah, so the desire mindset and
there's one last part I think I forgot.
I think everything kind of happens from that.
I was very focused, like, oh, sorry, yeah,
it was taking a risk, like a committed risk.
Like, if I joined landlords and didn't have that ticket book,
then things may have looked a little bit different.
But, you know, if you've got a family or something and you're not,
you kind of like book a flight or something, then
I think it's just equally important to have that desire, whether that's taking your
your kids to school. Like I look at Ryan Dalton and
digital landlords, you know, he's someone I really look up to.
You know, he's into like martial arts,
stuff like that, digital, grand congruent, but he's also got
kids and like a family. So, you know, to see the
to see what he can provide his kids, whether it's like personal training for
jujitsu or education, you know, I'm sure that's
one of his desires to have a nice family home with a dog.
Just getting locked in on that desire and then
following the book recommendation and landlords would be my
recommendation.
OK, why did you choose?
So you said that you were doing some lead generation before
you started doing rank and rent specifically, right?
What kind of lead generation were you doing?
I was building WordPress websites
for local builders and running some ads
and some SEO.
And were you doing that on someone's recommendation
or did you just stumble into it?
I was at my nine to five corporate
stuff learning a bit about marketing and then
I was trying to do free stuff. I remember
I did a couple of free websites back in the day, one for a
a lash extension company, one for a
homegrown honey one.
And then I think two years later when I was still making basically
nothing, I met a guy at a party who had a building company
and he's like, hey, I just want to grow my
building company. So I just did some free stuff for him
and got some good results. So for the next
two years, I think I've got one or two more clients like
in terms of like a long term client.
They didn't really grow, but I was kind of decent at
getting the leads. I just didn't have
the system or the vehicle to land more clients
and get clients. And obviously cold calling is a big part of the
digital landlords, the pre-selling.
Why did you choose
like instead of doing
one of the other models, why
why didn't you choose to do
you know, copywriting or
an SEO agency or
drop shipping, whatever, insert
whatever business model. What made you decide
and I'm asking this because maybe there's
somebody on this call that's like, you know,
number one, in order for you guys to make money at this, you have
to number one, there's a couple different things you have to believe.
Number one is you have to have
made up your mind that you have to do
something, right? Meaning you have to start something
on the side or you have to replace what you're currently doing.
So sometimes I'll get on calls with people.
This is back when I used to be the person that would sell people
into digital landlords. They'd get on a call with me and the first question
I would ask them is, are you
like, do you really believe, do you have the desire to do
something, period? Or are you still deciding
whether you should do something or not? And what I mean by that
is like once in a while I'll get somebody on the call and they'd be
like, yeah, I'm trying to decide if I should
start doing, if I should do something, right? And so guys,
if you're not sold, if you don't realize
that you need to do something, that's step one, right?
And I hope that the fact that you're on this call
is enough that like you know you need to do something.
I'm assuming if you're on this call on a Monday morning, if you're
in the U.S. or maybe a Monday evening if you're not
in Asia, that you know you need to do
something. That's step one. Step two is you need to realize
or you need to pick what do I need to do, right?
And there's a lot of things you could do. You could do drop shipping.
You could do copywriting. You could do SEO. You could build websites.
You could do social media
management. You could do
what other business models? A TikTok
shop. What else
am I missing? What's that?
Coaching, remote sales, affiliate marketing.
Right. These are all online things.
Affiliate marketing, blogging. There's a
thousand different things. And so the next step you guys need to
decide is what am I going to use? And you
used a really important word. You said you didn't know like
the vehicle. So for
you, what was the reason that this vehicle,
what was the number one thing? I know that like there's so many
things for me that make this vehicle
and just to make it simple, we'll call it
website rental or building and renting
simple websites. Why was it that this
model was so attractive? What was the number one most attractive
part of this specific model?
I was watching one of your YouTube videos
and it just really clicked in my head like, hold on a minute,
like I own like the website.
So I've got the power
here. You know, all the other guys that I've done a bit of like
SEO and Google Ads for, I'm building up their business,
building up their stuff. And if they cancel, like it's over.
You know, you'll rank a guy number one in SEO and it's like, hey man,
I'm going to cancel because I've got so many leads coming through.
Whereas this
and also the dynamic, it's not the usual agency client
dynamic where you're getting on monthly calls
like supplicating and telling them what you've got planned
for the next month. It's like, here's your leads,
you know, pay me my retainer. I'm going to make sure you're good
and you just leave me alone because I can go back to
jumping on the scooter and doing what I want.
I love the thought of Mike V
on a scooter around
Thailand. It's just, it's a good thought. I like that,
dude. I like that a lot. There's actually a Duke, we're on a Ducati
1100 CC a couple of weeks back.
But originally we started on the 50 CC scooter in Bali
and we've upgraded to the Ducati.
Dude, that's rad, man. I love
everything about that. And I need to come out, I would love to come out and
check out the place. I've never been to Thailand, by the way.
I'm going to come. Oh, no way. Never, never.
But I want to. It's been on the list for a while, so I'll make it happen.
Here's what I want
to ask really quick is, Aaron, are you still on the call?
Yes. Aaron, I'm going to put you on the spot.
What was your favorite thing about RankinRent?
And Aaron has a really, we had an interview
Aaron one of these days because he's one of the most persistent people
I've ever met and I love him for that.
What was the biggest thing for you?
You're a very, you study a lot.
You are pretty logical.
What was the reason that you decided that RankinRent was the vehicle?
Just for everyone here, because everyone has their own reasons.
What was the number one thing for you?
Yeah, I mean, a couple years ago when I first discovered it, I had
boxes in my mind that had to check in order for me to be able to
do something to make money. And this was the model
that checked most boxes.
Was there a specific box that stood out?
There was a myriad of like equally important
like one, I had to do it from home because I couldn't drive.
I needed it to be where there was low.
Aaron was 16 when he discovered this.
So he's like, I got to do something I can do at my, you know.
Yeah, and it had to be like low financial barrier to entry.
And it had to be do something that I could learn the skill.
And those were the three big ones.
And then there's a couple other ones I'm trying to remember.
But yeah, like that looks like a bunch and it had to work.
Like, come on, we've all looked at drop shipping
and affiliate marketing. And it's like, yeah.
Anyway, so those were the boxes in it.
Dude, I remember watching your YouTube video.
To be fair, I saw one guy first talk about it.
And then in the trending now or not, well, it wasn't trending for sure.
It was the recommended watch section in YouTube, which I usually dislike
because that's a time waster gets it down the rabbit hole.
But it had Nick Wood video with like super dark background
could barely see your face with like six views.
And I clicked on it and that's when it made sense.
So, yeah, for sure.
Here we are. Here we are.
And OK, thanks for jumping in, Aaron.
Guys, the reason I wanted to ask is everyone has their reasoning.
And I know when you're not in the model, like for me and Mike and Aaron,
Jason, I think he might have to hop off because he's he's literally jumping on a call,
which is awesome.
I mean, just to show you like we're practicing what we preach
when you're not in it, it seems so it's it's a tantalizing idea,
but it still kind of seems like like there's that little bit of you that still doubts.
Are these people actually making money?
Mike V, did you ever have that doubt?
Like, dude, this guy's full of crap.
Maybe this doesn't really work.
Or did you just blindly believe?
Your answer is fine. I'm just curious.
No, I mean, it makes sense.
You know, local businesses need leads, you know,
and people use Google to find local businesses.
So I didn't think it was farfetched at all.
I think it's one of the, you know, more classic business models
where you're just getting a local business, local business, more business and taking a cut.
And I agree 100 percent.
It was kind of the same like I kind of I don't want to say I blindly followed.
But for me, all that it took was understanding conceptually what was going on.
But when I joined my first program back in 2016,
I didn't ask the guy that sold me the program to show me a stripe account.
I probably should have.
I didn't ask who some, you know, I didn't see case studies like, you know,
I think we have like 150, 200 plus case studies of people from all walks of life that are making money.
I didn't see that kind of stuff. I was like, oh, that makes sense.
How much is your program? Oh, eight thousand dollars.
Boom. Let's go. You know, that kind of a thing.
And I think that could get you in trouble.
But I think for people like me and Mike, we kind of like my mentality is I'm going to figure it out.
You know, as long as you can show me the map, I'm going to figure it out.
And I heard her Mosi talk about this like he's like all the programs I've ever joined.
He's like, I joined it as a student and then I quickly became the top person in that group.
And then after I became the top person, I had people reaching out and then I did my own thing.
And he's like, that's kind of the trend. And that's exactly what happened with me.
That's exactly what happened with Mike. I joined my first group.
I didn't really I was like, dude, I didn't see anyone making really good money.
So I'm going to figure out how to make really good money.
Got to one hundred thousand dollars a month, started talking about it, started my own and Mike, he joined.
He's, you know, in Bali riding around his scooter and and figured this out.
And he's doing he's at forty thousand bucks a month. He's one of our top students.
I think you're at least top three. I know Ryan Dalton is up there.
I know that there's a few, but you you might be number two or like you're one of the top students in our program.
So anyway, guys, everyone's going to have a different reason.
But I just want to let you guys know that if you're sitting there going, I don't know if this is actually as good as it sounds or if people are actually making money.
That's totally normal. And it's completely fine to have those doubts.
But I guess you should just like intuitively look at it and go.
All right. Either either I have Mike completely lying through his teeth.
I have Aaron lying through his teeth. I have Jason lying through his teeth.
I have my brother Porter lying through his teeth, you know, or this actually does work.
Or and I'm also lying repeatedly on my videos, which very well could be the case.
And I could very well be capable of that for all you know.
But it sounds like a lot of work to continually.
I'd still watch them for the comedy aspect if it was BS.
Speaking of bad videos. Yeah.
Guys, Aaron, Aaron said he made a good point when I started digital landlords.
I started it December 1st, 2021.
And in March of 2022, I was on a trip to Mexico with my family.
And I realized like I should probably start doing some of this branding stuff.
I should probably start sharing some of this on YouTube.
And if you don't have a YouTube channel or you've never done it, it's pretty intimidating to like make that commitment.
Because you are no matter how confident you are, you're just all you're thinking about is, oh, my gosh, people that I know are going to see this.
And who am I? And they're going to think that I think I'm this or that or the rest.
And I remember I'm like, I just have to do it.
And I made like a couple of videos and I was super stressed out.
I went up into my into my room. My kids are at the pool.
And I I told my wife, I'm like, hey, I'm going to go up.
I'm going to make some videos. And I was so uncomfortable.
And I'm like, who am I to talk about this business model?
Meanwhile, I'd made millions of dollars doing this.
But the point is what I'm going to bring up is that I just did it.
I just started right. The videos Aaron's talking about.
I think Aaron was at the video. I was sitting at this desk with no lighting and no it was no intro.
It was the title was like seven hundred characters long.
And it was like just really weird topics kind of stuff.
Those kind of videos, dude, for sure, like super nice components of the business model.
It was like why you should stop waiting for your website to rank before you sell a flat fee deal.
Like no one would know what you're talking about unless you knew what ranking rent was.
But I just I want to make this point like, guys, you're not going to have all the answers.
You're not going to you're not going to be able to just like know 100 percent.
There's always going to be an element of uncertainty.
And if you're someone that's sitting there waiting for things to be 100 percent certain, it's not going to happen.
Now I want to talk about this really quick and then we're going to get the Q&A.
Timing is never going to be perfect, guys.
It's not. By the way, speaking of that, did we did we release that episode on why you should start now from on our podcast?
Yes. Aaron, we go get the link and I want you to share that in the chat, guys.
I just did a podcast episode on Thursday and it's called Why You Should Start Now.
Talking about this quote that my dad always told me, make hay while the sun shines.
There is never going to be a perfect time. It's never going to be the perfect conditions.
Mike, when you started this, was it the ideal time for you to jump in and start doing this full time?
Was it the ideal time? I already know the answer is no.
How did you still I'm just going to answer. No, it wasn't.
How did you still get yourself to take action even though it wasn't a perfect time?
No, it was terrible timing. I was about to drop a third of my net worth, which wasn't a lot at the time.
And I was quitting my safety net job in 10 weeks.
It's probably the worst time possible, but actually it was the best time possible because I had to make it work.
I love that. It was the worst time, but might have been the best time.
Guys, I'm telling you right now in this podcast episode that we're going to put in the comments.
I talk about this. I don't care what it is in life.
I don't care if it's when you're going to get married, when you're going to have kids, when you're going to start the business,
when you're going to have that tough conversation, when you're going to go do that volunteer trip,
when you're going to ask that girl out or the guy out.
It does not matter. I promise you the timing is never going to be perfect.
It's never going to be a good time.
And you can either be one of two types of people.
You can be the person that's always going to wait for the time to be perfect.
Oh, I'm going to wait until I look at this thing or I check that or oh, we're going on this trip.
We're going to wait till the trip's over or once this thing happens or oh, it's October.
And we have Halloween coming up and then we have Thanksgiving.
And then let's just start at the first year.
You know, you know the type of person that's always starting the diet, but it's on Monday, right?
I'm going to start on Monday, right?
We all know that type of person. We've all been that type of person.
The timing is never going to be perfect, just so you know, I promise you.
And you can either be that person that's waiting or you can be the type that's like me and Mike.
And I would I dare say Aaron as well.
And I dare say Jason, even though I don't think he's on the call anymore.
The type of person that I am is that when I feel like doing something, I just do it.
And guys, sometimes that is terrible timing.
Mike, have you ever done 75 hard?
No, I never really did that because I've always been pretty disciplined anyway.
Yeah, I didn't really do anything for you. And I totally get that.
I've only done it once. I'm not a big Andy Frisella guy.
I'm not a big like, you know, I actually think a lot of that stuff has value.
I think the cold plunges are probably good for you.
I just don't love when people post about it, that kind of stuff.
But anyway, there's this thing called 75 hard.
And I heard about it. And guys, I just like I just felt like I needed to do it.
And I just started it. And I it was like in the winter, it was cold.
I had a cruise coming up, a trip coming up.
All these different things. And I just felt like I needed to do it because if I didn't do it, then I would never do it.
And I remember being on my cruise and doing my second workout of the day up at the top of the cruise ship at 12 a.m.
And not being able to eat the desserts, all these different things and being like, Nick, you're such an idiot.
Why don't you just end? But then at the same time, realizing like that's why I am where I am because I just take action when I feel like it.
And so I guess my point is, is I want you guys to understand whoever's on this call that's waiting for the perfect time.
There's never going to be a perfect time. There's just not. That's just that's just how it is.
So for sure. You got to jump in the trenches with anything.
You know, there's definitely an element of trenches like I've grinded super hard leading up to leaving Thailand.
You know, I was working five days a week at nine to five. I was working on this two hours a day after work.
I was going to the gym six days a week. You know, I take some days off and there's definitely a lot of time in the trenches.
But what really carried me through was the fact that I already committed to the program and I was reading the Think and Grow Rich books.
So the subconscious mind was programmed like to get through.
And when the moments do get tough, which they will, you still knew what that that dream outcome was and the consequences of not achieving it.
Yeah. Yep. Same, man.
When I started, I had my second child on the way. I just bought a house. I just bought another car.
I was in the middle of the job that provided my entire yearly income for the whole year in five months,
meaning if I messed it up or I distracted myself too much, I was risking my money.
It's paying the bills. I was door knocking. I had no energy.
I had no time, but I just went for it and I figured it out.
And so those of you that are like, I don't have time. You do. You do.
I promise. Especially you that don't have kids or that don't have other stuff like I had kids.
I had a full time door knocking job. I had a wife. I was all these different responses.
I was managing a team of guys that were also knocking with me.
So anyway, I just want to talk about timing is never going to be perfect.
Don't wait for it to be perfect. If you're that type of person, it's it's it's just going to be tough, man.
You're going to sit there and wait forever. And we all know that type of person.
They're sitting there. Oh, I don't want to start the campaign because I have, you know, I've got that double that I've got that shift with those extra hours.
And what if a lead comes in while I'm at work? It's like, dude, you step out or you miss the call.
You go in the bathroom and call it like you just figure it out.
You would like if you guys are those type of people, it's going to be very, very difficult for you.
So anyway, I've talked enough. I want to I do want to ask one more thing.
And then any questions you guys have, we've got about 10 minutes.
I'm going to let you guys ask questions in the comments.
I'm going to have Aaron kind of filled those questions. You can ask Mike anything.
But Mike, tell me about you said you're a pretty disciplined person.
What does that mean? Are you disciplined with what you eat?
Is it your schedule? Is it your routine? Is it your like your thoughts?
When you say you're a pretty disciplined person, what do you mean?
I guess when I've got a goal or something that I want to achieve, then, you know, I'll be pretty consistent with just the daily actions.
For example, at the start of the year, I was on about 10k a month in December and I was like, I want to get to 40k a month.
And I just asked myself, what is what does a 40k a month version of me do?
And then just had the discipline to embody that.
And then here we are now doing it.
I was really always been in fitness and stuff.
So I think that that comes with like not really drinking and going to the gym and just and eating well healthy.
I think like right now I'm super tired and jet lag and flu and I haven't been able to like make money or work hard.
So I think health help is a really important aspect of being successful, you know, launching a business as well.
Do you think that people that are not disciplined can learn to be disciplined?
Yeah, I think it's I remember watching a video back when I was driving to the corporate job doing digital landlords.
And it's that classic motivation video where he's like, you know, when you want to when you want to be successful as much as you want to breathe.
Then you'll be successful.
And off the back of that, you have to have the discipline like you say, which is like so ingrained in my head, which I'm very grateful for is you have to do what needs to be done when it needs to be done, regardless of how you feel.
And that's why I think your program and you as a person has been so awesome to be a part of this because of like your mindset and and just like the aggression that you have with with getting stuff done.
Because you need to just you need to be disciplined with decisions you make and join up, you know, getting home from work.
You don't want to do life transfers, but you've got to call them up.
All that kind of stuff.
It's easy on Sunday afternoon or Saturday afternoon when you're thinking about you kind of daydreaming about doing this job and living in Bali or living in Thailand and thinking about all this stuff.
It's really easy.
But then about Wednesday, you've had a couple bad nights of sleep.
You've got your butt kicked by some of these business owners, you know, and I mean your butt kick like you've got yelled at you.
You know, you're not feeling 100% gym.
You're sore because of the gym, all this different stuff.
And then by about Wednesday, it's really easy to start slipping.
But it's so true, man.
Once you figure out what it takes, like let's take anyone on this call.
Let's say someone on this calls at zero dollars right now in this business and they want to get to 10k a month.
There is an exact map of how you're going to get there, right?
There is a certain number of people you need to call in order to get a certain amount of life transfers or opportunities to live transfer like trials.
And there's a certain amount of trials you need to do to close a certain number of deals to get to 10k.
And once you map that out, which we do train you how to do inside of digital landlords.
Once you map that out, guys, all you have to do is just do the things that you have to do.
And that's it. And you have to do them when they need to be done.
And the hard part is when you don't feel like it like Mike V. Right.
He's not feeling great today. He's jet lagged.
He's sick, but he's on this call.
Like today, it's Monday. It's I woke up at 630. I've been traveling all weekend.
I didn't get much sleep. I was on two red eyes.
It's my daughter's birthday. I've got every excuse in the world to be like, yeah, let's just skip this week.
You know what I mean? But you just got to get in the habit of, hey, I on Mondays for me, I do this call and I don't care if I'm sick.
I don't care if I didn't sleep last night. I just do this call.
And Mike's done the same thing. You know, he has to do certain things.
He has to call business owners at certain times and he has to do certain things.
And that's why he's at 40k.
And so it's not rocket science. It's not rocket science.
Just doing what needs to be done when it needs to be done.
And sometimes you don't feel like doing it. You gotta do it anyway.
So great. Great point, bro.
Aaron Vogler, do we have any comments, any questions, anything in the chat yet?
Yes, Matt Torres says great to see Mike is successful.
Absolutely. Like Mike, it was so cool when I first heard that you hit 40k because I remember watching your interview.
I joined a few months, I think, after you had had that interview and I was just binge watching all this stuff.
And I distinctly remembered yours because you kept harping on thinking Grow Rich.
And I like that book a lot, too. And it was so cool to hear like less than two years later or two years later, whatever, that you'd like kept it going.
And you were a pretty quiet guy. I mean, you don't like you're not super.
It's not like you're having daily comments in the group, but it was so cool to just see you were grinding for two years and you hit that.
Yeah, it's awesome. I just for the compliment.
And yeah, back in the day, I was posting heat, but haven't posted too much.
But it's always good to catch up with them. Everyone in the group.
Yeah, you know, so it's good to point out, Mike, is that Mike V has gotten to 40k.
And what has it been? Two and a half years, two years and some months.
What has it been? About two years. Yeah, two years.
He's got the 40k in two years. But what you guys might not have caught is that there was like a year of that that Mike basically just went and lived life.
Like he got to 10k and then he and that was his plan.
And that's what I love about Mike is he's very disciplined, but he's intentional.
And if like and that's what I think you guys need to realize is you don't have to be on all the time.
If you tell yourself, hey, I'm going to work four days a week and then I'm going to frickin Fridays.
I'm going to go and I'm going to go see the country that I live in.
I'm going to go do this. It's all about being intentional.
So, Mike, for Mike, he got to 10k.
And then what do you spend like a year basically like just traveling because that's what you plan on doing.
Yeah, we got to 10k and then I traveled all over Southeast Asia for a whole year.
And then I was like, OK, let's scale it up.
Yeah, yeah, I remember that.
I remember you. That was your story.
And you're like, and you know what I admire about that is that was your plan.
And, you know, it's kind of like that.
Have you heard that song by Macklemore called Make the Money?
You ever heard that?
A really good song. It's called Make the it's like says make the money.
Don't let the money make you.
And it's like we have we make money not for money's sake.
We make money for a specific reason.
And so anyway, I just admire that you you had a plan.
You wanted to move to Thailand to have a lifestyle.
And you wanted this to fund the lifestyle.
And then once you did it, you went and executed.
And then when you decided to get busy, you decided to get busy.
And now you're at 40k.
And I have no doubt that if next year you decide to go and hit 100k, you're going to hit 100k.
I truly believe that.
So anyway, Matt Torres, shout out to Matt Torres.
And yeah, shout out to Mike for making it happen.
What else we got, Aaron, anything?
Yeah, for sure. We got like two questions here.
So Eric Funk says great conversation, guys.
I have a general Google ask question.
Are you setting keywords for exact match or phrase match or mix of both?
Yeah, I just run phrase match.
You know, concrete contractor, concrete specialist, concrete layer, concrete company.
I think concrete plus city, all is phrase match.
I would say that negative keywords can be you definitely want to consider those.
But even on top of that, you know, if you've got four campaigns live, which you should,
which is what I had at every given point leading up to leaving, you know,
you could set up the exact same campaign in a different city and get zero leads from it.
So yeah, just just set up the basics.
Use your phrase match.
But just remember that it's more important to have three guys on trials,
because not all of them are going to work, no matter what, how you what keywords you've got.
Absolutely. We got an action.
I'm just letting Jason in already.
We'll see if he closed that deal.
While you let Jason, I want to say one thing really quick.
That question lets me know that whoever that person is and not to call that person out,
but just like that person is the type that's there.
You're trying to avoid paying the piper.
OK, so and I can tell because that question is specific enough that you you've watched a lot of content.
You've listened to a lot of stuff.
You're doing everything except for paying the piper.
So you either got to pay the piper, you got to pay someone that pays the piper.
You know, you're not going to jump on and like every single little nuanced question.
This is all the stuff that's covered.
But the question I would ask that person is like, why are you wasting time trying to pick up a piece here,
pick up a piece there? Why not just go in and like get the full thing?
And so I could just tell by based on how specific that question is,
that you're trying to avoid doing everything but just paying the piper.
So for me, what I did is when I ran Google Ads, like for me, I bought I bought a program that spent eight grand.
That's how I learned the basics.
Then I spent up one point four million dollars learning ads.
That's how I learned the answers to questions you're asking.
Mike, he did the opposite.
He paid me.
I taught him ads and he learned.
And of course, he's learned other stuff since then through running his own campaigns.
But just to remind everyone, like we're going to do everything we can on these calls to get you guys value.
I mean, that was a great answer and a correct answer.
But just understand that like no matter what, no matter what way you slice it,
there are laws of the universe and you can't avoid them.
And one thing you can't do is you can't get a six pack without putting in work.
And I know there's some of these people out there taking ozempic, whatever, and or taking steroids to use the male example.
I know males use ozempic.
And I know they think they're cheating the system.
But if y'all don't think there's negative side effects to taking steroids or taking ozempic, we'll see.
We'll see.
There's no shortcut to a six pack.
There's no shortcut to a million dollars a year.
There's no shortcut to having a great relationship.
So that's just the facts.
Jason already did you close the deal or did he know show you?
Yeah, I closed it.
Yeah, buddy.
What'd you get?
Fourteen hundred per month in concrete.
My man.
Concrete saturated, Jason.
No, it is.
There's you just got to put in the due diligence, man.
Put in the work to find a good area and go get those deals.
It's crazy.
Amazing.
Fourteen hundred dollars a month deal.
Concrete live.
Yeah, Jason, it is saturated, bro.
Why are you still in concrete, dude?
Dude, did you guys not know rank and rent saturated?
Why you guys?
You know, honestly, like, is it as many people as you see in the rank and rent industry?
Like, you know, just this overall, like, I think there's so little people that are willing to take the action that we're willing to take over here and deal that.
It's not as saturated as you think.
There's so many sites that actually aren't being rented out, like you've mentioned several times.
And, you know, people can rate websites, but how many people are actually calling business owners and trying to close deals?
Not very many.
There's a lot of hungry business owners out there.
How much does that put you?
What are you at now per month?
I don't know if you lost any.
In the meantime, what are you at per month?
I'll have to go recount because I lost a twelve hundred dollar per month deal and then he's in a cold area.
So I'm going to we're still going to talk about it, but the lead slowed down, so I lost him.
So we're actually, I think I'm at thirteen, six hundred, but I got two more closing calls scheduled.
So we're going to get those numbers up before winter hits.
Amazing.
Was that Aaron?
Yeah, I was going to say real quick.
I know we're going to be wrapping it up soon, but this is just the last question.
I know Laura's been on from the beginning.
She had asked, and Mike, this is more directed to you, but I'm sure Jason, I mean, you're at over 10K in like less than three months when you started to actually get focused.
But the question is, what are some mindset tips that helped you shift from 10K to 40K?
This is for Mike.
Yeah, this is mainly for Mike.
OK, also, what I want you to do while he's answering that question, Aaron, is I want you to screenshot everyone that's on this call so we can get them to reply.
Secondly, is I want you to drop a link for anybody that is that realizes that they would rather pay somebody that's paid the piper.
So drop a link to digital landlords for those that actually want to apply.
Again, you don't have to apply, guys. I'm going to keep showing up for these calls.
I'm going to keep being in the live group.
I guess I just sit there and I ask, why the hell are we still trying to avoid the thing that's got to happen?
So for those of you that are finally like, OK, it's time.
I want you to drop that link while Mike's answering the question.
So go ahead, Mike, answer that question.
What's the mindset shift that went from 10 to 40?
Yeah, from 10 to 40.
My mindset was pretty good because I honestly just wanted to make 2K a month.
That was my original goal. That was the price of freedom.
So hitting 10K a month, like, hey, if I was able to do something that I previously thought was completely impossible, then, you know, I've got supreme confidence and literally just picking.
It was just like I said before, just pick a number and then work back from what that version of Laura or whoever it is is doing.
And I think on the side note, being around other people who are making similar numbers can definitely help because that will just make everything more real.
You know, everyone's talking about 40K or, you know, what are these people doing that you're not kind of thing?
Like Nick says, it's not it's equally about what you need to do to get there, but also what you need to not do.
And a big part of that is keeping things simple.
You know what I was just going to say is I was going to say, I don't know if you guys have noticed on this interview, but Mike, Mike's not telling like and this is what I noticed this about everyone doing big numbers, right?
And Dalton, the same thing. It's like, Mike, like when you guys ask Mike questions, he's giving you very simple answers.
And I think probably maybe some of you guys are expecting like some intricate answer or this crazy niche that he's in or do this little hack or whatever.
And it's like I've learned more than anything, being around people that are successful, that the people that are making the most money are the ones that are just disciplined in doing the simple stuff that works and disciplined in not doing the stuff that does not move the needle.
That's it. And I could tell Mike, you're very disciplined in not doing what shouldn't be done and doing what should be done.
I'll kind of say one more thing. Just what you said to me in our last interview, you know, when I was making 8K a month, you just said, Mike, all you need to do is do this, you know, 10 more times, 15 more times, and then you're going to be a 30K a month, whatever.
So that was an extremely simple way to look at the task ahead and then just show up daily.
That was it for me, man. I heard somebody talk about something they said, and I don't know why it clicked that time.
They said, if you've made $1,000 doing this business model, you have a $1,000 a month client, why don't you have 100 of those?
Why are you trying to reinvent the wheel? Why aren't you just doing that 100 times? Or why don't you, instead of doing 100 times, why don't you double your price and do it 50 times?
And I was like, yeah, that's what I should do. I should stop trying to do SEO, build websites, do consulting, do social media management.
Why don't I just do this one thing that works really, really well and just do it 100 times? And that's when I scaled up to 100K.
And it was like, I think I'm just so stupid. I needed to hear an answer that was that simple. And it was like, oh, yeah, that makes sense.
That's such a good answer. Just do it. Do it 100 more times. It's so simple.
That's it. It's like that phrase, kiss, keep it stupid, stupid, simple, or keep it simple.
For me, it's keep it simple, stupid, right? Either one.
Just gotta get that first deal and then that's it. Just do it 50 more times, 10 more times, whatever number it is that will allow you to live the lifestyle that you want.
Guys, it's not rocket science. I keep saying rocket scientists. It's been a long weekend. It's not rocket science. I'm nothing special.
I know, speaking for me, I know that everyone else on this call, Mike, Jason, these guys have really special qualities, but they weren't born with some...
We're not Bill Gates caliber minds. We're just people that are simple, doing the simple work, but doing it again and again and again, even though we don't feel like doing it.
Doing it on a... Jason just barely scheduled a closing call on a Monday at 7 a.m. That just shows you where his head's at. He's grinding, man. I love that.
So, Mike V, thank you for being on the call, man. Do you have anything else you want to add, Aaron?
I think we're good. Great call.
Amazing call. For those of you that were on this call, we're going to get you guys to replay and we will be doing another call next week.
But again, I would just recommend, guys, if you actually are serious about making money, you either got to just hunker down and say, hey, I'm going to do what Nick did and spend five years and $1.4 million,
or you can do what Mike did, and it's a much quicker option to say, hey, let's just get the blueprint. Same with Jason, same with Aaron, and let's go and learn that and get there quicker.
And basically, Mike's basically got to $40K in a year because he took a year off, but obviously we can't say that, but essentially getting to $40K in a year.
So anyway, that said, guys, and Jason, I think Jason started in January. He's eight, nine months into this, 10 months into this, and he's at almost $14K per month.
So, proof's in the pudding. Appreciate you guys being on the call. Thank you, Mike. V, go get some sleep, get feeling better, and we'll talk soon.
Thanks, guys. Bye.